本作品之片源、字幕均來自互聯網，僅供個人影視製作的學習、交流之用。版權歸原電影公司所有。
果然字幕組
www.grzmz.com
果然字幕組出品
監製 非一般的島
♪ 上帝啊 你創造了我
翻譯 三弟 老德 大牛餅乾
♪ 但我沒有那麼信任你
翻譯 蝦餃 咪咪姐 傻得
♪ 上帝啊 我堅持走自己的路
翻譯 嚕啦啦 顧盼
♪ 你想如何擺弄我的命運都行
校對 蜥蜴
♪ 我就在這裡
後期 肥鶯
♪ 不達目的不罷休
♪ 我流連酒吧忘返
♪ 壞女人企圖讓我春心蕩漾
美工 11
♪ 清晨醒來 渾身灼熱
壓制 Rat73 OrcaZ
♪ 一邊喝酒一邊冥想
♪ 撒旦魔鬼都是虛幻
♪ 邪惡是由你本心所造
♪ 感謝上帝 讓那草木燃燒
♪ 天生我才開大奔向前跑
♪ 我在路上 抽著大麻
♪ 兄弟 不要擔心大家
♪ 鄰居來敲門
♪ 讓我們調低音量
臥槽
Jesus!
♪ 我  我要
♪ 要抽一口
♪ 喔喔喔
♪ 我需要
不好意思 對不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
♪ 要抽一口
♪ 誰能阻擋的了我
♪ 我要抽到飛
♪ 需要它 需要它活下去
對不起 對不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
史泰
登島
國
王
♪ 需要活下去
回來
Get back!
我喜歡這個電影
I love this movie.
他們在史泰登島拍的這個
They-they shot this on Staten Island.
- 唷   - 哦
- Whew! - Oh!
- 哦  - 我的媽呀
- Oh! - Ooh, God!
- 好贊  - 沒錯
- Awesome.- Hell yeah.
嘔
Ew!
對我的口
That's my shit.
這電影邏輯不對啊
This movie makes no sense.
為什麼 為什麼政府允許人類清除計劃的存在
Why-why would the government make a purge legal?
- 很明顯是為了讓人洩憤啊    - 就是
- Clearly to let them blow off some steam. Hello.- Yeah.
- 那你可以去做水療啊 - 是的 或是去找心理醫生啊
- That's why you go to the spa. - Yeah. Or the therapist.
或者去做美甲
- Or get your nails done.
或者殺點人咯
Or murder some folks. Hmm?
我說 大傢伙兒 我把Tara帶來
I mean, come on, guys. I-I brought Tara over
就是為了讓大家走出這個地下室
so that we could get out of this basement.
我們出門玩兒吧  去蹦迪吧
Let's go out. Let's go dancing.
- 我喜歡蹦迪   - 去做點什麼別的吧
- I love dancing. - Let's do something.
我們不出門
We don't go out.
我們不蹦迪
We don't dance.
- 看《人類清除計劃》 還不夠嗎 - 不夠
- The Purge is not enough for you? - No.
還有誰喜歡蹦迪的
Does anybody else like dancing?
- 我喜歡  - 是的 我
- I like it.-  Yes, me!
- 你喜歡嗎   - 我喜歡蹦迪
- You do? - I love dancing.
是的
Yes.
他超愛  他蹦得可好了呢
He loves... He's a really good dancer.
你最喜歡的招式是
What's your favorite move?
就那種有律動的搖擺
It's kind of like a shake.
- 搖擺 額   - 說不上來啦
- A shake? That's...- I don't know.
就跟著音樂搖擺唄
I just do whatever the m-music tells me to do.
迪廳裡只有混賬
There's nothing but douchebags at these clubs.
- 我喜歡呆這裡 安全  - 噢 別這樣嘛
- I love it here, man. It's safe.- Oh, but, come on.
你這是打算坐這裡一整天
God, you just sit here all day,
- 吸大麻  - 然後互相打手槍嗎
- and then smoke weed and jerk each other off.   - Yeah.
挺好的呀
That sounds amazing.
我朋友從來沒有給我打過手槍
I've never been jerked off by any of my friends.
我也沒有
Me, either.
我蠻喜歡你紋身的
I like your tattoos.
- 我就知道你會喜歡 好看吧  - 那些是
- I knew you would, right? - Those are...
- 哦 我去  - 別 別跟他搞
- Oh, my God. That...  - No, don't talk to him.
- 他有 他有披衣菌   - 過去有
- He has, he has chlamydia. - I had.
- 我的天   - 已經治好了
- Oh, my God. - Had chlamydia.
- 那是可治癒的毛病   - 是你介紹給我認識的妹子傳給我的
- It's curable.- And you introduced me to the girl that gave me chlamydia,
所以基本上是你傳染給我的
so you basically gave me chlamydia.
你助長了披衣菌的傳播
You assisted the chlamydia.
他沒有醫保
He doesn't have insurance.
- 他沒那錢治的  - 還好啦
- He can't get the meds. -  It's fine.
我其實給他紋了幾個
I act... I actually did some of those.
哦真的嗎
You did?
我必須得代表我的島
You know I got to rep the island.
- 史泰登島  - 哇喔  史泰登
- Staten Island. -  Wow, Staten.
- S.I. 你懂的  - 嗯
- S.I., you know. - Yeah.
- 看起來很贊哦  - 謝謝
- Looks so good. - Thank you.
- 你也有一堆紋身  - 是啊
- You have a bunch of tattoos also. - Yeah.
- 那個日期是啥意思  - 啊 哦
- What is that date? - Oh.  Ooh.
呃 那天我爸去世了
Uh, that's, uh, the date my Dad died.
啊天哪 你爹去世了啊 不好意思啊
Oh, my God, your dad died? I'm so sorry.
沒啥的啦 還好了 沒事的
Don't be. It's fine. It's totally cool.
- 怎麼去世的呀   - 哦哦哦
- So, what happened? -  Ooh!
- 這就不用問了吧   - 別
- Okay, you don't need to ask. - No.
- 別別別  - 別問了
- No, no, no, no. - Don't ask that.
不是太禮貌啊
It's kind of inappropriate.
額 他是個 消防員
Uh, he was a, he was a fireman.
所以 他死於一場火災
So, he died in a fire.
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 我們知道啊  - 我們知道啊
- Yeah, we knew. - Yeah, we knew.
- 只是我們不喜歡討論這個  - 我們知道
- We don't like to talk about it. - We knew.
所以我們才不怎麼提
That's why we don't bring it up.
- 跟Scott道個歉啊  - 確實有點不禮貌
- Apologize to Scott.- It's the right thing to do.
- 你得道歉  - 不道歉就滾出去吧
- You should say sorry. - Apologize or get out.
這不對
It's not okay.
Scott 呃 我只想說我真心抱歉啊
Scott, um, I just wanted to say that I'm really sorry
- 我不該問你紋身含義的  - 啊對
- that I asked about your tattoo.-  Yeah.
怎麼了
What?
他不介意的啦 還好了
He doesn't care. It's fine.
- 他不介意的   - 你看他
-  He doesn't care. - Look at him.
- 他一直在笑  - 我不管
- He's laughing so much. -  I don't care.
我們經常提起他過世的老爹的啦
We talk about his dead dad all the time.
- 咚咚咚  - 誰呀
- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
不是你爹啊
Not your dad.
我最喜歡這個梗了
That's my favorite one.
我去 太好笑了
Oh, my God, that's so funny.
我們經常拿這個打趣兒
We've made so many jokes about it.
我去 我一點兒
Oh, my God, I don't even...
- 我一點兒都不想他  - 太搞笑了
- I don't even miss him at all. -  So funny.
是啊
Yeah.
哦
Oh!
哦 是的 就是這樣 很好啊
Oh, yeah, yeah,that's pretty good.
就這樣 就是這樣
Keep-keep doing that! Keep doing that!
你爽嗎
Are-are you, are you happy?
爽爽 老娘太爽了 就這樣接著來
Yes, yes, it's fucking great! Keep going!
別停 別停
No, wait, d-d... don't stop!
額 你高潮了嗎
Did you, um, did you, did you come?
嘿嘿 有呀
Well, yes.
你呢 高潮了嗎
Were you there?
我反正高潮了
Yeah, I did.
- 高潮了6趟   - 挺好
- Like, six times.- Cool.
- 很贊哦  - 剛才這炮挺好
- Awesome. - It was great.
- 你呢  - 沒有誒
- Did you? - No, no, no.
但是沒事兒啊  我挺開心的
But it's okay. I-I had fun.
我感覺挺好
I had fun back there.
是嘛
Yeah.
你總是不高潮 我覺得很抱歉
You know, I feel bad that you never do.
哦不 我 我經常
No, I-I do all the time.
我只是不像你會演一整場音樂劇
I just... you know, I don't put on a Broadway show like you do.
我比較安靜
You know, I'm-I'm more quiet.
我的高潮跟卓別林比較像
I'm more like Charlie Chaplin when I come.
- 像無聲電影   - 無聲電影
- Like a silent movie.- Silent movie.
呃 你覺得是因為抗抑鬱的藥物的作用嗎
Um, do you think it's the antidepressants?
嗯 是吧 應該是
Oh, yeah, for sure.
是啊 如果不是吃了抗抑鬱的藥
Yeah. If I didn't have the antidepressants,
我8秒就射了
I'd come in, like, eight seconds.
然後你的高潮就沒有了
And then you wouldn't come.
然後你會抑鬱的
And then you'd be depressed.
然後你就得吃抗抑鬱的藥了
And then you would have to take antidepressants.
- 我不知道呢 我能發表下我的想法嗎 我...   - 你說
- I don't know, can I say something? I, um...- Yeah.
我就是不能理解為啥咱倆要這般偷雞摸狗呢
I just still don't understand why this is such a big secret.
你懂為什麼的呀 因為咱倆這是特殊關係呀
You know why it's a big secret.'Cause it's special.
這是我們之間的小秘密啊
It's-it's, like, our thing, you know?
如果大家都知道了我們的關係就不特殊了呢
It-it wouldn't be special if everybody knew about it.
話雖如此 但我不想我倆只是這樣的關係啊
Yeah, but I don't just want to do this.
懂 我理解 那我們以後就不搞了嗎
Yeah, I totally get that. So, should we stop?
我不是這個意思
No, I...
我不知道怎麼說 我們這算什麼呀
I don't know, like, this... like, what is this?
我不知道為啥  這關係
- And I don't know why... - This?
- 咱們這是  - 我想像正常人一樣
- This is... - I want to do what normal people do.
我懂 我只是 你知道的 我
Yeah, I know. I just, you know, I...
公開可能會很奇怪啊
It-it might be weird, you know.
我們都認識對方那麼久了
We've known each other for, like, ever.
從小學四年級開始吧
Since fourth grade.
公開的話感覺像亂倫一樣
It would be like incest.
不會啦
No, it wouldn't.
會啊 感覺就是我們一直是好朋友
No, it's like, yeah, w-we're best pals,
我不想因為這個傷到 我們的友誼
and I wouldn't want to, like,jeopardize our friendship
或者友誼就被其他什麼取代了
or something like that over something...
不是不對 就是這樣風險很大
not silly, but, you know, it's just... it's a big risk.
但是我們已經發生關係了呀
But we've already done the deed.
- 我說還有啥阻礙的  - 已經發生關係了
- I mean, what else is there? - "Done the deed"?
- 我不知道啦   - 但是 你知道 就是
-  I don't know.- But, you know, it's just,
- 你值得一個比我更好的人  - 什麼
- you deserve somebody way better than me. - What?
你已經很好了
You're a good guy.
- 你很好啊 我喜歡你  - 呃
- You're a good guy. I like you.- Uh...
好吧  你為什麼這麼說
Well, I... Based on what?
我也喜歡你啊 就是
I mean, I like you, too. It's just like...
好吧 我 跟你說 我可以跟你說個事兒嗎
All right, can I just tell you... can I tell you something?
但只有你知道不要告訴別人
But can you, like, not tell anybody?
可能別人也知道吧 但是 就是
Well, people probably know, but, like...
我可能有毛病
There's, like, something wrong with me.
- 精神上   - 啥
- Like, mentally, like... - What?
我這兒有問題
Like, I'm not okay up there.
就像
You know? Like...
我會變得癲狂 像瘋子一樣
I-I get all mad, acting, like, crazy,
然後我真的會神志不清 做一些衝動的事情
and I, and I make really insane,impulsive decisions.
然後我
And I get...
我自己都怕自己 但我不想
I'm d... I'm scared o-of myself, and I don't...
我不想嚇到你或和我自己
I don't want to, like, scare you or me
或者傷到其他人 你懂嗎
or, like, hurt anyone, you know?
所以我想最好
So, I think it would just be best
最負責任的選擇是離你遠點 你知道吧
and really responsible of me if I just backed off, you know?
我不希望你這麼想自己
I don't want you to f-feel like that about yourself.
不是我這麼想自己
Oh, no, it's...
我只是我不想冒犯到你 懂嗎
I just, I just don't want to offend you, you know?
你最好了 我覺得你是最好的
You're... you're the best. I think you're the greatest.
我知道你覺得我很好 覺得我很好
I know you think I'm great. I'm awesome.
我只是很抱歉你看低了你自己
I feel bad that you don't think you're great.
早啊 親愛的
Hey, honey.
我給你做了煎蛋卷
I made you an omelet.
你打算穿啥去你妹妹的畢業典禮啊
What are you gonna wear to your sister's graduation party?
我在想要不你穿你爹的西服吧
I was thinking, what about one of your dad's suits?
我不知道
I don't know.
我覺得我不太適合穿西服吧
I-I don't think I'm really a suit guy, you know?
再說那些西服都過時了 所以
Plus-plus, all those suits are out of style, so...
我聽說現在流行復古
You know, I thought they were back in style.
還有你去聚會前咱能不吸大麻嗎
And... can you not smoke pot before the party?
為毛
Why?
因為太臭了 到時你渾身都裹著臭味
Because it smells. You smell bad.
也別吸電子煙 不然人家會以為你吸了大麻
And no vaping because they're gonna think it's pot.
那個叔叔是個警察
The uncle is a cop.
我們別給自己找麻煩
We don't need that kind of trouble.
去他媽的
Fuck that guy.
我討厭這個家
I hate this family.
他們渾身銅臭又傲慢
They're so rich and snooty.
他們對Claire很好
They've been really nice to Claire.
嘿 老媽 可以給幾個塑料箱子麼
Hey, Mom. You got me the plastic containers.
我只需要幾個紙箱丟不要的東西
I just need the cardboard boxes I can throw away.
但是它們很適合用來收納東西
But they're so good for storing things.
是 但是我沒有收納的地方
Yeah, but I don't have any storage.
我衣櫥只有兩尺寬
My closet's, like, two feet wide.
嘿 Chaire 你要我去你畢業典禮嗎
Hey, Claire, do you even want me at your graduation party?
我想讓你去嗎 我都隨便
Do I want you to go? I don't care.
只是 你不去會顯得很奇怪
Just... It's weird if you don't go.
那聽上去不是個熱情的邀請啊
That wasn't exactly a warm invitation.
哈 好吧 你不是我最期待的部分
Yeah, well, it's not the part I'm looking forward to most.
但我還是想你在的
But I want you to be there.
- 她邀請你去了  - 不她不想
- She wants you to go. - No, she doesn't.
- 她剛說了呀   - 不 我不想他去
- She just said it.-  No, I don't want him to go.
他得去
He has to go.
就不要全程縮在沙發上的一個角落就行
Just don't sit on the couch in the corner the whole time.
- 太詭異了  - 我沒覺得
- It's weird. - No, I don't see the problem
坐在一個角落裡有啥問題啊
with sitting in the corner, okay?
聚會上有些人會去舞池裡跳舞
There's some people that go to the party and dance,
有些人就是會坐在角落看而已
and there's some people that sit in the corner.
我就是那個坐角落的人而已
I'm the corner guy.
接受你哥吧
Accept your brother.
還有別想著跟Layla上床
Also, don't try to fuck Layla, okay?
她都跟你說了她對你沒興趣
She told you she's not interested.
你說啥呢
What are you talking about?
我從來沒想過要跟她上床啊
I never tried to hook up with her.
是她自己一直想勾搭我 而我必須
She's always trying to fuck me,and I-I have to avoid it
不惜一切代價躲著她 因為你
at all costs, out of respect for you.
我只是覺得她穿那條褲子很好看而已
I just thought she looked really good in those pants.
- 我去  - 我以為那是個簡單的稱讚
- Jesus. - Thought that was a nice thing to say.
- 別說了  - 我不知道我會因此被捲進Me Too運動裡
- Just don't. - I didn't know I would get MeToo'd for it.
你爹的西服塑封著放在車庫裡
Dad's suits are vacuum-sealed in the garage.
- 哦   - 挑個好一點的穿吧
- Yeah? - Just pick yourself a nice one.
你得好好打扮下
You have to look nice.
我們是去慶祝你妹妹獲得的成就的
We're celebrating your sister's achievements.
等她不在了你會想她的
You're gonna miss her when she's gone.
是啊 為我慶祝吧
Yeah. Celebrate me.
哇 時間過得真快呀
Wow, this, uh... this all happened so fast.
真不敢相信你這麼就畢業了
I-I can't believe you're graduating already.
我會想你的
I'm gonna really miss you.
第二回合
Round two.
開打
Fight!
喲 你從哪兒搞到這個的啊
Yo, where'd you get this?
這玩意兒味道不是很好啊
This shit does not taste very good.
你說啥呢 這玩意兒很猛的 不識貨的傢伙
What are you talking about? This shit's fire, dawg.
你們現在還能磕到嗨嗎
Do you guys even really get high anymore?
我覺的現在嗑藥都沒啥意思了
I-I don't really think I get high anymore.
我抽完了就感覺跟我自己沒啥兩樣
I think I just kind of am myself.
兄弟我有陣子沒嗨過了
I haven't been high in a while, man.
但我還是會嗑的
But I still do it.
我就是喜歡這種生活方式
I like the lifestyle.
我現在超嗨
I'm mad high.
嘿 跟Scott 說說
Yo, tell Scotty about
你是怎麼被仙人跳的
how you're being catfished.
- 誰  - 你啊
- Who? - You!
兄弟 你怎麼被仙人跳的
How you're being catfished, bro.
快說來聽聽
Tell him the truth.
你交女朋友了還是怎麼了
You got a girlfriend? What's up?
- 沒    - 有
- No. -  Yeah.
- 太好了啊  - 是啊
- That's awesome. - Yes.
她叫Carla
Her name is Carla.
- 我們通了電話  - 不是的 兄弟
- We talk on the phone.  -  Nah, dude.
那女孩突然就私聊了他
Like, this girl, like, slid into his DMs, and, like,
不知道後面怎麼了就約他出去
I don't know, she, like, asked him out or whatever.
- 但是100% 是個陷阱 兄弟  - 她
- But hundred percent a trick, dude.-  She...
- 她是很野 但她不是你的   - 怎麼說
- She's wild, but that's not yours.   - Why?
她身材很火辣 兄弟
And she's, like, so hot, dude.
她就像遊艇女郎
Yo, she, like,hangs out on yachts.
- 就像  - 嘿 兄弟
- Like, yo.- Oh, come on.
沒啦 沒啦 不是   - 老兄
- No, no, like, no.- Dude...
超不可思議的
Like, it's not real, like...
兄弟 他們就是嫉妒
Bro, they're just being jealous, bro.
他們就是嫉妒 因為你釣到了
They're just jealous 'cause you're getting that...
哦 對 這就仙人跳
Oh, yeah, that's a catfish.
喔 你他媽真的就被詐騙了啊
Oh, you getting catfished like a motherfucker!
- 我去  - 我說的是吧 兄弟
- Oh, my God! -  Right, dude?
兄弟
Bruh
我要把這圖片發給我自己
Straight up, I'm-a send myself this one, honestly.
講真 兄弟 她也太假了吧
Honestly, dude, she's fucking fake.
她覺得我很性感
She thinks I'm hot.
怎麼會 你倆都沒見過面
How? You guys never even seen each other.
你倆怎麼沒視頻下
How come you guys don't FaceTime?
跟Scotty 說說你為啥沒跟人視頻
Tell Scotty why you don't FaceTime.
她手機攝像頭壞了 但是她給我發了這些照片
Her phone camera's broken, but she sent me all these photos.
- 是啊  - 兄弟 這些是谷歌出來的圖片好吧
-  Yeah.-  Bro, these are Google Images.
- 對啊 兄弟   - 我去 不一定啊
-  Exactly, dude. -  Shit, you don't know that.
可能人家妹子就愛 Igor 這款的呢
Maybe-maybe this girl is, uh, is into Igor.
他其實很 你知道 很可愛啊
Well, you know, he's-he's, you know, cute.
哈 你都不知道怎麼和妹子聊天
Yo, like, you don't even know how to talk to girls.
你怎麼和這個妹子聊天
What do you even talk to her about?
-Igor  - 哦哦
- Igor.-  Mm-hmm.
去開門啊兄弟  你愣著幹嘛
Go get that shit, bro. What are you doing?
他 真的是最爛的助手了
Yo, he is the worst assistant.
他看上去最近很多爛事纏身
He's clearly going through a lot.
6片贊安諾多少錢來的
How much for, like, six Xanax?
6個
Six.
我們有多少 我們有多少
What do we have? What do we have?
- 誰需要6片贊安諾啊 - 我這裡有1片 2片
- Who needs six Xanax? - I got one, two...
我這裡有 3個
I got three right here, I think.
1個 2個
One, two...
這個是麼  是的
Is this a... Yeah.
- 你最近過得怎麼樣了  - 我還好啊
- How you doing? - I'm all right.
嘿 你是Jimmy Bags的兄弟對嗎
Yo, you're Jimmy Bags' brother, right?
是的 兄弟
Yes, bro.
轉告你兄弟說他是個賤人
Tell your brother he's a bitch.
- 懂了嗎  - 好 懂了
- You understand that?- Yeah. I do.
- 跟我說一遍   - 他是個碧池 他是個碧池
- Say it back to me.- He's a bitch. He's a bitch.
現在
And now, you know what?
我只有4片 但是你要付我6片的錢
I got four,but you're paying for six.
不 別這樣 大哥 那他媽的是我哥
Nah, come on. That's my fucking brother, bro.
- 你想幹嘛  - 不不不 小兄弟
- Like, what are you... - Nah. Nah, dude.
我討厭你哥
I hate your brother.
你看著就像迷你版的他
And now you look like a little version of him,
我現在就想揍你
and I want to punch you in the face.
如果不想這樣你就給我60塊
So, instead of doing that, just give me 60.
我只有40塊
I only got 40.
那就滾回家 做點家務 然後別來了
Then go home, do chores, and dont come back.
- 我才不管  - 不行啊
- I don't give a fuck. - I-I can't.
這錢是從我媽錢包裡偷的 她錢包裡只有40塊啊
I stole it from my mom's purse, but she only had 40.
好吧 那這樣吧 你把你鞋給我
Well, then, give me your shoes.
大哥不行啊
No, bro, I can't.
給我你的鞋子 就這麼成交了
Just give me your shoes and we'll call it a day.
- 嘿你鞋多大碼的 - 鞋碼9
- Hey, what size are you? -  Like, a nine.
那適合你
Those'll fit you.
- Igor 那給你了  - 嗯 我要了
- Igor, you can have those. - IGOR: I'll take 'em.
快看 Igor 得到了個禮物
Look at that, Igor got a gift.
- 他不是9碼的  - 操你的
- He's not a fucking nine.- Fuck you!
別取笑我朋友
You don't make fun of my friend!
他連他媽的過山車都做不了
He-he can't get on fucking roller coasters,
- 矮成這樣  -你丫的閉嘴
- he's that small. - Shut the fuck up!
- 我們可以取笑他  - 他怎麼穿得上
- We make fun of him! - How is he gonna wear them?
- 但你不可以取笑他  - 他是我們的朋友
- You don't make fun of him! - He's our friend.
他一直都能坐過山車
He rides roller coasters all the time.
我們可以取笑他 你不能
We make fun of him, not you.
他也就穿5號吧 大哥
He's, like, a size five, bro, like...
嘿 閉嘴
Yo! Stop!
滾出我窗口
Get the fuck away from my window.
你們就是群小娘們兒
You guys are a bunch of fucking pussies.
老媽 他說他要穿這個工裝褲去參加我的典禮
Mom, he's saying he's gonna wear these cargo shorts to the party.
哦 別
Oh, no.
啥 我都跟你說了去穿你爹的西服啊
What? I told you to wear Dad's suit.
我不想穿老爸的西服好嗎
I don't want to wear Dad's old suit, okay?
- 我有自己的穿衣風格 我 - 滾離我遠一點
- I have my own personal style, and I... - Get the fuck off me!
- 別這樣  - 我不想穿西裝好嗎
- Don't do that! - I-I don't want to wear a suit, okay?
我感覺我要吐了
I think, I think I'm gonna throw up.
我感覺我得了流感
I think I have the flu.
哦哦 好吧 用你的鼻子呼吸
Oh, oh, okay. Just-just breathe through your nose.
等下啊
One second.
閉嘴 老媽 他看起來
Oh, shut up. Mom, he looks like
就像天橋底下賣可卡因的毒販子
he fucking sells crack under a bridge.
我認識天橋下賣可卡因的販子好嗎
I know the guy who sells crack under the bridge, okay?
他看起來可精神了
And he looks awesome.
你就穿西裝吧 拜託了 Scott
Just put on the suit, Scott, please.
不 這不公平
No! It's not fair!
她覺得自己是整個世界的公主
She thinks she's, like, princess of the world...
好了 就麻煩
Okay, well, then just please
稍稍尊重我下好嗎
be respectful for two fucking seconds!
因為她高中畢業了
...because she graduated high school.
誰沒高中畢業啊
Everybody graduates high school!
- 閉嘴  - Scott
- Shut up! - Scott!
媽 求你了
Mom, please...
你把西裝穿上
Just put on the suit.
有點禮貌
Be respectful.
我一小時後回家
I'll be home in an hour.
我穿 行了吧
Fine!
謝謝
Thank you.
你感覺怎麼樣
How are you feeling?
對不起
I'm sorry.
剛才想提醒您來著 可您忙著視頻呢
I tried to warn you, but you were on the phone.
謝謝你讓我用你的手機
Thanks for letting me use your phone.
我家也有問題
My family has problems, too.
我喜歡這房子
I love this house.
你要是有這個錢的話
If you have money,
幹嘛還要住在史泰登島呢
why would you ever live in Staten Island?
- 哦 耶  - 太棒了
- Oh, God. Yeah.  - So good.
我們為我們的女兒Joanne
We are so proud
感到非常驕傲
of our daughter Joanne...
還有Claire 這些年常常在我們家
and Claire, who's been at our house so much over the years
你就像我們的第二個女兒
you feel like our second daughter.
Margie 謝謝你這些年讓女兒陪伴我們
Thank you, Margie, for lending her to us all these years.
你們是非常努力的人 我們也非常為你們驕傲
You guys have worked so hard, and we are so, so proud of you.
老天 您別裝了 智障嗎
Jesus Christ, dial it back, you fucking fruits.
Joanne
Joanne,
你是我們最重要的女兒
you are a very special girl.
你也讓我們夢想成真
You made our dreams come true, too.
你是我們可愛的天使
You're my sweet angel.
她可不是
No, she's not.
能成為你的父母是我們的榮幸
It's such an honor to be your parents.
你教給我們的和我們教給你的東西一樣多 還有Claire
You've taught us as much as we've taught you. Claire...
你經歷了太多
You've been through so much,
但卻非常爭氣
and you've done so well,
換做我們也不可能做得這麼好
so much better than any of us could have handled it.
你父親Stan一定也為你驕傲
Your dad Stan would be so proud of you.
他此刻就在天堂看著你
He's looking down at you right now.
是的
Yes, he is.
他可沒有
No, he's not.
敬Joanne和Claire
A toast to Joanne and Claire.
太驕傲了
So proud.
祝賀你們
Congratulations!
- 你好啊 Todd  - 你好 Scott
- What's up, Todd?  - What's up, Scott?
你什麼時候也要上大學吧
You going to college, too, someday?
是啊 我是想去 我想學法律
I'd like to, yeah. I'd go study law.
是嗎 那挺不錯的
Oh, yeah? That's awesome, man.
聽著真不錯 你有大麻嗎
That sounds really cool. Do you have any weed?
- 有啊  - 我能來點兒嗎
- I do.  - Could I have some?
- 當然 我去拿點兒  - 好啊 謝啦 Todd
- Definitely. I'll go grab it.  - Cool. Thanks, Todd.
小伙子還他媽不錯 托德
Fucking home run, Todd.
一想起我妹妹
It makes me sad to think of my little sister
獨自坐在那可憐的家裡
sitting in that sad little house,
等著兒子成才 我就傷心
waiting for her son to be perfect.
我沒有
I'm not.
那你可白瞎了這副好身材
Then you're wasting all of this.
活活浪費了
All of it's getting wasted.
- 你真糟糕  - 你喝醉了
- You're a mess.  - You're wasted.
媽媽可要...她可要對你失望了
Mom would be so disappoin... Mom would be disappointed in you.
你才是那個經常喝醉的人
You're the one who's always wasted.
你浪費了 就像剩飯一樣
You're wasting. It's like leaving food on the table.
得了吧
Come on.
- 我帶你出去玩  - 與人交往太難了
- Let me take you out.  - It's so hard to meet people.
- 我很大方開放了  - 不 我是說 唉
- I'm totally open.  - No, it's... I mean, God...
你一點也沒有敞開心扉
You're not open at all.
- 與人交往就是很難  - 你撒謊
- It's really hard to meet people.  - You're a liar.
自欺欺人 什麼叫與人交往很難
You're not open. "Hard to meet people"?
- 我在急診室工作 我看到的都是  - 你一晚上
- I'm in the E.R. All I see is, like...  - You meet...
- 你一晚上能見到上百人  - 中槍的人
- You meet a hundred people a night.  - People who were shot...
就是說啊 都中槍了
Yeah, they're shot.
他們 他們 呃 他們是罪犯
They're-they're, uh, they're criminals.
- 別總是自我束縛了  - 我見誰啊我
- Stop limiting yourself.  - Who am I gonna meet?
別自我束縛好嗎
Stop limiting yourself.
- 但我在醫院上班  - 是啊
- But I'm at the hospital.  - Yeah.
- 他們也不全是罪犯啊  - 你工作能遇見很多人
- They're not all criminals.  - You meet people at work.
- 這就是為什麼  - 有些也是受害者呢
- That's what it's...  - Some of them are victims.
親愛的
Doll...
我們可以給你一周安排兩班
You know, we could put you on two shifts a week,
- 就 就只是試一試  - 我不需要工作
- just-just, just to try it.  - I don't need a job.
我跟文身店簽了合同了
I, uh, I got a contact at a tattoo shop.
我 我準備去做學徒
I'm-I'm hoping for an apprenticeship, so...
那你肯定需要錢吧
Then you're gonna need some money.
可不 有些人走的時候還給80塊小費呢
Yeah, some of these guys walk away with 80 bucks in tips.
Scott你堂兄在給你安排工作 你就考慮一下吧 好嗎
Scott, your cousin's offering you a job. Consider it, okay?
要是你幹的好 你還能當個侍應生
If you're good at it, you can become a waiter.
說起來你為什麼要給我安排工作
Why are you offering me a job anyway?
因為我跟你父親保證我會照顧你
Because I told your father I'd always look out for you.
怎麼可能 他死於一場突發火災
How? He died suddenly in a fire.
你問的是他的魂兒嗎
Uh, did you ask his ghost?
別耍這種小聰明 Scott
That's not witty, Scott.
我覺得你那黑色幽默一點也不好笑
Your dark sense of humor doesn't work for me.
我覺著好笑
I find it funny.
今天是你妹妹重要的日子 有點禮貌
It's your sister's big day. Be a gentleman.
好吧 移民局突擊檢查拘了我們幾個人
Okay, we lost a few guys in an ICE raid.
操蛋 抱歉
Ah, shit. Sorry.
也許你可以半工半讀
Maybe you should work and go to college.
- 讀大學可太扯淡了  - 哦
- College is bullshit!  - Oh.
你知道誰讀的哈佛大學嗎 炸彈怪客
You know who went to Harvard? The Unabomber.
你知道誰讀的天普大學嗎 比爾 克斯比
You know who went to Temple? Bill Cosby.
著名美國笑匠 因性侵入獄
你知道還有誰讀的天普大學嗎 泰德·邦迪
You know who else who went to Temple? Ted Bundy.
70年代連環殺手
你知道還有誰讀的霍夫斯特拉大學嗎 伯尼·麥道夫
You know who went to Hofstra? Bernie Madoff.
造市商 因龐氏騙局入獄
你知道誰讀的沃頓商學院嗎 唐納德·特朗普
You know who went to Wharton? Donald Trump.
大學就是個騙局
It's all a scam.
好吧 那我也不該上大學
Okay, well, maybe I shouldn't go, then.
哦不 你會度過人生中最好的時光的
Oh, no, you'll have the time of your life.
嗨 Scott
Hey, Scott.
坐吧
Sit down.
好
Okay.
我給你買了這個
I got you this.
這 這啥啊 這 這什麼意思
So, what-what is, uh, what is, what is this?
就是畫筆和一些顏料
It's paintbrushes and some paint.
我知道你喜歡美術 所以我就想著 在我不在的時候
Well, I know you're into art, so I thought you could
你可以用這些來開闊視野
expand your horizons while I'm gone.
你還專門要了禮物收據嗎
You got a gift receipt for this?
- 你沒事吧  - 沒事 嗯
- You okay?  - Fine... Yeah.
怎麼了 沒事啊
Wh-What do you mean? Yeah, I'm...
我不在家你沒事的吧
You gonna be okay without me here?
什麼意思 你覺得你走了我就活不了了嗎
What, you don't think I can survive here without you?
好吧 那你別老干混蛋事兒啊
Okay, just don't be a dick, okay?
對媽媽好點兒 聽到沒 別老氣她
Like, be nice to Mom, okay? Don't give her a hard time.
- 讓她歇會兒吧  - 我怎麼沒讓她歇著了
- She deserves a break.  - I always give her a-a break.
你什麼意思 我 誰能讓我歇會兒
What are you... When's... When am I gonna get my break?
就
Like...
你說什麼呢
What are you talking about?
每個人就知道關心你
All anyone ever does is worry about you.
我的童年沒人理就是因為你
I was ignored my entire childhood 'cause of you.
哦 是嗎 我還真不記得我的童年多美好了
Oh, yeah, I forgot that my childhood was so dandy.
你不能就因為爸爸去世
Okay, you don't get to act crazy your whole life
就瘋瘋癲癲一輩子 好嗎
just 'cause Dad died, okay?
至少你還見過他
At least you got to know him.
告訴你 你沒見過他才是幸運的
Well, you're lucky you didn't get to know him, okay?
因為這個你好歹像個正常人
'Cause that's why you're almost normal.
如果你見過他 你就會知道
If you got to know him, you would've known that he was,
他他媽是最酷的人
like, the fucking coolest guy ever,
然後你這輩子就不會再好了
and that would've ruined the rest of your life.
但你還能怎樣呢
Okay, like, but what are you gonna do?
你準備去找工作還是離開家
Are you gonna get a job or are you gonna leave the house?
不知道
I don't know.
我 我想開那家紋身餐廳
I-I'm gonna open that tattoo restaurant.
不 是說認真的
No, like, for real.
我就是認真的啊
I am being real.
會很棒 前所未有的概念
It's a great...It's never been done before.
我查過 谷歌的
I looked it up. I googled it.
前所未有的概念 都不曾在梗裡出現過
It's never been done, not even as a joke.
那是因為沒人想去餐廳吃飯的同時
Because no one wants to go to a restaurant
還得看著別人紋身
and watch people get tattooed while they eat.
- 太噁心了  - 這個主意最棒了
- It's gross.  - It's the best idea ever.
紅寶石紋身日 歡迎所有人光臨
Ruby Tattoosdays, where everyone's welcome.
- 炸雞與紋身  - 根本沒有這行兒
- Chicken and tattoos.  - That's not a business!
知道嗎 你必須振作起來
You know, you got to get your shit together.
時光飛逝
Time is passing by very quickly.
這就是為什麼我一天到晚抽大麻 好吧
That's why I smoke weed all the time, okay?
它會讓時間慢下來
It slows it all down.
去你媽的
Fucking God.
我這是在擔心你
See, I'm worried about you.
現在擔心什麼 你不是從來不關心的嗎
Well, why now? You never gave a shit.
你 這一秒之前 一直也沒鳥過我
You, like, literally never cared until this second.
有什麼動機嗎
Like, wh-what, what gives?
你從沒有罩過我一次
You never looked out for me once.
你是我哥哥
You're my older brother.
難道不是應該你罩著我嗎
You're supposed to look out for me.
你 你只是因為要走了所以心中有愧吧
You're-you're just guilty 'cause you're leaving?
現在突然間 你就一下子開始擔心我要死了
Now, all of a sudden, you're afraid I'm gonna die?
我終究會死 你走不走都一樣
I was gonna die anyway, whether you stay or not.
- 你要自殘嗎  - 說不定呢
- Are you gonna hurt yourself?  - Probably.
是啊 我有可能會自殘
Yeah, I'm probably gonna hurt myself.
還沒想好怎麼做 但會的
I don't know how, but yeah.
我就是最有可能這麼做的人了
If anybody could do it, it's me.
這就是為什麼我不想理你 因為我知道
This is why I don't talk to you, 'cause the one thing I know is
你不會聽我的 所以
you're not gonna listen to my advice, so...
是啊 我為什麼要聽
Yeah, well, why would I?
你根本就不在乎
Like, you don't even give a shit.
你 你還要走呢
You're-you're leaving.
你都不屬於這個家了
You're not even part of the family.
我他媽才是這個家裡唯一的正常人
I'm the only fucking normal person in this family.
天哪 你知道嗎
Jesus. You know...
我不在你身邊的每一秒我都在擔心你
Every second I'm away from you, I'm worrying about you.
你就是這樣讓人擔心
That's what you do to people.
你就該擔心
You should be worried.
好了 別破壞我對大學的嚮往了
Okay, don't fucking ruin college for me, okay?
滾
Go!
好啊
Fine.
嘿 你真該把這討喜的性格帶到大學裡去
Hey, you should bring that chipper personality to college.
男生都喜歡
Guys will love it.
你好
Hello.
好的 我先看看我的日程安排
Okay, let's see my to-do list.
我們已經把行李裝到車上了
Yo, we're finished packing the car.
你想出來告別一下嗎 還是
You want to come out and say goodbye or...?
哦 當然 馬上就看完了
Oh, well, yeah, this is almost over.
我們馬上就走了
No, like, we're leaving.
- 哦 她要走了嗎  - 要去大學啊 記得嗎
- Oh. She's leaving?  - Like, to go to college, you know?
- 哦哦 抱歉  - 是啊 四年呢
- Oh, oh, my bad.  - Yeah, four years, so...
- 好吧  - 走吧
- Oh, all right. - Let's go.
別看了 趕緊走
Nope, like... Go. Come on.
別為我擔心 好嗎
Uh, don't worry about me, okay?
要到傷感的時刻了
This is really hard right now.
你看起來不太好
You don't seem fine.
我真為你驕傲
I'm so proud of you.
我愛你
I love you.
好了
Uh, okay.
你是我生命中的光
You're the light of my life.
哦
Oh.
好啦
Okay.
幫忙裝行李可真是謝謝你
Thanks for helping us pack the car.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道你們已經裝好了
I didn't realize you guys were done already.
對媽媽好點兒
Be nice to Mom.
還有一定要回我短信
And please respond to my texts.
我會的 不用擔心
I will. Don't worry about it.
我 呃 回頭我會去找你的
And, um... I-I'll come visit you at some point.
好啊
Okay. All right.
嗯
Yeah.
- 我愛你  - 我也愛你
- I love you.  - I love you, too.
- 展翅高飛吧孩子
- Fly.
嘿
Hey.
呃
Uh...
我想著我還是要看看那個權力的遊戲
I was thinking of finally seeing that Game of Thrones.
我是不是應該一次性全看完
Should I binge it?
哦 那個劇 挺 挺暴力的
Oh, it's a, it's a pretty violent show.
你確定要看嗎
You sure you could watch that?
我在急診工作
I work in an emergency room.
哦對
Right, yeah.
那你看燒殺搶掠啥的應該沒問題
So, you could probably handle a good pillage.
是啊
Yeah.
好 那我就準備看了
Okay, well, maybe I'll start watching it.
- 好的  - 你跟我一起嗎
- Yeah.  - You watch it with me?
呃 其實我 差不多看完了 所以
Um, well, I actually just kind of finished it, so I-I don't...
劇情還在我腦中盤旋 所以我可能
It's really fresh in my mind, so I-I would probably...
- 好吧  - 我可以看一部分
- Okay.  - I can watch some of them.
我覺得我可能不能全看一遍了 但
Uh, I don't think I can watch all of them again, but...
- 嗯  - 那就晚點見了
- Well...  - I'll see you later, then.
好吧
All right.
你還好嗎
Uh, are you okay?
還是
Or...
怎麼了
Oh. Yeah?
過來
Come on.
沒 沒
Uh, it's, it-it's...
沒事的
It's okay. It's...
我 我在這兒 我在
I-I'm here. Uh, I'm here.
別 別難過了
Don't-don't worry about it.
你知道 她
She's, you know...
她離咱們只有45分鐘車程的
Well, she's only, like, 45 minutes away,
她肯定 過個五分鐘就會打來電話的
and she'll-she'll probably call in, like, five minutes.
但是
But, hey.
你不是還有我呢嗎 對吧
You still got me, right?
是呀
Yeah.
哦 草
Oh, shit.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
看 你應該這樣拿
See, you got to hold it like this.
我看看 噢
Let's see. Oh.
- 哦耶  - 哦
- Oh, yeah!  - Oh!
嘿 嘿 等下 兄弟們
Hey, hey, wait. Hey, hey, guys.
是這樣
Look, look.
你們不能在這兒呆著
You can't be here, man.
- 你們得離開  - 為什麼
- Y-You got to go.  - Why?
這是私人土地 這就是為什麼
It's private property, that's why.
這是個廢棄的孤兒院 我們怎麼不能呆了
It's an abandoned orphanage. Why can't we be here?
誰鳥你啊 兄弟
Who gives a shit, man?
你在這兒幹嘛
What are you doing here?
你在守著孤兒們的鬼魂兒嗎
You fucking protecting the ghosts of dead orphans?
聽著 胖Kanye 閉上你的臭嘴
Look, fat Kanye, shut your damn mouth.
我五分鐘後再他媽過來
I'll be back in five minutes for you assholes.
如果你們還在這兒 我就報警 沒商量
If you're still here, I'm calling the cops, period.
你最好報警 哥們兒 因為你是個假警察
You better get the cops, man, 'cause you're a fake cop.
- 你需要真警察  - 小王八羔子
- You need the real ones.  -  Motherfuckers.
- 操你們娘的  - 我有點後悔
- Fuck all of y'all.  - IGOR: I feel bad.
我們 是 是不是太過分了
We-we were a little too mean.
- 是啊  - 他人挺好的
- Yeah.  - He's nice.
是啊 他是個好人
Yeah, he's a really good guy.
那種人 他才是史泰登島真正的問題
See, that guy... that is what is wrong with Staten Island.
別的鎮上的人都不來我們這兒
We don't get any cool people from any of the other boroughs.
沒人來
No one comes here.
我們只能跟這兒的土著混蛋們過一輩子了
We're stuck with the fucking pricks that live here.
你在罵我們
You're talking about us.
還當著我們的面
Right in front of us.
是啊 算是吧
Yeah, kinda.
我是想說 沒人願意來
I mean, no one comes here.
沒有任何人員流動 那傢伙 都有兩百歲了吧
There's no flow of people. That guy's, like, 200.
咱們6歲的時候就認識他了
We've known him since we were six.
為什麼咱們這兒不能像布魯克林一樣酷
Why can't we be cool like Brooklyn?
沒有道理我們不能像布魯克林一樣酷啊
There's no reason we shouldn't be cool like Brooklyn.
我們這兒景色美 離曼哈頓又近
We got amazing views. It's close to the city.
物價便宜 居民和藹 真是沒道理
It's cheap. Nice people. It makes no sense.
我們算是新澤西唯一可以瞧不起的地方了
We're, like, the only place that New Jersey looks down on.
這裡的垃圾場你從太空都能看見
You could see the garbage dump from space.
這地方也就這樣了
This place is never gonna change.
不是的 肉類加工廠區不就改變了
No, it happened to the Meatpacking District,
還有那個村兒
the Village.
布魯克林原來也是個操蛋的地方
Brooklyn used to be a fucking shithole.
咱們就是下一個了
We are next.
我要參加公務員考試
I'm gonna take my civil service test.
我要在城裡工作 在城市規劃部門
I'm gonna work in the city, in city planning.
你們看著吧 這地方即將成為下一個威廉斯堡
You watch, this place is gonna be like fucking Williamsburg
布魯克林的一片街區
- 十年內建成  - 別 別介 我們可不想要
- in ten years.  - No, all right? No. Nobody wants that.
為什麼你想在市裡干城市規劃的工作
Why do you want to work in the city and do city planning?
聽著就無聊
That sounds so boring.
我覺得布魯克林更好
I feel like Brooklyn is better.
我曾經跟一個住布魯克林的人約過會
I dated a guy that lived in Brooklyn.
他是個調酒師
He was a mixologist.
他用牛奶做冰塊
He made ice cubes out of milk.
- 他真是太有品味了  - 閉嘴
- He was so classy.  - Shut up!
我愛史泰登島
I love Staten Island.
這裡好的沒話說
It's amazing.
很快人們就將看到這一點 相信我
And people are gonna see it soon, trust me.
你要是這麼愛這裡
Well, if you love it so much,
幹嘛不讓我把它紋在你身上
why don't you let me tattoo it on you?
不 我可不會再讓你給我紋身了
No, I'm not gonna let you tattoo me again.
好吧
Fine.
那我也需要一個可以紋的人
Well, I need somebody to tattoo.
我 我已經沒有
I'm, I-I'm running out of...
Rich 你呢 兄弟
Come on, Rich. What about you, man?
- 看都別看我 哥們  - 為啥
- Don't even look at me, dude.  - Why?
你紋的東西太醜了
Your work is mad inconsistent.
奧巴馬不長這樣
Obama ain't right.
我只是把眼睛文錯了 好吧
I got the eyes wrong, okay?
哪兒哪兒都不對
He's not right.
好嘛 這個紋身傷到我了
All right, man, this has hurt me, all right?
我再也沒有黑人朋友了
I don't have any black friends anymore.
我再也不能去理髮店了
I can't go to a barber shop no more.
你把奧巴馬紋錯了 沒有比這嚴重的問題了
You got Obama wrong. Ain't nothing worse than that.
你呢 Igor 你要紋條龍還是啥嗎
What about you, Igor? You want a dragon or something?
哦 我可真喜歡你的紋身
Oh, I love your tattoos.
我弟弟
My brother?
太像了
It's a spitting image.
- 是啊 是我的代表作之一  - 是我的最愛
- Yeah. It's one of the best. - It's my favorite.
不不不 這是我的最愛
No, no, no, no. This is my favorite.
哦 這個真的精彩
Oh, you killed that.
- 可不 眼睛上很下功夫了  - 只是
- Yeah, I really worked hard on the eyes.  - Just...
真是可愛 我喜歡那個菊花
He's so cute. I love his butthole.
它時刻提醒我我有個肚臍眼
It reminds me that I have a belly button.
- 我還是算了  - 那什麼 我得走了
- So, I'm good.  - Yeah, I got to go.
看你上趕著送紋身真是悲哀
Watching you beg to give tattoos is too sad.
那玩意兒瘆死我了
And that's freaking me out.
快完事兒了
We're almost done.
馬上
Almost.
好了
All right.
- 大功告成  - 看起來很不錯啊
- You're all done.  - That looks really good.
是啊 我是說
Yeah, I mean, I wish
我希望你能讓我紋點兒更酷的 但也可以了
you'd let me do something cooler, but yeah.
臥槽 好疼 太疼了吧
Oh, fuck no. That hurts so bad.
- 又一個傻帽紋身  - 是啊 但 但我喜歡那種疼痛感
- Another dumb tattoo.  - Yeah, but I-I like the pain.
疼痛才是紋身的真諦
The-the pain is the whole point of getting tattoos.
難道你不喜歡那種 紋身的時候
Don't you just love when you're getting tattooed,
深入骨髓的痛 讓你的神經顫動
and it hits the bone and pinches a nerve,
那就像
and you're like...
我對疼痛不感興趣
I'm not a fan of the pain.
你不應該讓他紋你的 好吧
You shouldn't let him do it to you, all right?
他發揮不穩定
He's inconsistent.
我覺得那個紋身很傻
I think that tattoo's dumb.
那你們看見圖案的時候就該告訴我
Y'all should've told me when you saw the design.
上面說:取關我
It says, "Unfollow me."
本來你粉絲也不多啊
You don't even have that many followers.
Carla關注我了
Carla follows me.
- 兄弟 她不是真人  - 卡拉不是真人
- Bro, she's imaginary.  - Carla not real.
Carla不是真人 哥們兒
Carla's not real, dude.
要我們說多少遍啊
How many times do we have to say this?
她不是真人
She's not real.
我討厭這蟲子
I hate bugs, dawg.
我是土匪
I'm a gangster!
別 那是只蜜蜂 老兄
No, that's a bee, bro!
那邊有個孩子
There's a kid down there.
- 喲 小孩兒  - 喲
- Yo, kid! - Oh, yo.
- 喲 小孩兒 你好啊  - 哦草 那兒有個孩子
- Yo, kid, what's up?  - Oh, shit, there is a kid.
你在幹什麼
What are you doing?
你在海灘溜躂嗎 過來 上這兒來
You hanging out on the beach? Come here, come here.
別害羞 我們不會害你
Don't-don't be shy. No stranger danger here.
我不碰你
I'm not gonna touch you.
- 你好嗎 小老弟  - 你在幹什麼
- What's up, pal?  - What are you doing?
我在找我朋友
I'm looking for my friend.
"Looking for my friend."
你想跟我們當朋友嗎
You want to be friends with us?
我們是好人 對吧
We're the good guys, right?
- 你可以跟我們一起玩兒 小老弟  - 來吧
- You can hang out with us, pal.  - Come on.
來跟我碰拳 把你的拳頭放在這兒
Let me get some of that. Put it right there.
你入伙了
You gang.
是我們的人
Part of the gang.
我們的人
Gang.
那是什麼
What's that?
這是紋身槍
Uh, it's a tattoo gun.
我在給哥們紋身
I was giving the homeys tattoos.
我也想紋身
I want a tattoo.
- 小老弟挺狠的啊   - 真的嗎
- You're a tough guy? - Really?
- 行啊小伙子 你確定要紋身嗎   - 我確定
- Sure, young guy. You want a tattoo? - Yeah.
哥們 這孩子想要紋身 小老弟行啊
Dude, kid wants a tattoo. That's my guy right there.
老哥 你不能給他紋身
Bro, you-you can't give him a tattoo.
- 他還是個孩子   - 來吧來吧
- He's a little kid. - Yeah, there we go.
- 想紋身嗎   - 我總得找個人練練手
- You want a tattoo? - Bro, I got to practice on something.
- 沒錯   - 他看上去不小了
- Yeah. - He seems old enough.
- 是真漢子嗎   - 當然
- You a tough guy? - Yeah.
你是純爺們
You a badass.
來 老弟 給咱們秀一下肌肉
Come on, show those muscles, kid.
- 兩隻手 兩隻手   - 好樣的
- Come on. Both arms, both arms. - Yeah, there you go.
- 舉起來   - 肌肉猛男秀僅對內部開放
- Put 'em up. - You got tickets to the gun show?
- 秀出來秀出來   - 就是這樣   - 好樣的
- There it is. There it is - All right. - There we go.
- 你叫什麼名字   - Harold
- What's your name? - Harold.
那我叫你Harry
I'm-a call you Harry.
不行 叫我Harold
Don't. It's Harold.
好吧
Okay.
- 好小子   - 我喜歡他
- Hell yeah. - I like this kid.
我的生命裡就缺一個他
I need him in my life.
是個人才
He has structure.
兄弟們 我不覺得這是個好主意
Guys, I don't think that's a good idea.
拜託 我們也不聽你的
I mean... we don't listen to anything you say.
- 沒錯   - 是啊 你說你到底為什麼老提意見呢
- Yeah. - Yeah, I mean, why do you even try to give us advice?
那麼 你想要什麼樣的紋身
So, what do you want a tattoo of?
懲罰者
The Punisher.
- 懲罰者   - 行吧
- The Punisher? - Okay.
- 狠角色啊 哥們   - 好吧
- That's tough, man. - All right.
他可以選任何圖案 但他選了懲罰者
He could've said anything. He said The Punisher.
沒問題 我可以的 是這個嗎
Oh, yeah, I could do that. Is that it?
沒錯 是他
Yeah, that's him.
- 你確定嗎   - 確定
- Are you sure? - Yes.
能否請你給我你的法定許可
Do I have your legal permission to do this?
- 允許   - 對我來說就夠了
- Yes. - That's good enough for me.
- 你們覺得呢   - 可以成為呈堂證供
- How about you guys? - Holds up in court.
你們都聽到了 好勒
You guys heard it. All right.
唷 他不能給你許可 他才十歲
Yo, he can't get consent. He's ten.
那麼 別亂動好嗎 這紋上了可就洗不掉了
Now, hold still, okay? 'Cause it is permanent.
夥計們 停下 快停下
Yo, guys. Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
- 表情嚴肅一點   - 別擔心 哥們
- Put your game face on. - Don't worry, dude.
這玩意也不過就是會跟你一輩子
This will just be on you for the rest of your life.
開始了
There you go.
- 看看這個堅強的小伙   - 好樣的
- Look at you, tough guy. - There you go.
我不想紋了
I don't want to do it!
- 我不紋了   - 可是我得把這紋完了
- I don't wanna! - Well, I got to finish it.
- 現在只有一條線   - 冷靜點 哥們
- Now there's just a line. - Calm down, man.
- 這會讓你看上去很傻 坐回來 放輕鬆   - 冷靜點
- You're gonna look stupid. Sit back down. Relax. - Calm down.
- 坐下 繼續   - 放鬆
- Sit down. Do it. - Relax.
快跑 快跑孩子
Run! Run, kid!
跑快點 小屁孩 快跑
Run, little man! Run!
跑
Run!
該死
Goddamn it.
我他媽的還信了他了
I fucking believed in that kid, man.
剛開始看著挺堅強 下一秒就慫了
He seemed so tough at first, uh, but then immediately wasn't.
所以我才不跟千禧一代玩啊 哥們
That's why I don't fuck with millennials, dude.
我再說一遍 我們也是千禧一代
Again, we are the millennials.
他老這麼說 但我都不知道他在說什麼
He keeps saying that, but I don't know what that means.
我後悔跟你們交朋友了
I regret my friendship with you guys.
你好 我叫Raymond Bishop
Yeah, hello. My name's Raymond Bishop.
這個是我兒子 Harold 跟人家問好 Harold
This is my son, Harold. Say hello, Harold.
對不起
I'm sorry.
這是怎麼了
What's going on?
是這樣 你兒子好像在樹林那邊
Well, it seems your son was down in the woods
給別人免費紋身 而我兒子上了他的當
giving out free tattoos, and my son was one of his victims.
什麼 我 我不太明白
What? Well, I-I don't understand.
你怎麼知道是我兒子 你怎麼找到這裡的
How do you know it was my son? How'd you get this address?
我有我的辦法 相信我 我有門路
I have my ways. Believe me, I have my ways.
你是警察嗎
Are you a cop?
不 我是個消防員 行了嗎 我玩命工作
No, I'm a fireman, okay? I work for a living.
看看這個 你能相信嗎
Look at this. Do you believe this?
看這裡 你看到這條線了嗎
You see that there? See that line?
我不知道這是得燒掉還是怎麼樣
I don't know if you burn these off or what,
但這個必須得給我弄掉
but we're taking care of this
而且你得承擔所有費用 你明白嗎
and you're paying for it, you understand me?
- 我都不知道這是什麼   - Scott 哦
- I don't know what this is. - Scott! Oh.
我 我真的很抱歉
I am... I'm so sorry.
我 我
I-I-I...
我工作的醫院有一台激光美容儀
There's an aesthetic laser at the hospital where I work,
可以把這個去乾淨了
and it can completely remove it.
呃 我能給你打折
Uh, I get a discount.
我 這錢我來付
I'm-I'm gonna pay for the whole thing.
我有點語無倫次了 我感到抱歉
I don't know what I'm saying. I'm... I feel terrible.
你應該抱歉
You should feel terrible!
看看這個
Look at that!
- 怎麼了 哦媽的   - 啊 終於來了
- What's up? Oh, fuck. - Ah, there he is.
- 你給我滾過來   - 嘿 他跟我說他18歲了
- You get your ass out here! - Hey, he said he was 18.
他看上去像4歲 你個傻逼 不好意思
He looks like he's four, you fucking moron! Sorry.
- 他同意了   - 他騙人
- He consented! - He's lying.
- Harold 拜託   -他當然是在騙人
- Harold, come on! - Course he's lying!
你同意沒有法律效力 他才9歲
You can't have consent! He's nine years old!
爸爸 咱們走吧 你這樣我很尷尬
Dad, let's go. You're embarrassing me.
我們不走 好嗎
We're not going anywhere, okay?
他還是個小孩
He's just a little kid!
你他媽的是哪根筋搭錯了
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
呃 他在林子裡亂竄
Uh, he was roaming around in the woods.
說想要個紋身 當時你在哪呢
He wanted a tattoo. W-Where were you?
我他媽的在工作
I was at fucking work!
- 去你的吧   - 你給我出來
- Fuck you! - Come out here!
我要是你 我現在就乖乖閉嘴
If I was you, I'd shut your fucking mouth,
要不然我現在就報警
because I can call the cops right now
你馬上就得進局子
and have your ass thrown in jail.
- 我犯了什麼法   - 你給孩子捅針眼了
- For what? - For sticking needles in a kid's arm,
你個癮君子
you fucking dope!
他是你帶大的嗎 你教他什麼了到底
Did you even raise him? Did you even raise him?
是這樣 沒必要報警
You know, there's no reason to call the cops.
這事我能處理 他我也能處理
I can handle this and I can also handle disciplining him.
切 明顯你處理不了 要不然你兒子也不會年過中年
Well, clearly you can't or you wouldn't have a middle-aged son
還住在你家 到處給未成年人瞎紋身
still living at home, tattooing minors against their will!
是我讓他紋的
I asked him to do it.
- 不是他的錯   - 聽見了嗎 這才是個漢子
- It's not his fault. - That's right. That's my man.
去 車裡待著 Harold 去
Go wait in the car. Harold, go on.
以後不許對我這麼大聲
And don't raise your voice at me, either.
回見了 Harold
Later, Harold.
誰要跟你再見 別忘了看路
Don't say goodbye to my kid. Look both ways.
- 兩邊都要看   - 回你房間
- Look both ways! - Go to your room.
- 我看了   - 怎麼說話呢
- I am! - Watch your mouth.
順便告訴你 我沒有人到中年
For your information, I am not a middle-aged man.
我才24歲 現在我要回房間了
I'm a 24-year-old man, and I'm going to my room
因為我他媽的想回去了
'cause I fucking want to.
你在這房子帶大的這玩意是人嗎 哈
What kind of fucking animal are you raising in this house, huh?
發票我肯定會拿來
I'm bringing you the bill.
我才不管花了多少錢
I don't care what it costs, all right?
- 這他媽的算什麼事啊   - 好的
- I mean, what the fuck is going on around here? - All right.
給我一天的時間 我給你預約激光
Just give me a day to arrange the laser.
行 另外
All right. You know, you know something?
他爸爸在嗎 他爸在哪裡
I-Is his father home? Where's his dad?
我 我也不想對著你大喊大叫
I-I don't, I don't want to fucking yell at you.
他爸爸不在了
He's deceased.
哦
Oh.
呃 呃
Well, uh...
我 呃 很抱歉
I'm, uh, sorry for your loss.
我肯定如果他爸爸還在
I'm sure if he was still around,
他肯定也會同意的
he would agree with the fact that,
就是 這錢還是應該你們來付
you know, you should still pay for it.
像漫畫裡面一樣大的山羊鬍
Comically huge mustache.
他是不是長這樣
Is this what he looked like?
他就長這樣
That's exactly what he looked like.
- 你看上去很害怕   - 是的
- You're scared of me. - Yeah.
唷 他 他 這沒什麼好笑的
Yo, he-he… And that's not funny.
他就這麼衝進來 開始大喊大叫
He burst into the door, started screaming,
氣得鬍子亂飛亂跳
and his mustache was flapping all over the place.
- 亂飛亂跳   - 他看上去像大富翁的那個人
- Flapping. - He looked the Monopoly Man.
非常嚇人
It was terrifying.
「注意看路
"Look both ways!
兩邊都得看」
Look both ways!"
- 簡直神經   - 但我還是得說
- Fucking maniac. - But I will say,
在樹林子裡給小孩紋身可不算什麼好主意
probably not a good idea to tattoo children in the woods.
- 那可不   - 你有可能會惹上麻煩的
- Yeah, probably. - You know, you could get in trouble.
- 是啊 有可能   - 你為什麼要這樣
- Yeah, you could. - Why did you do that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我還以為不會有事的
I thought I would get away with it.
而且 我以為他 至少得15了吧
Plus, I thought he was, like, at least 15, you know?
- 哦真的嗎   - 我 我第一個紋身是我
- Oh, really? - I got... Yeah, I got my first tattoo...
- 他到底多大了   - 9歲
- How old was he? - Nine.
你以為他15了
You thought he was 15?
- 是的 我簡直   - 你是不是抽太多了
- Yeah, I'm fucking… - Maybe you've been smoking too much.
我可能就是蠢
I think I'm just stupid.
你得看看我媽最近
No, you should see my mom, though.
- 自從我妹妹走了以後就很奇怪   - 是嗎
- It's so weird since my sister left. - Yeah.
她總是在哭 而且
She's just crying all the time and, like,
她總是想跟我聊天 跟我待著
she's trying to talk to me and hang out with me.
有一天 她讓我陪她去逛商場
The other day, she asked me to go to Nordstrom Rack.
我差點就自刎了
I almost slit my throat.
那你去了嗎
Did you go?
沒有 我假裝睡著了
No. I pretended to be asleep.
拜託 她 她可能就是想有個人陪陪她
Oh, come on, she… Maybe she needs company.
你妹妹走了以後她很孤單
She's lonely without your sister.
沒錯 她 她肯定會寂寞的
Yeah, she's-she's, she's gonna be lonely.
你是沒看見她在我妹妹歡送派對上的樣子
I mean, you should've seen her at my sister's send-off party.
就 就很奇怪
It was, it was really weird.
你們給你妹妹辦歡送會了
There was a party?
是啊
Yeah.
為什麼沒邀請我
Why wasn't I invited?
邀請你去高中畢業派對
To a high school graduation party?
那 都有誰去了
Well, who was there?
就 就是
It was, you know, it was just
家人 之類的
family and... shit.
怎麼 你不想讓我和你家人在一塊嗎
What, you don't want me to be around your family?
從我十歲開始就認識他們了
I've known them since I was ten.
嗯 就是
Well, yeah, I just...
我以為你不會感興趣的
I didn't think it was something you would want to go to.
我錯了
I'm-I'm sorry.
拜託 這也太扯淡了
Come on, that's fucked up.
怎麼了 這怎麼扯淡了
Why? Why is that fucked up?
因為我們 你懂的 我們不一般
Because we're, you know, doing something here.
我們 我們什麼不一般了
We're... Are-are we doing something here?
我也不知道 我以為我們開始了什麼
I don't know, we're starting a thing.
就是 咱倆睡也睡了 玩也玩了
I mean, we're having sex and we're hanging out a lot.
- 就我以為   - 我以為咱倆就是
- I mean, it's… - I thought it was just, like,
就是 沒這麼認真的關係
more, you know, casual than that.
你懂嗎
You know?
那你是說 你生命中的重要時刻不希望我陪著你嗎
Well, you don't want me to go to any, like, life events?
生命 生命中的重要時刻是什麼
Life... What's a life event?
什麼 我都不知道那什麼意思
What does that what does that even mean?
算了 隨便吧
You know what? It's fine.
- 怎麼了   - 沒事
- What? - No, it's fine.
你回來
Come back.
對不 等等
I'm sor... Wait.
等
Wai...
- 你知道嗎 你說的沒錯   - 什麼
- You know what? You're right. - What?
你這話什麼意思 我從來都是錯的
What are you talking about? I'm never right.
不 這次你沒錯 我們就這樣吧
No, you're right. We shouldn't do this anymore.
我不想咱倆再這麼繼續下去了
I don't want to fucking do this anymore.
你說什麼呢 我不明白
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
這事就不對 是個小失誤
It was all a mistake. It was a mistake.
但沒事 咱倆現在達成共識了
But it's fine. We're on the same page.
咱們的關係跟以前一樣
We'll go back to what it was before.
我會像對Oscar和Richie那樣對你
I'll treat you like I do Oscar and Richie.
我不是這個意思
I-It's not even that.
就是 我還不知道我到底想要什麼
It's just, like, I-I don't know what I want yet.
我還在試著理清頭緒
Like, I'm trying to figure my shit out.
你說得對 你確實應該 好好整理整理
And you should. Please do. Figure your shit out.
但以後我不會跟你上床了 好嗎
But we're not gonna have sex anymore, okay?
我得走了
I got to go.
我應該請你跟我一起去的
I should've invited you to the party!
我也不知道那是我人生的重要時刻
I didn't know it was a life event!
我已經跟醫院說好了 到時候直接付錢
I-I already arranged to, uh, pay directly at the hospital.
但如果你想讓我付你支票 你等我兩分鐘 好嗎
But if you want a check, just give me two minutes, okay?
不不不 我 我想付這個錢
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I'm-I'm... I-I want to pay.
我來付 這錢我來付
I'm gonna pay for it. I'm gonna pay for it.
不不不 我會付的
No, no, no. I'm gonna pay for it.
而且我也 我會跟Scott好好談談
And I'm, and I'm also gonna talk to Scott
這事太過分了 簡直瘋了
because that was totally out of line, totally nuts.
對 我明白
Yeah, I-I understand that.
但 聽著 我就是想跟你道個歉
But, uh, look, I just wanted to apologize, okay?
我 上次我有點失控了
I-I got a little out of control before, uh...
我 我讓憤怒沖昏了頭腦
You know, I just, I let my anger get the best of me.
破了當初下的決心
Broke my stupid resolution.
我就是這樣毀了我的婚姻
God knows it's what messed up my marriage,
我 我真的很想跟你道歉 可以嗎
and I-I just really wanted to apologize, okay?
我 我當時很煩躁
I mean, I was upset,
但我不應該那樣表達自己
but I-I shouldn't have conveyed it that way.
你不用道歉
There's no need to apologize.
我兒子表現得像個神經病 這樣不好
My kid's being a fucking lunatic. It's not cool.
我 我也反應過激了 他還行
Oh, I... I overreacted. He's fine.
不 這還只是冰山一角
No, it's the tip of the iceberg.
孩子嘛 好多都這樣
Ah, you know, lot of kids do stuff like this.
嗯 孩子才不這樣呢
Mm, kids don't do stuff like this.
他在小樹林裡對你兒子做了
He did the second-worst thing
第二差的事情
you could do to a kid in the woods.
不管怎麼樣吧 我之前不應該那樣對你
Well, either way, I shouldn't have behaved the way I behaved.
所以我真心向你道歉
So, I'm truly sorry.
我接受你的道歉 這很好
Apology accepted. It's nice.
這附近的人可不都這樣
Don't get many of those around here.
- 謝謝   - 哦 這樣可能
- Thanks. - Oh, hey, this might seem
有點突然 但是
a little crazy, but, uh...
我能請你喝杯咖啡嗎
can I take you out for a cup of coffee?
Scott給我紋了這個
So, Scott did this.
哦 這是個可卡犬嗎
Oh. Is that a cocker spaniel?
不不 這是我女兒
No. No, that's my daughter.
我女兒Claire
That's Claire.
哦 沒錯 我看
Oh, yeah, yeah. I can...
- 我以為   - 沒事
- Yeah, I just thought… - No, it's okay.
- 我以為那是耳朵   - 沒事
- I thought those were ears. - Um, it's okay.
- 那是她的頭髮   - 是的 我明白了
- That's her hair. Okay, yep. - I know. I hear that.
Scott十六歲的時候有了他第一個紋身
Scott got his first tattoo when he was 16.
- 哦 這樣   - 他紋了個科米蛙
- Oh, okay. - It was of Kermit the Frog.
- 還挺可愛的   - 是啊 是啊
- That's kind of cute. - Yeah, yeah.
抽大麻的科米蛙 嗯
Kermit smoking a joint, so...
抽大麻的科米蛙
Kermit smoking a joint?
天 我怎麼不記得芝麻街裡
Geez, I don't remember that episode
有這麼一集 哈
on Sesame Street, huh?
還挺好笑的 他是個幽默的孩子吧
That's kind of funny. He's a funny kid, then, huh?
- 他特別好笑   - 是嗎
- Oh, he's so funny. - Yeah?
- 他真的很好笑   - 你覺得他會事業有成嗎
- He's so funny. - You think he's gonna stick it out?
嗯 我也不知道
Uh, well, that I don't know.
我 我曾把他送去藝術學校 但他退學了
I mean, I sent him to art school, but he quit.
他 他沒法集中 因為
He-he couldn't really focus 'cause...
他有注意力缺失症 所以他
He also has ADD, so he...
反正 他是個有注意力缺失症的紋身藝術家
Anyway, he's a tattoo artist with ADD.
嘿 你知道嗎
Well, you know what?
我們消防局裡的所有人
All the guys down at the firehouse,
他們都有紋身之類的
they all have tattoos and stuff, you know.
我自己是沒有紋過 但是
Personally, I never got one, though, you know.
你知道 我也不是反對這個事
You know, not that I have anything against them.
我就是 我總覺得我太慫了
I just, I just always felt I was too pasty.
- 消防局 是吧   - 是的
- So, the firehouse, huh? - Yeah.
那個消防局
The old firehouse.
- 嗯 就是那個消防局   - 是啊
- Mm-hmm, the old firehouse. - Yeah.
你負責爬梯子還是負責消防車
So, you're a ladder or engine?
爬梯子
Ladder.
我猜也是
Knew it.
你們家有誰是消防員嗎
You got firefighters in your family?
是的 我先生
Yeah, my husband.
- 哦 天 很抱歉   - 沒事
- Oh, geez. Sorry. - Yeah.
我忘了
Forgot.
嘿 不知道這樣是不是唐突了 但是你不介意的話
Hey, uh, I hope this isn't too forward, but do you mind
我能問問你先生發生了什麼事嗎
if-if I ask what happened to your husband?
哦 有個酒店著火了
Oh, it was a hotel fire.
屋頂塌陷
The roof collapsed.
他進去想救人
He went in to save somebody.
他們告訴他這樣太危險了 但是你知道 他就是那種人
They told him it wasn't safe, but, you know, he was like that.
- 等等 San Carlin是你丈夫嗎   - 沒錯
- Wait, Stan Carlin was your husband? -  Mm-hmm.
- 派拉蒙酒店大火   - 是的
- Paramount Hotel fire? - Yeah, yeah.
你認識他嗎
Did you know him?
- 你 你聽說過   - 沒沒沒有
- You, you... Or you heard… - No, no, no, I...
你見過他還是
Hung out with him or...?
不 我只是聽說過他
No, I j… I just heard about him.
他真的很勇敢
He was a real brave guy.
- 是啊   - 他其實
- Yeah. - He was kind of a,
其實是個傳奇人物 老實跟你說
kind of a legend, to be honest with you.
是 是吧
Yeah. Yeah.
事情發生的時候 Scott那時候才7歲 所以
And Scott was only seven when it happened, so...
- 哦 那還挺難的   - 導致了很多後果
- Oh, that's tough. - A lot of consequences.
- 是啊 這情況挺艱難的   - 是啊
- Yeah, that's a tough situation, but… - Yeah.
但我還是得說 你做得很棒 你知道嗎
But I-I got to tell you, you did a great job, you know?
你看 我是說
See, I mean, I...
我知道我們之前有點小小的衝突
I know we had a little bit of a difference there,
但是 我覺得 他是個好孩子
but, I mean, he's a good kid.
而且我得說 如果他所做的最壞的事
And I got to tell you, if-if the worst he's doing is-is,
是給人畫幾個不正規的紋身
you know, a couple unlawful tattoos,
- 你做得真的很棒了   - 是啊
- you-you did a hell of a job. - Yeah.
但 我卻不覺得這是他會做的最壞的情況
Yeah, I don't think that's the worst he's doing, though.
- 是啊   - 害 我也不知道了
- Yeah. - Well, I don't know.
但是 小孩嘛 就這樣的 不是嗎
You know, uh, that's how kids are, you know?
每個人在不同時期總會經歷這樣一段
Everybody gets it at a different time.
不管怎樣 你 呃
Anyways, what are you, uh...
咱們坐在這裡 全聽我說話了
I-I'm just sitting here, doing all the talking here.
你呢 你是做什麼的
What do you, what do you do?
我是個護士
I'm a nurse.
在學校裡的護士
I'm a school nurse.
也在急診室當護士
I'm also an ER nurse.
你在急診室工作嗎
You work in the ER?
天啊 Margie 我們之前可能見過
Jesus Christ, Margie, we probably met each other.
有可能
Could be.
那 你工作如何
So, how you doing?
我
I'm...
非常累
very tired.
真的嗎 你看上去精神不錯
Really? Well, you don't look tired.
真的我說真的 你看上去很好
No, seriously, you look great.
- 真的嗎   -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我就是 你 你是在跟我調情嗎
I just don't, like... I mean, are you flirting with me or...?
- 對啊   - 真的嗎
- Yeah. - Yeah?
真的 我很努力了 看上去不像嗎
Yeah, a lot. This is, this is what it looks like.
還挺微妙的 我都不
It is really subtle. I couldn't...
我都看不出來是不是
I can't tell what's going on.
這就是了 我的確做得很微妙
This is how it looks. I'm very subtle.
行吧
All right.
- 我比較笨 你比較巧妙   - 對啊
- I'm rusty. You're subtle. - Okay.
- 是 是啊   - 很高興認識你
- Yeah, yeah. - Nice to meet you.
我看到你在外面的表現了 哥們 幹得不錯
I see you out there, man. You're doing great.
繼續 繼續保持
Keep... Just keep doing what you're doing.
享受工作 明白嗎
Have a good time, you know?
你開心 顧客也會開心
The more fun you have, the more fun the customers have.
好的 謝啦
All right, thanks.
嘿打雜的 為什麼12號桌還是髒的
Hey, busboy, why is table 12 still dirty?
哦 他們之前還在聊天
Oh, 'cause they were talking.
我覺得我不應該打擾到他們 但是
I didn't think I should interrupt them, but...
打斷他們 讓他們走
Interrupt them. Get them out of here.
- 好吧   - 這是你的工作
- All right. - Do your job.
- 抱歉   - 小心點 夥計
- Sorry. Whoa. - Take it easy there, brother.
- 我錯了   - 天啊   - 謝謝
- My bad. - Jesus. - Thank you.
呃 你好 你這邊吃完了嗎
Uh, hi. Uh, are you done enjoying your meal?
我嘴巴裡還有東西 而且我還在嚼呢
There is food in my mouth, and I am chewing.
你覺得我吃完了嗎
Do you think that I'm finished?
我是舉著這個純當鍛煉是嗎
I'm just holding this for my health?
- 給我倒點水   - 抱歉
- Get me some water. - Sorry.
- 嘿 你過來 過來 我們能點單了嗎   - 可以啊
- Hey, come here. Come here. Can we order? - Uh, yeah.
- 我去叫你這桌的服務員   - 不行 不行
- I'll go get your waiter. - No, no, no.
我們沒時間等了 待會還有事呢
We don't have time for that. We're in a hurry.
我餓死了
I'm starving.
好 那我先點了
Okay. Can I go?
通常是女士優先 但算了你點吧
Usually, the woman goes first, but go ahead.
- 沒事沒事   - 是嗎
- No, no, no, no. - Oh, yeah?
- 要不然這頓我付了   - 行吧
- How about I'm paying? - All right.
我要一個巴馬芝士雞胸排 加肉醬
Can I have a chicken parm with meat sauce?
不要放瑪瑞納拉醬
No marinara.
薄一點 雞排要薄一點
Thin. Thin chicken parm.
你為什麼不寫下來
Why aren't you writing it down?
哦 因為我其實 我其實不負責點餐
Yeah, I-I can't actually because, uh, I'm not a waiter.
我只是個打雜的 所以他們沒有給我筆
I'm just a busboy, so they don't even give me a pen.
那就記住了
Memorize it. Yeah.
我要一個海鮮意面
Seafood pasta. That's what I want.
不要蛤蜊 好嗎 雙份的蝦
No clams, okay? Double up on the shrimp.
我總是這麼點 我們是老顧客了
That's how I always get it. We come here all the time.
你們剛才說的話 我一句都沒記住
I'm not gonna remember a word you guys just said.
這又不是什麼高科技 趕緊去
It's not rocket science. Just go.
- 給我們下單   - 但我 好吧
- Get our shit. - Oh, I'm... All right.
我餓死了
I'm starving.
♪ 給我點興奮劑 我要追捕他們
這是要開舞會嗎還是什麼
There a dance party or something?
- 是格鬥之夜 - 好的 格鬥之夜
- It's fight night. - All right, fight night!
冠軍錦標賽
Tournament of champions!
為了小費而戰
Fighting for tips.
誰要上 誰第一個上
Who's going? Who's going first?
-我 Zoots - Zoots
- I, Zoots. - Zoots.
- 每個人為了他們的小費而戰  - 是我們賺的小費
- Everyone fights for their tips.  - The tips that we earn?
對 但是你現在必須要為它們而戰了
Y-Yeah, but you have to fight for them now.
誰想來點 哼
Who wants some?! Huh?!
- 嗯  -誰要來  - 到你了哥們
- Huh? - Who got it?! - It's you, bro.
- 不可能 不 不可能 - 把手套帶上
- No way. No, no way. - Put the gloves on.
上吧 上吧 揍他
Get in there. Get in there. Hit him.
-嘿 喲 - 嘿
- Hey, yo. - Hey.
我不想 別這樣 我不想幹這個
I don't want... Please, I don... I-I don't want to do this.
- 我們還是別打了  - 你不想打了
- Let's just not do this. - You don't want to do this?
- 你什麼意思  - 嗯 我的意思是我們是朋友對吧
- What do you mean? - No, well, 'cause we're friends, right?
但是在接下來的15秒
Yeah, no, for the next 15 seconds,
我們的友誼結束了 朋友
this friendship is over, son.
-明白嗎  - 啥
- Understand that? - What?
- 嗯  - 啥
- Hmm? - What?
你必須得明白 格鬥是件嚴肅的事情
Got to understand, fighting is serious.
-我不喜歡  - 太嚇人了
- I don't like it. - It's sacred.
這是我向我的主和救世主致敬的方式
It's how I tribute my Lord and Savior.
-啥  - 這是我向
- What? - It's the way I tribute
我的主和救世主致敬的方式 耶穌
my Lord and Savior, Jesus.
我不認為耶穌會讓你
I don't think Jesus would want you
把我揍出屎
to kick my ass right now.
他想讓我拿走小費
He would want me to have these tips.
- 這是他的意思  - 你可以把小費都拿走
- That's what he means. - You can have the tips.
我原來也沒想要
I don't even want 'em.
- 這是啥啊  - 我不知道
- What is this? - I don't know.
這什麼鬼
What's this shit?
我看過好幾遍《奎迪》
I've seen Creed a f... a couple times.
- 你看了啥  - 我看了好幾遍《奎迪》
- What'd you do? - I seen Creed a couple times.
- 噢  - 我們在跳Cotton Eye Joe嗎
- Oh. - Are we about to do the Cotton Eye Joe?
一首鄉村樂及其延伸的民間舞蹈
- 沒錯 - 沒錯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- 來吧 朋友 - 好的
- Come on, son. - Okay.
- 好的 - 來吧 老弟 噢 這才對
- Yeah. Okay. - Come on, son. Oh, that's right.
你要過來這裡嗎 來這兒 老弟
You gonna come this way? Come this way, boy.
-好的  - 來吧 出拳吧夥計
- Okay. - Come on. Go ahead, take your shot, boy.
- 來吧 出拳吧 夥計  - 真的？
- Go ahead, take your shot, boy. - For real?
- 嗯哼 耶 來吧  - 噢
- Uh-huh, yeah. Come on! - Ooh!
現在我們是朋友了
Now we are friends,
- 該死的  - 噢 天啊
- goddamn it! - Oh, geez.
吃屎吧 耶
Take that shit. Yeah!
我們現在是朋友啦 這就是朋友的意義
We friends now, nigga, 'cause that's what friends are for.
淘汰了這個傢伙
Out this bitch.
Zoots又成功了一次
Zoots done did it again, uh
跟我說Zoots又成功了一次
Said Zoots done did it again, ah...
我想我們有了贏家
I think we have a winner.
- 過來  - 嗯嗯
- Come here. - Mm-hmm.
嗯
Mm.
嗯 讓我...
Mm. Let me just...
- 我想把毛衣脫掉  - 好啊
- Just want to get this sweater off. - Okay.
再把這個燈關上
And I want to turn off this light.
讓我把這個燈關上
Let me turn it off.
- 好  - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
等我一下
Just one-one second.
讓我 讓我 把這個燈關上
Let me, let me, let me turn off this light.
檯燈可真多
Got a lot of lamps, huh?
和商店似的
It's like a store or something.
來吧
Come here.
嗯
Mm.
♪ 很好
♪ 姑娘 最近怎樣 我想我是多此一問
♪ 現在要讓他們都去死，我已經買好了棺材
♪ 他們本來該逮捕你 或者直接逮捕那個給你買衣服的傢伙
♪ 我不想給你增添壓力
♪ 但是我想讓你知道 姑娘 你的魅力秒殺了他們
♪ 你秒殺了他們
♪ 姑娘 你秒殺了他們
♪ 噢 噢 噢
♪ 一直被模仿 從未被超越
♪ 人們說她是個超級美女 要我說這都算低估
♪ 漂亮 我剛與她邂逅
♪ 下一步已經出爐
♪ 讓我的老情人 立馬處決
♪ 姑娘最近怎樣 我想是多此一問
♪ 現在要讓他們都去死 我已經買好了棺材
♪ 姑娘 你秒殺了他們
♪ 你秒殺了他們
- Scott  - 在
- Scott? - Yo.
過來一下
Come sit down.
我有點事情想給你說
I need to talk to you about something.
怎麼啦
What's up?
有人死了
Someone die?
不 誰都沒死
No, no, nobody's dead.
謝天謝地
Thank God.
我開始約會了
I'm seeing somebody.
什麼意思
What does that mean?
呃 我在和一個男人約會
Uh, uh, I'm seeing a man.
我 我已經和個男人約會了一陣了
Well, I-I've been dating someone for a little while now.
你在約會
You're dating someone?
那 那太棒了啊
That-That's awesome.
為啥你要偷偷的約會 小蕩婦
Like, w-why are you dating him secretly, you little slut?
你怎麼不告訴我呢
W-Why didn't you tell me?
是... 是因為他特別特別老...
Is he, like, really, really old or...
還是特別特別年輕
or is he really, really young?
難道是我的朋友 是Igor嗎
Is it one of my friends? Is it Igor?
不 不 不 我只是
No, no, no. I just, I...
我只是不想讓你困擾 除非這事能成
I just didn't want to bother you unless it was really serious.
困擾 你是我媽啊
Bother? You're my mom.
我當然希望你能非常性福
I hope you're getting banged out real good.
這個幸運兒是誰啊
Who's the lucky guy?
呃 是...
Uh, it's, um...
是Ray
It's Ray.
誰是Ray
Who's Ray?
你還記得那個被你紋身的孩子嗎
Remember the kid you tattooed?
是他爸爸
His father.
- 是那個混蛋  - 嗯 我知道
- That fucking prick? - Yeah, I know.
他真的是個很好的人 對我也很好
He's a really nice man, and he's really good to me.
- 他還是消防員  - 他是個消防員
- And he's a fireman. - He's a fireman?!
這就操蛋了
That's fucked up.
- 為什麼  - 你是什麼意思 為什麼
- Why? - W-What do you mean, why?
自從17年前我爸死了以後 你就沒有約會過任何人了
I mean, uh, you haven't dated anyone in 17 years since Dad,
然後你約會的第一個人還是消防員
and the first guy you date is a fireman?
你不感覺有點奇怪嗎
You don't think that's a little fucking weird?
我對消防員沒什麼意見啊
I got nothing against firemen.
我也沒有 但是這傢伙也不喜歡我
Neither do I, but the-the guy doesn't like me,
這人和我爸幹著一樣的工作
and he has the same job as Dad, like...
我已經搞砸了 媽 我還有克羅恩病
I'm fucked up as it is, Mom. Like, I have Crohn's, okay?
一種原因不明的腸道炎症性疾病
我這裡也不怎麼正常
There's something wrong up here. Huh.
我找不到手錶
I can't find my watch!
你想對我做什麼
What are you trying to do to me here?!
我受的苦還不夠多嗎
Haven't I been through enough?!
等等 我幹了什麼 我做錯什麼事了嗎
Wait, what did I, what did I do wrong?
我做錯事了嗎 我幹了什麼
W-What did I do wrong? What did I do?
我 對不起 我做了什麼
What... I'm sorry. Like, what did I do?
我沒有 我沒有對你怎麼樣
I'm not, I'm not doing it to you.
我只是不想下半輩子一直孤零零的
I just... I-I don't want to be alone the rest of my life.
我也不想讓你孤獨
I don't want you to be alone, either.
那這樣就很爛了 就像是 就像是
That would suck, but, like, come on. This is, like...
這很明顯不是一個好的選擇 對吧
This is pretty obvious this is not a good choice, right?
我想一起吃個飯
I would like us to have dinner.
這... 這對我很重要
I... This is very, very important to me.
我對這份感情十分認真
I am in a serious relationship...
- 你十分認真  - 和一個好人
- You're in a serious rela... - ...with a very nice man.
那個人 得了吧
With that guy?! Come on!
你不愛他的 對吧
Y-You don't love him, do you?
你不會那麼說吧... 你不會那麼說的 對吧
You're not say... You're not, like, saying that, right?
呃 我們還沒說那個字
I-I... Well, we don't use that word yet.
但是如果他對我說了 我想我應該也會說
But if he said it to me, I-I would say it back.
噢天啊 上帝
Oh, my God! Jesus!
你還沒長記性嗎
Do you not learn?!
你看看上次發生的事
Look what happened last time!
- 你想再來一遍嗎  - 好的 好吧
- You want to do that again? - Okay. All right?
這怎麼樣
How about this?
我們一起去你工作的餐廳
How about we come by the restaurant
吃一頓晚飯
and we have dinner when you're working
然後你就過來打個招呼
and you just come by and you just say hi?
就過來打幾次招呼 怎麼樣
Just say hi a couple times. How about that?
怎麼樣
How about that?
怎麼樣... 你怎麼不問問他
How about... Why don't you ask him?
昂
Huh?
你怎麼在這裡
Why don't you just build
也給Ray弄一個祠堂
another shrine to Ray while you're at it?
就放爸爸對面 搞不好他們還能成他媽的兄弟了
Right across from Dad's so they can be fucking pals!
嗯 我更喜歡那個
Yeah, I like that better.
我才發現你還挺搞笑
But I'm actually finding you funny
因為你真的很搞笑
'cause you're really funny.
看看這人
Look at this guy.
- 享受著這輩子最好的時光  - 嗯
- Having the time of his life. - Mm-hmm.
好像這是他家一樣
Acting like he owns the place.
我知道這傢伙 帕馬森烤茄子
I know that guy. Eggplant parmesan.
噢 我會的
Oh. I'll be.
你媽像個壞女孩哦
Your moms is a bit of a baddie.
她看起像是 事後
She look postcoital.
- 什麼事後  - 就是睡完以後
- What's "postcoital"? - It's like post-fucking,
但因為是你媽 我想禮貌一點
but it's your mom, so I want to be nice.
但是 哦 絕對已經發生了
But, uh, oh, it's definitely happening.
事後
Postcoital.
如果你來看我
If you ever come to see me,
如果你來看我 那...
if you ever come see me, that's...
- 那晚上會發生的 我保證  - 我知道
- It'll happen that night, I guarantee it. - Yeah, I know.
噢 他來了
Oh, here he is.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 你好嗎 - 挺好 你呢
- How you doing? - Good. How are you?
很高興再見到你
Good to see you again. Yeah.
呃 我很抱歉給你兒子打了標
Uh, I'm-I'm really sorry for branding your kid.
噢 沒有沒有 沒關係的 沒關係的
Oh, no, no, no. It's-it's fine. It's fine.
花了三百五十塊 但是我沒讓你媽掏錢
Cost 350, but I didn't make your mom pay for it.
但是 嘿 沒傷害 沒犯法
But, uh, hey, no harm, no foul.
你知道 要是沒有這檔子事 我...
You know? 'Cause, uh, if that didn't happen, I, uh...
我也不會遇見這位美麗的女士
wouldn't have met this lovely lady.
噢 很高興幫忙
Oh, well, happy to help.
事情解決了
Things work out.
對
Yeah.
感謝上天我幹了這事
Thank God I did what I did, then.
你們是想要純淨水還是
Uh, would you guys like to start with still
呃 蘇打水
or, uh, sparkling water?
- 哦 那就蘇打水  - 噢 蘇打水 好
- Oh, let's go sparkling. - Uh, spar... Yeah.
你喜歡蘇打水嗎
Yeah? You like sparkling?
- 喜歡 - 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
我們能再來點麵包嗎
Yeah. Oh, can we get some more bread, too?
一般就這樣
Usually go still.
知道嗎 上次我來的時候 麵包是熱著上來的
You know? Last time I came here, it came out hot.
- 對 - 真的 真的是太完美了
- Yeah. - It was... oh, it was perfect.
就像是我媽做的一樣
It's like my mom made it.
當然
Sure.
蘇打水和熱麵包
Sparkling and hot bread.
好的 謝謝夥計
All right. Thanks, buddy.
噢 你不能就那麼吐口水 兄弟
Oh, you just can't spit on that like that, man.
你得狡猾一點 你可別就那麼吐上
You got to be crafty. You can't just go out at, like...
你得 你得略施小計
You got to, you got to maneuver.
拿舌頭舔舔或者放點料進去
Lick on it or put a boogie in it or something.
你覺著我能把這一整個塞進屁股裡嗎
You think I can fit this whole thing in my ass?
如果 呃 你真的下決心要那麼干 兄弟
If, uh, you really put your mind to it, bro.
嘿 我看見他往麵包裡吐口水了
Hey, I saw him spit in the bread.
來了 熱騰騰的麵包
All right, scorching hot bread.
- 哦  謝謝 - 好
- Oh, thank you. - Yeah.
你媽媽去上廁所了 請坐一下吧
Your mom's in the john. Have a seat.
噢 別擔心 你不會惹上麻煩的
Oh, don't worry, you're not gonna get in trouble.
就一小會
Just for a minute.
好吧
All right.
那麼... 你喜歡在這裡工作嗎
So... how, uh, how you liking the job here?
呃 挺操蛋的
Uh, it eats ass.
我記得 原來的時候
You know, I remember I... Back in the day,
我在那個地方 那個披薩店上過班
I used to work at that, uh, you know that pizza parlor
- 主路頭上的那家 - 嗯
- down there on Main Street? - Mm.
- 你還記得那家嗎 - 我過去在那裡上班
You remember the one? Yeah. I-I used to work down there.
我愛死它了 做披薩
I loved it. You know, making the pizzas.
姑娘們老來
Girls would come in, you know.
她們就不得不和我說話
It's like they just had to talk to me.
嗯
Yeah.
嗯 那真不錯
Well, that's awesome.
我很開心你在披薩店約到不少
I'm glad you got laid a lot at your pizza place.
好吧 聽著 Scott
All right. Listen, Scott.
我知道這有點奇怪
I-I know this is weird, okay?
你和你媽媽已經單獨生活了很久
You and your mom were alone together for a long time.
你有自己的熟悉的套路 對嗎
You got set in your ways, you know?
你都已經習慣了
You got used to things.
但我不知道 我就感覺
But I don't know, I just feel like
你媽媽現在值得的到更多
your mother deserves more right now.
我是認真的 我真的覺得我可以讓她高興
And I'm serious, I really think that I can make her happy,
她也能讓我高興
and she makes me happy.
我的意思 這是件好事 對吧
So, I mean, that-that's a good thing, right?
對 對 我覺得是個特棒的事
Yeah. Yeah, I think it's a great thing.
我... 我希望我媽高興比一切都重要 那...
I... I want my mom to be happy more than anything, so...
那太好了 我也是
Good. I do, too.
你喜歡什麼運動
So, uh, what's your sport?
- 呃 我喜歡籃球 - 哦 是嗎
- Uh, I like basketball. - Oh, yeah?
- 嗯 - 打什麼位置
- Mm-hmm. - What position?
呃 我打小前鋒
Uh, I played small forward.
- 小前鋒 - 對
- Small forward. - Yeah.
好吧 我自己算是棒球迷
All right. I'm kind of a baseball guy myself.
- 哦 是嗎？ - 你喜歡 呃...
- Oh, yeah? - You like, uh...
我是個老頭 我喜歡那玩意
I'm an old man. I like that stuff.
我有洋基隊的季票
I got season tickets to the Yankees.
- 不可能吧 真的嗎 那太帥了 - 對
- No way. Really? That's cool. - Yeah.
今年是史泰登島的一年
I think it's Staten Island's year.
噢 史泰登島洋基隊啊
Oh, Staten Island Yankees.
- 小聯盟 - 噢 當然
- Minor League. - Oh, absolutely.
我才不會掏錢去看那些貴的要死的小屁孩
I'm not gonna go pay to see those overpaid crybabies.
他們很努力的維持小聯盟的位置
They try harder at the Minor League level.
還有 我還是紅襪隊的粉絲 從來沒變過
Plus, I'm a Red Sox fan. I'm never setting foot
- 在那個體育場裡 - 好吧 我得回去了
- in that stadium. - Well, I-I should get back
回去工作 呃 在被吼之前
to work, uh, before I get yelled at.
- 好吧 去吧 - 那麼 就這樣
- Okay. Go ahead. - So, yeah.
-當然 好的 - 好的
- Absolutely. All right. - All right, man.
享受熱麵包吧
Uh, enjoy the hot bread.
- 嘿 - 好的 酷
- Hey. - Okay, cool.
嘿
Hey.
你們兩個在討論什麼呢
What are you fellas talking about?
- 嘿 媽媽 - 我就在問Scott
- Hey, Mom. - Oh, I was just asking Scott
他有沒有空來看洋基隊的比賽
if he wanted to go to a Yankee game sometime.
噢 Scott怎麼說
Oh, what did Scott say?
Scott... Scott說好啊
S-Scott... Scott said yeah.
好的 今天晚上誰要打拳
All right, who's fighting tonight?!
我想打打拳
I want to fight somebody!
哦 對不起 Pepe
Oh, I'm sorry, Pepe.
我不是針對你
Don't take this personally.
噢
Oh!
怎麼了這是
What happened?
就是一擊刺拳
That was just a jab.
噢 沒事的 Pepe
Oh, it's okay, Pepe.
- 沒關係的 - 你... 你確定嗎
- It's all right. - You s... You sure?
當然
Yeah.
我之前從來也沒有這樣過
I-I mean, I never done that before, so...
我感覺很對不起你
I feel bad for you.
♪ 在街道上
♪ 的角落裡
♪ Willy在和窮孩子們一起玩耍
你好啊 謝謝
How you doing? Thank you.
謝謝 謝謝
Thank you. Thank you.
♪ 裝腔作勢的人在路上栽了跟頭、
♪ 引來了人們的朗朗笑聲
♪ 彈貝斯的人的勇氣可嘉還獨奏了一段
♪ 窮孩子們彈起了琴...
觀眾們請注意
May I please remind you
場地內禁止使用閃光燈拍照
that there is no flash photography.
你好嗎 你好嗎 你們還在戒酒嗎
How are you? How are you? You guys still sober?
- 投球真垃圾 投的真爛 - 你就那麼干
- Shitty throw. Shitty throw, though. - That's how you do it!
好的 就這樣 就這樣
All right, there we go. There we go.
跑 寶貝兒 跑啊
Let's go, baby, let's go.
精神點
Look alive!
你覺著他們能拿下三色堇施平納嗎
Think we're gonna take these pansy Spinners tonight?
哦 兄弟 我覺著要是拿不下施平納
Oh, man, we can't take the Spinners,
- 那乾脆就別打了  - 嗯
- you might as well just shut it down. - Mm.
我們得加把勁兒
We should just pack it in,
把這些人送回單A
send these guys back to Single-A.
美國棒球小聯盟主要分為3A 2A 和單A三個梯隊
我孩子兒童聯盟的隊伍可以給這些人
My kid's Little League team could give these guys
出人頭地的機會
a run for their money.
這些人也都還能打
These guys are all on the job, too.
這是老混蛋
The old ballbuster here...
他是這裡的老大哥
he's the senior man of the house.
你叫我老
Did you call me a senior?
你是這裡唯一的禿子
You're the one who's bald.
得了吧 Papa 我就是開個玩笑
Come on, Papa. I'm just fucking around.
嘿 想吃熱狗嗎
Hey, you want a hot dog?
噢 不 我有克羅恩病
Oh, no, I can't. I, uh, I have Crohn's.
那是個啥
What's that?
就是你的胃裡全部都亂套了
It's, like, when the lining of your stomach is all messed up,
讓你總是需要開大
so it makes you shit all the time.
哦 謝謝分享
Oh, thanks for sharing.
下次你就只說我不想要熱狗就行
Next time, just say, "I don't want a hot dog."
好的 我只是想讓大家多多瞭解一下
All right, I'm just trying to spread awareness.
就這樣 就這樣
There we go. There we go.
- 打得漂亮 打得漂亮 - 看著真棒 夥計們
- Nice hit. Nice hit. - Looking good, guys.
幹的不錯
Way to hustle.
26號
Number 26...
嘿 呃
Hey, uh...
你有沒有想過要穿上這身制服
you ever think about putting on the jacket?
- 不  - 你笑的什麼
- No. - What are you laughing about?
這是個很傻的問題 Ray
'Cause it's a stupid question, Ray.
- 你說傻什麼意思  - 這他媽就是很傻
- What do you mean, stupid? - It's fucking stupid.
如果你問那個在太空被炸死的老師的孩子
Would you ask the kids of that teacher who blew up in space
你想不想當個宇航員
if they want to be an astronaut?
哇 我不覺著那個女士有孩子
Whoa, I don't think that lady had any kids, though.
是啊 我也覺著她沒有 她都死在天上了
Yeah, I'm sure she didn't 'cause she died in space.
你要是死在天上就不太容易生個孩子
It's hard to have kids when you're dead in space.
聽著 我可以告訴你我對消防員的感覺
Look, I-I could tell you how I feel about firemen,
但是 我覺著這些夥計不會想聽我的意見
but I-I don't think you guys want to hear my opinion.
- 不是的 請告訴我們 - 別 別 別這樣
- No, no, no, please tell us. - No, no. No, no, no.
- 別 我不想聽 - 你不用非得那麼干
- No. I want to hear it. - You don't got to do this, man.
- 得了吧 - 行吧
- Come on. - All right, no.
- 行 那這樣怎麼樣 - 算了 你別
- Yeah. Okay, how about this? - Come on, you don't...
嗯 如果你是個消防員 就別要孩子了
Uh, if you're a fireman, just don't have kids
或者家庭也乾脆別要 行吧
or a family at all, okay?
那樣的話 當你他媽回不了家的時候
So that way, you don't fucking crush them
也不會讓他們徹底崩潰 明白嗎
when you don't come home that one time, you know?
你們就是太自私了
And-and you're just so selfish.
你們成天就和你們的兄弟閒逛
You just hang out with your boys all day
像他媽的兄弟會一樣
like it's a fucking frat house.
甚至一半的時間都沒在滅火
Half the time, you're not even putting out fires.
就只會打飛機 看《疤面煞星》 對吧
You're just jerking off, watching Scarface, okay?
- 行了 放鬆點 夥計 - 不 我就是那麼說
- All right, take it easy, man. - No, I'm just saying.
你告訴孩子你會一輩子
And it's wrong to tell a kid that you're gonna be there
陪在他身邊是不對的
for him for his whole entire life.
嗯 然後你就會錯過畢業典禮 錯過生日 是吧
Yeah, but you miss graduation, your birthdays, okay?
嗯 還有我的畢業舞會
Uh, my d... my prom dances.
這對一個孩子來說太殘忍了
That's a very mean thing to do to children.
如果你有一個家庭
And, uh, if you have a family,
- 那你就是個混蛋 - 不 聽我說 不
- y-you're an asshole. - No, listen, no.
放鬆 放鬆點
Take it easy, take it easy.
- 這是一種方式看待他 - 對
- Well, that's one way to look at it. - Yeah.
給我爸說去吧
Tell that to my dad.
但是你不能 因為他死了
Oh, but you can't, 'cause he's dead.
有人對此有什麼好的說法嗎
Anybody got a good response to that?
耶
Yeah!
再來
Again!
哇哦
Whoo!
比賽太棒了 比賽太棒了
What a game. What a game.
所以 我不該生孩子了
So, what, I shouldn't have kids?
不 你可以有孩子
No, you... you should have kids.
我要生孩子
I'm gonna have kids.
你知道 也許你該從你的T恤上
You know, maybe you should take a cue
學一下 明白嗎 微笑
from your shirt, you know? Smile.
放輕鬆
Lighten up.
實際上還挺搞笑
That's actually kind of funny.
好的夥計們 為什麼不能更像他一點
Guy's all right. Why can't you be more like him?
他沒事的
He's all right.
為什麼你要讓我那麼尷尬
Why can't you not embarrass me like this?
對不起
I'm sorry.
對不起我讓你在你朋友面前丟人了
I'm sorry I embarrassed you in front of your friends.
繼續堅持你的立場吧
And just-just stick to your guns.
好嗎 會好的
All right? It'll be fine.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey!
進來吧
Come on in.
和我們一塊吃早飯
Come have breakfast with us.
我做了薄烤餅 還做了你喜歡吃的香腸
I made pancakes, and I made the sausage that you like,
還有煎蛋卷
an omelet.
來吧 來吧 來坐下
Come, come, come, come sit.
夥計 這雞蛋配著
Man, these eggs are spectacular.
洋蔥和胡椒真的太讚了
With the onions and the peppers.
太好吃了 太好吃了
I love it. I love it.
他這是 在這裡呆了一晚上嗎
Did, uh, did he sp-spend the night?
對 是的
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
他昨晚睡在這裡
He slept here.
在這屋裡
In this house.
我已經成年了哦 這沒什麼問題
I'm an adult. I can do that.
有些事情我想和你談一談
I-I need to talk to you about something.
好的
Okay.
我覺得 你現在是時候
I was thinking that it's time
去找一間屬於你自己的公寓了
to think about getting your own apartment.
什麼
What?
你為什麼這麼說
W-Why would you say that?
是這樣的
Well...
你呢 是個很棒的孩子
You are so awesome.
而我呢 有時候可能有點過分關照你了
And I think I've been there for you too much.
人嘛 往往只有在走出安全區的時候
'Cause sometimes in life, the thing that's motivating
才能激發他的潛能
is when people don't have that safety net.
話是沒錯 但我現在正需要這份安全感
Right, right, but I need that safety net
我還沒準備好呢
'cause I don't have my shit together.
為什麼 你早不提完不提 偏偏現在提
So, like, uh, w-why are you doing this?
是因為他嗎
Is this 'cause of him?
不
No.
你看你也二十四歲了
It's just you're 24 years old now.
二十四啊 菲爾普斯二十四的時候都好幾塊金牌了
24. I mean, Phelps had a fistful of gold medals by 24.
你插什麼嘴
Why are you talking?
我也就是給些參考 沒別的意思
I'm just giving you some perspective, that's all.
你看啊 格雷茨基二十四歲的時候 已經打進了九十六球
You know, Wayne Gretzky had, like, 96 goals when he was 24.
加拿大著名冰球運動員
啥
W-What?
羅傑·斯陶巴 現實畢業於西點軍校
Roger Staubach graduated West Point,
著名美式足球運動員
然後贏得了海斯曼獎 再參加了越南戰爭
won a Heisman Trophy, fought in the Vietnam War,
授予美式足球傑出大學生球員
回來後加盟了達拉斯牛仔 那時他也就二十四歲
and then joined the Cowboys by the time he was 24.
這都是些什麼人 關我屁事啊
I don't know who that is, so, s-so who-who gives a fuck?
我覺得 你應該可以的
I think that maybe you're-you're ready
只是你自己不自覺
and you just don't even know it.
所以你是要把我趕出去咯
So, you're kicking me out?
不 不是的
No, no.
我只是希望 你可以夏天前 找好自己的公寓
I just want you to get your own apartment by summer.
好的 所以說就是把我趕出去咯
Right, so you're kicking me out of the house.
有整整九個月的時間呢
That's nine months from now.
你看啊 九個月你如果動作快一點孩子都有了
I mean, you-you could have a baby in nine months.
時間還多著呢
It's a long time.
你是要搬進來嗎 所以先要把我擠出去嗎
Are you moving in? Are you trying to push me out?
我到底是做了什麼 我以為我們倆關係還行
What, like, what did I do? I-I thought we were cool.
Scott 大家都是成年人了 要互相體諒
Scott, Scott, let's all be adults here. Come on.
你媽媽已經以努力了很久了
Your mother has worked very hard for a very long time.
我呢過幾年也要退休了
And I'm gonna retire in a couple years,
所以生活呢會發生一些變化 當然了這都是往好的方向
so things are gonna change around here, but in a good way.
我們相信 你可以自己幹出一番成就的
I mean, w-we think you... that you can do great things.
對對對 我知道我會趕出一番成就
Yeah, I know I'm gonna do great things.
但這不需要你來提醒我 而且啊
But, like, I don't need you to tell me that, like...
這到底是怎麼回事
This is... What's going on?
我怎麼了我
This is... I-I...
我不喜歡這樣
I don't like this.
別太在意 就目前來說
So, be that as it may,
直到你搬出去前 當然了搬出去對你是一件好事
until you leave... which is gonna be good for you
可以幫助你更積極地面對生活
and it's gonna be motivating...
搬出去前 你需要幫忙幹點活兒
you're gonna have to pull your weight
不多不多 就一點兒
a little more around here.
比方說 有件事情 我們就覺得你一定能勝任
And one thing that we thought would help you contribute...
對你來說舉手之勞 一點都不難
would be easy, wouldn't be hard to do...
我們覺得 當Ray需要工作 沒有時間的時候
is to help Ray bring his kids back and forth to school
你可以去幫Ray接孩子上下學
when he can't do it because of work.
比如現在
Like now.
今天開始
Like today.
你們在逗我吧
You're joking, right?
你要我幫你接孩子
You want me to take your kid to school?
就是我給紋身的那個
The kid that I tattooed?
我有兩個孩子 另一個現在七歲
I got two kids. The other one's seven.
你要讓我幫你帶孩子啊
You're gonna make me babysit your kids?
這... 我嗑藥的哦
Do... I'm on... I do drugs.
沒事 我看你現在很清醒啊
Well, looks like you're walking.
謝謝
And thank you.
我現在可是一肚子意見啊聽到沒有
I'm not cool with any of this, okay?
況且 你們要我搬哪裡去
And-and where do you expect me to live?
我拿什麼錢去找地方
And w-with what money?
你知道我還在啃老的不是嗎
You know I'm a fucking bum, right?
都什麼亂七八糟的 臥槽
Yo, this is fucked up! Seriously.
尤其是昨天晚上 還搞什麼交流感情
Especially after last night, all that bonding boy bullshit.
你真的是滿嘴跑火車
You're full of shit, man.
就是一個騙子
You're a fucking liar.
那麼 我現在就去幫你接孩子
I'm gonna go walk your kids.
接個屁 你想也不要想
No, I'm not fucking letting you take 'em.
你誰啊你 就來接孩子
Fuck you. Who the fuck are you?
你可說得太對了
Yeah, I-I agree with you completely.
我來接孩子 這都是Ray出的主意
Why... 'cause that... It was Ray's idea.
我也覺得我來接很不妥當 真的
I don't think I should be taking them, either.
你說得對
I agree with you.
你是變態嗎
Are you a weirdo?
哈 可變態了
Oh, the weirdest.
誰能變態得過我呀
Nobody's weirder than me.
得了吧 變態哪會承認自己是變態
See, a weirdo wouldn't say that.
變態都說自己不變態
A weirdo would deny it.
那麼 我是接還是不接呢
So, do I have to take 'em or...?
接
Yes.
媽呀
God, no.
那怎麼辦 本來應該是Ray干的活
I mean, Ray was supposed to do it.
我也沒辦法
I can't fucking do it.
還有半個小時就上課了
Their schools start half an hour apart
去學校還要橫跨整個小鎮呢
on the other side of town.
我說 你媽勾搭了我前夫是吧
So, your mom is banging my ex?
對 而且我也不是很開心
Yeah, I'm not thrilled about it, either.
那是 你開心的起來就邪乎了
Yeah, well, you shouldn't be.
Harold  Kelly.
Harold. Kelly.
你們過來 快
Come here. Come here.
有好玩的事情哦 快過來
There's something, something kind of fun.
來這邊
Come here. Come here.
你好啊
Oh, hey, man.
這個是Harold 這個是Kelly
So, this is Harold, and this is Kelly.
這位是...
And, uh, this is...
Scott
Scott.
好的Scott 接下來他送你們去學校
Scott. He's gonna be taking care of you.
- 聽到了嗎   - 你好啊 Scott
- Okay?   - It... - Nice to meet you, Scott.
你好啊 Harold 第一次見面吧
Hi, Harold. It's nice to meet you.
真高興認識你
For the very first time.
如果他做了什麼奇怪的事情
If he does anything weird,
你們就告訴我
you tell me.
就算他讓你們不要說 你們也告訴我
Even if he tells you not to tell me, you tell me.
我覺得這人應該挺正常的 但也不是沒可能看走眼
I'm pretty sure he's not weird, but I could be wrong.
明白了嗎
'Kay?
- 愛你們哦   - 好的
- Love you. - Okay.
- 愛你 媽媽   - 我可沒開玩笑
- Love you, Mom. - Seriously.
愛你 媽媽 拜拜
Love you, Mom. Bye.
小心了
Pay attention.
明白
Got it.
拉好手 兩個人的都拉好
Hold both their hands!
謝謝你了
Thank you.
看汽車 兩邊都要看
Look both ways. Look both ways!
讓他別吵
Tell her to stop.
媽呀
God!
Harold 你平時喜歡什麼呀
So, w-what do you like to do, Harold?
我喜歡超級英雄
I like superheroes.
哈 誰不喜歡呢
Well, so does everybody.
我喜歡自己想出來的
No, I make up my own.
這樣啊 什麼樣的英雄呀
Oh, yeah? What kind?
閃冰俠
Ice Flash.
他能幹什麼呢
What does he do?
他能把東西凍住 還能向別人射出冰塊
He freezes stuff and shoots ice at people.
哦 聽著不是很厲害呀
Oh, well, that's not gonna work.
為什麼
Why not?
我那個電吹風就能錘爆他了
I could just use a hair dryer and ruin him.
不過想法不錯 再接再厲
Keep thinking, though.
你呢 你平時都喜歡幹什麼呀
What do you got? What do you like to do?
- 我喜歡唱歌   - 唱歌呀
- I like to sing. - You do?
能給我來一曲兒嗎
Could-could you sing for me?
好的
Sure.
啊 多麼美麗的早晨
Oh, what a beautiful morning
沒錯
Yes.
嘔 多麼美麗的一天
Oh, what a beautiful day
很好
All right.
喜悅由心而生
I've got a wonderful feeling
萬事順心發展
Everything's going my way
唱的真好聽 擊個掌來
That shit was dope. High five.
她唱歌可好了
She's a good singer.
這首歌的歌詞我持保留意見
I don't agree with the sentiment of the song,
但唱得真不錯
but it was really great.
就這樣 在學校一天開心哦
Anyway, have a great day at school.
至少 但願不會太糟糕
Uh... I hope it's not shitty,
還有 給你妹妹 一個吻別吧
and, um, yeah, give your, uh, sister a kiss goodbye.
- 我們從不搞這個   - 你吻就是了
- We don't do that. - Just do it.
怎麼樣 感覺不錯吧
See? Wasn't that nice?
如果她明天就掛了 那你至少你會記得
Now, if she dies tomorrow, you'll remember that,
你吻別過你妹妹了
that you kissed her goodbye.
上學愉快哦
Have a good day at school.
- 拜拜   - 專心學習
- Later, man. - Pay attention.
- 我明天怎麼就掛了呢  - 不知道
- Why would I die? - I don't know.
這種事情你永遠都說不准
You never know what's gonna happen.
你覺得自己是不死之身嗎
Think you're immortal?
這裡 就是這間
This. It's this one.
好的
Okay. All right.
那麼 在學校玩得開心哦
Well, have a good day, okay?
- 好的   - 放學再見 大概吧
- Okay. - I'll see you soon, I guess.
- 請問需要什麼幫助嗎   - 噢 你好啊
- Can-can I help you? - Oh, hi.
我是Ray的朋友
I'm-I'm Ray's friend.
我就是來送她上學的
I was just here to bring her here.
- 你認識Ray嗎   - 大概算認識吧
- You-you know Ray? - I know Ray a little bit.
他最近在勾搭我媽媽
He's kind of, like, banging my mom.
所以 你懂的 嗯
So, yeah, I'm just, you know,
我就把她送過來了
just dropping her off.
你在辦公室那邊登記過嗎
Did you sign in at the office?
沒有 我都不知道還有辦公室
No. I didn't even know you had an office.
好吧
Okay, um...
Kelly 你有什麼問題嗎
Kelly? You okay?
沒有
Yeah.
- 你確定嗎   - 確定
- You sure? - Yeah.
如果有的話你可以告訴我哦
You know you can tell me.
我沒事
I'm okay.
你認識他嗎
Do you know him?
算認識吧
Yeah, kind of.
是個新朋友
He's a new friend.
好的
Okay.
哈 我在車裡教她教得可好了 才不會招供呢
Oh, I trained her in the car. She's not gonna break.
開玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
我是不會傷害她的
It's, uh... I'm not gonna hurt her.
那麼 祝一天愉快 我這就...
Um, but have a great day. I just...
那個 等等 能不能幫忙把畫都擺好
No, uh, actually, could you, uh, set up the paints?
- 不   - 來 來 來
- No. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 還有這些刷子   - 不
- Uh, and just wash these brushes. - No.
- 謝謝你啦   - 不 不
- Thank you so much. - No. No.
- 謝謝   - 不
- Thank you! - No.
不好意思 請問您有沒有看過
Did-did you happen to get a chance
- 我給你的那個   - 哦 看過你的本子了
- to take a look at the, uh... - Yeah, I looked at your book.
我以前也這麼幹過 大概十四歲的時候吧
I mean, I drew like that, too, when I was 14.
從你的本子來看 你還缺少一些基本的東西
From what I saw, you don't really have the basics,
你得再練練
so you got to figure that out.
嗯 所以我才來這裡的
Well, yeah, that's why I'm here.
我希望可以從你這裡學紋身
I mean, I was hoping I can learn from you.
那麼 你就是要做我的學徒咯
Right, well, um, you'd be my apprentice.
你在店裡會和一個奴隸一樣
Uh, you'll be a slave to the shop.
- 沒事的 只要我最後可以給別人紋身   - 不行
- Hey, man. As long as I get to tattoo people, right? - No.
在我允許你紋身之前 不行
Never. Until I say.
你要做的是給針消毒 給我洗車
Uh, you'll be sterilizing needles, washing my car,
幫店裡扔垃圾
taking the trash out.
基本上 就是個店裡的傭人
I mean, you're basically our bitch.
那麼 在這裡打工能掙 大概多少錢呢
So, how much will I be, like, making here?
- 掙個雞巴   - 雞巴
- Dick. - Dick.
好吧
Okay, well...
有很多人想要這份工作呢 老兄
It's a long line of people who want this job, man.
那我怎麼付房租啊
How do I, like, pay my rent?
這就不是我要關心的問題了
That one right there is not my problem.
你第一天來這裡 已經開始抱怨了是吧
It's your first day, you're already complaining.
很奇怪 不是嗎
It's kind of weird, huh?
不然還是算了吧
Yeah, let's not do this.
你還是出去走走吧
You should take a walk.
- 沒種   - 好吧
- Pussy. - All right.
那我能問個問題嗎
Well, could I ask you a question?
假設我在這裡工作
If I did work here?
他怎麼還在這裡
Why is he still here?
比如說吧 有個傻帽來到店裡
Let's say some idiot walks in, right?
他想要紋一個死神在身上 而這個死神呢
And he wants to get a tattoo of a Confederate flag
還披著聯盟國國旗
wrapped around the Grim Reaper.
內戰時美國南部分裂出來的政權
你可以讓那個傻帽滾蛋的是吧
You could tell that guy to go fuck himself, right?
畢竟這麼一個紋身實在是太二了
'Cause that's a ridiculous tattoo to ask for.
我不會去評價別人想紋的圖案
It's not my place to judge people, man.
這不是我該幹的事情
I don't do that.
那如果來了另一個人呢 他走了進來
Well, what if another guy walked in and he wanted to get
想要把他死去的朋友James紋在胸口
a tattoo of his dead friend James on his chest, right?
但是你知道那個James
But you know James, and you don't want
你不想紋這個圖案 因為你知道
to give him the tattoo, 'cause you know James
James是個混賬 世界上少了他
and he's an asshole and that the world's
才算清淨呢
better off without him.
- 那你該怎麼辦   - 你找死嗎
- What do you do then? - You have a death wish?
不 我不想找死
No, I don't have a death wish.
但那位摩托車上的女士有點那意思
But that lady on the motorcycle does.
她連內褲都沒穿一條
She's not even wearing any underwear.
- 下面可是會燒焦的啊   - 你欠揍是吧
- She's gonna burn her pussy. - Do you want to do this?
欠揍就來啊 我來揍你
You really want to fucking do this?
不不不 我不想挨揍
I don't want to do anything with you.
我只想知道James是怎麼死的
I just want to know who killed James.
是那個披著國旗的傢伙幹的嗎
Was it the Confederate flag man?
還是騎摩托的小姐姐干的
Was it the motorcycle lady?
說實話 Kelsey 你和照片上真的是一模一樣
I got to be honest, Kelsey, you look exactly like your picture.
不過更加豐滿一些 更勁爆
You're kind of thicker, more robust.
哈哈哈 謝謝
Oh, thank you.
- 真的   - 瞧你誇的
- Yeah. - It's a compliment.
你看著有點像 安東尼奧·班德拉斯
You look a little bit like Antonio Banderas,
西班牙演員
不過我先得把眼睛瞇起來看
if I squint really hard.
哈哈 那你就瞇著吧
Oh, please squint all night long.
別睜開了
That's great.
真的Chelsea... 不好意思 我是說Kelsey
Chelsea, you are... I mean, Kelsey, I'm sorry.
- 沒事沒事 正常   - 你不介意就好
- Th-That's all right. It's only... - Yeah, you know.
你叫什麼來著
What's your name again?
- 我已經忘了   - 我叫Jake
- I forgot already. - Um, it's Jake.
實在是不好意思
Sorry about that.
你是做什麼的呀
So, uh, w-what do you do?
我在學習如何在城市中工作
Oh, I'm studying to work in the city.
- 哦   - 我想可以
- Oh. - Um, I want to make
讓史泰登島重新成為一個好地方
Staten Island, like, a great place again.
這個島已經很不錯啦 為什麼要這麼做呢
Staten Island's already cool. What are you talking about?
是呀
Yeah, it is.
- 真的挺不錯了   - 你是我見過第一個這麼說的人
- Yeah. Yeah, it is. - You're the first person here to say that.
不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
這可是這個星球上最好的地方了
It's the best place on Earth.
至少在東海岸 是一個不錯的地方吧
Well, at least on the East Coast, I think.
不好意思
Excuse me.
嗨
Oh, hey.
- 嘿   - 你好
- Hey. - Hi.
- 你好   - 嘿
- Hello. - Hey.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你們想要 汽水 還是說沒汽的
Uh, would you guys like, uh, still or sparkling water?
你來選吧
Um, you pick.
我比較喜歡帶汽的
Uh, I'm more of a sparkling guy,
- 那就汽水   - 就汽水吧
- so sparkling. - Sparkling it is.
不過我更喜歡龍舌蘭 所以我能否
But I do like tequila, so if I could
來一瓶培恩 倒在冰塊上
get just a Patron, you know, with a rock.
知名龍舌蘭牌子
- 可以嗎   - 沒問題 可以 沒問題
- That cool with you? - That's fine. Yeah, that's fine.
- 可得嗎 那就好 我比較喜歡龍舌蘭   - 沒問題
- Yeah? Cool. Yeah, I prefer a tequila. - Cool.
龍舌蘭加冰 你們還需要什麼嗎 熱麵包啊
Tequila and rock. You guys want, like, warm bread or...
橄欖油啊
uh, olive oil?
麵包吧
Warm bread.
噢
Oh.
老兄啊 你不會又把一個顧客給嚇跑了吧
Bro, did you scare off another customer?
你怎麼回事啊
What's wrong with you?
真的很不好意思
I'm so sorry about that.
他是有人介紹開後門進來的
He has, like, nepotism, you know?
是什麼病
Is that a disease?
是一種很壞的病
Yeah, it's a bad one.
我帶個人過來就是想讓你吃醋
I brought that guy here to make you jealous.
好氣氣你
You could give a fuck.
讓我吃醋啊
T-To make me jea...
- 你一點都不吃醋 也不生氣   - 我在乎啊
- You don't seem jealous or upset at all. - I do care.
我當然在乎啊
Of course I care.
我在Tinder上找了一個最帥的男人
I chose the hottest guy on Tinder.
你看看我 看看我
Look at me. Look at me.
看看我的胸
Look at my tits.
都和埃菲爾鐵塔差不多了
There is literally the Eiffel Tower...
就拖在這裡
it's holding them up in here.
你看著很漂亮
You look great. I'm...
謝謝你啊
Thank you.
請別在這裡哭了 求你了
Please don't cry here. Please.
你看著太糟糕了
You look awful.
啥 啥意思 什麼糟糕不糟糕的
What? What do you mean? What are you...
你的皮都快透光了 還有你那黑眼圈
Your skin looks see-through and the circles around your eyes
看著就和一隻厭食的熊貓似的
are so dark you look like an anorexic panda.
唉 我知道
I... Well, I-I know.
我知道
I know I do.
你總是看著病怏怏的 皮膚蒼白得和得了病一樣
You always look sick and pale like you have a disease
你自己是不知道 但你現在看上去
but you don't know it yet, but you literally look like
好像我輕輕碰你一下你就要灰飛煙滅了一樣
if I touched you, you'd just turn to dust.
對不起 我最近過得不是很好
I'm sorry. I-I'm not doing very well.
我真的 你懂的 我
I-I'm not, you know... I...
那我怎麼和你約會的對象解釋啊
Well, what do I tell your date?
你問我啊 讓他滾蛋啊
I don't know. Tell him to fuck off.
我就剛認識他十分鐘 是個做DJ的
I met him ten minutes ago. He's a DJ.
你為啥覺得控冰就不能是一種牛逼的超能力呢
Why do you not think ice is a good superpower?
牛逼壞了好嘛
It's amazing. I mean...
閃冰俠的冰是無所不能的
Ice Flash can do anything with his ice.
而且堅不可摧
And it's indestructible
那可是超級英雄的冰啊
'cause it's superhero ice.
他可以用冰做一個反射一切的大盾牌
He can make giant shields that reflect anything.
可以製造一個巨大的冰坦克
He can make giant ice tanks,
還有大號的冰飛機
giant ice planes and giant jets,
還有發射大導彈的直升機
helicopters that shoot giant missiles.
想想就激動啊 什麼都能變
I mean, think of all the possibilities.
這麼一說的確挺厲害
That's actually kind of cool.
- 謝謝   - 都是你自己想出來的嗎
- Thanks.   - You came up with that?
是的
Yeah.
你越來越厲害了呢
You're getting, like, really good at this.
謝謝
Thanks.
他的盾牌是什麼顏色的
What color is his shield?
呃 是冰的顏色
It's, well, the color of ice.
那冰的顏色是什麼樣的顏色呢 透光的那種嗎
Well, what's the color of ice? Is it, like, see-through?
比如淡藍的 還是說
Like, light blue ice or is it like...?
是藍的 因為
It's blue ice 'cause it's...
- 就像是超級英雄的冰 超厲害   - 好的
- it's, like, superhero ice, and it's cool. - Right.
Ronnie 還記得那個孩子嗎
You remember that kid Ronnie?
他舅舅開藥店的那個
His uncle owns the pharmacy.
他給了我鑰匙 我們馬上就要滿載而歸了
He gave me the key. We're gonna load up on oxys.
所以從今往後我們就做起搶匪了嗎
So, we're robbers now. That's our future.
不不不不 就這麼一次嘛
Nah. Nah, nah, nah, nah. We're gonna do this one time.
干他一票 才能夢想成真
Get the money to seed our dreams.
才能有啟動資金
Get that venture capital.
才能開一家你想要的紋身餐廳
Open that tattoo restaurant you wanted.
這也沒什麼 Jay-Z 也這麼做的
It's not that big a deal. Jay-Z did it.
他就是通過賣白面才有錢搞Rap的
He sold crack to fund his rap career.
但是Jay-Z的朋友基本上 不是死了就是在蹲大牢吧
Aren't most of Jay-Z's friends, like, dead or in jail?
沒錯 但在這次行動中 我們是Jay-Z
Yeah, but we're Jay-Z in this situation.
而不是Jay-Z的朋友
We're not Jay-Z's friends.
但Jay-Z只有一個啊
We can't all be Jay-Z.
不可能有四個Jay-Z吧 這不合理啊
There can't be four Jay-Zs. That doesn't make any sense.
你們知道的吧 我可以為你們赴湯蹈火
You guys know I'd do anything for you, right?
謝謝
Thank you.
- 謝謝   - 但這事兒不行 我不幹
- Appreciate you. - Just not this. I'm out.
你在說什麼呢
What are you talking about?
- 你說什麼   - 這太瘋狂了
- What? - This is crazy.
嘿 我們不能沒有你 你可是在外面放哨的啊
Hey, we need you, all right? You're the lookout.
放哨誰不能放啊
Literally anybody can be the lookout.
- 我不想參與到這種事情裡來   - 不 不 不 不
- I don't need to be a part of this. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
我們需要你 你是我們最好的朋友
We need you. You're our best friend.
- 我們信任你   - 啥
- We trust you. - Wha...
但是 好朋友是不會讓他的好朋友
Well, best friends don't make other best friends
去做違法亂紀的蠢事的
do stupid illegal shit.
你讓我幹的蠢事還不夠多嗎
You make me do stupid shit for you all the time.
- 比如說  - 我想想啊
- Like what? - Uh, I don't know.
記得有一次你以為你
What about the time when you thought
- 得睪丸癌了嗎   - 又來了
- you had testicular cancer? - Here we go.
- 我就知道又是這事情   - 是的吧
- Knew this was gonna come up. - All right?
我大老遠開車過來 然後你讓我摸你蛋蛋
And then I drive over and you make me touch your nuts.
換了我我也會為你這麼做啊
I would've done it for you, bro.
如果你說 艾瑪我的屁股好像有什麼問題
You're like, "Hey, yo, there's something wrong with my ass."
- 那我也會說 來 彎腰脫褲子   - 得了吧
- I'd be like, "Yo, bend over." - Come on.
我們為你做了這麼多事
After everything we've done for you?
你能為我做些什麼呢
What do you do for me?
我讓你把我全身都紋了一遍
I let you tattoo my whole body.
所以呢 你不是很喜歡嗎
So what? You love my tattoos.
你把我當做了人肉筆記本
You use me as a human sketchbook.
我是真 真的 不那麼
I-I-I-I don't, really.
沒有我嘴上說的那麼喜歡這紋身
I don't. Not as much as I say I do.
我不幹 對不起
I'm out of here. My bad.
你啊 你
You know what?
就是個賤人
You're a real bitch!
- 大賤人   - 噓
- You're a bitch! - Shh.
噓你個頭啊 噓
Yo, don't shush me.
-噢  - 天啊 看她這是有多興奮
- Oh.  - My God, look how excited she is.
-我認為肯定是她 -我已經興奮得飛起來
- I'm assuming that's her. - I started running too early!
嗨
Hey! Oh.
噢 你這也太纖瘦了
Oh, oh, oh, you're so skinny.
-一直都有進食嗎？ -是呀
- Have you been eating? - Yeah.
-嗨 -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
你好嗎？
How are you?
這是Ray
This is Ray.
-嗨 -你好嗎？-噢
- Hey. How you doing? - Oh.
-很高興我們最終還是見面了 -很高興見到你
- Nice to finally meet you. - Nice to meet you.
我覺得我已經很瞭解你了
Yeah, I feel like I already know you.
你母親時常提起你
Your mom talks about you all the time.
-噢 是嘛 -哦
- Oh, God. - Oh.
不 僅提及你的優點 真的只是你的優點
No, only good stuff, only good stuff.
我們可以去吃點什麼嗎 我沒法再吃飯堂了
Should we go eat? I am so sick of eating off a tray.
- 你餓嗎？ -好 我也可以吃
- You hungry? - Yeah, I could eat.
隨時都能吃
Could always eat.
學校很漂亮
Beautiful school.
「好呀 我也想吃 我可以隨時吃」
"Yeah, I could eat. I could always eat."
該死的混蛋
Fucking asshole.
看這兩位小天使
Look at those two angels, huh?
- 是呀 我認識他們  - 對呀
- Yeah, I know them. - Yeah.
- 嗯 - 你送他們上學不是嗎
- Mm-hmm. - You walk them to school, don't you?
- 是 我知道他們是誰  - 噢 天哪
- Yeah, I know who they are. - Oh, my God.
- 她也太可愛了吧 - 看這卷髮
- She's so cute. - Look. Look at those curls.
我曾帶他們去百老匯看破銅爛鐵
We took them to see Stomp Off-Broadway.
- 他們好高興啊 -噢 天啊
- They went crazy! - Oh, my God.
我超愛破銅爛鐵
I love Stomp.
破銅爛鐵是什麼 那是什麼
What's Stomp? What is that?
它一直歷史上最棒的音樂劇
It's the greatest musical of all time.
是的 在這個劇中演員們表演敲打 比如敲打垃圾桶
Yeah, it's, like, that show where people play the drums on, like, garbage cans
再比如敲掃帚
and, like, tap with broomsticks.
- 敲打家裡用的東西 - 是的
- Stuff around the house. - Yeah.
我們只覺得烤爐可做英式瑪芬
Like, you just see a toaster, we make an English muffin.
他們可以用烤爐敲打出音樂 真不可思議
They-they see a whole song. It's incredible.
據我所知流浪漢靠在地鐵裡敲打垃圾桶的蓋子來索要
I know a homeless guy that plays trash can lids on the subway, for a dollar.
然後在站台上拉屎
And then he took a shit on the platform.
噢 好吧
Oh. Well, you know.
也不知道他能不能獲個托尼獎什麼的
I don't know if he's gonna get a Tony for that, but...
音樂劇最高殊榮
也許他們不斷的練習說不定哪天可以帶著成人尿布
Maybe if they keep practicing and get an adult diaper,
去百腦匯表演
they can, uh, get to Broadway someday.
好吧
Yeah.
你們的感情是認真的嗎
So, are you guys really serious?
噢
Uh-oh.
是這樣的
Well, actually,
我打算在今年的感恩節去波士頓見見他的父母
I'm going up to Boston to meet his parents at Thanksgiving.
- 哦  - 什麼 你要在感恩節的時候去波士頓...
- Oh. - What? You're going to Boston to...for Thanksgiving? To wha...
好吧 那我去哪呀
Well, where-where am I gonna go?
- 你也可以和我一起 一起去 - 是呀 我怎麼辦
- Ah, you'll come. You can come. - Yeah, me, too.
-我們也可以去的 -是呀 我們很樂意你們也去 -噢
-We can all go. - Yeah, we'd love to have you up there. - Oh.
你覺得你會再婚嗎
You think you're gonna get married again?
噢 天啊 我這搞得讓我們有點尷尬
Oh, boy, look what I got us into.
Claire
Claire.
好吧 這個 我來
Well, you know what? I'll...
我來回答這個
I'll, uh, I'll answer that, you know?
幾個月前 我可能會不想結婚 但
A couple of months ago, I would've said no, but...
嗯 我們能走了嗎
Uh, can we go?
Scott
Scott.
別這麼沒禮貌
Don't be rude.
我嘛 我不覺得我沒禮貌
Me? I'm not being rude.
他一直都在叨逼叨
He's talking the entire time.
他才是沒有禮貌的那個
Wha... He's the one being rude.
僅是聊天而已
Was just making conversation.
好吧 那你覺得我還可以說些什麼
Okay, so what did you want to say?
- 別扯了 - 現在你想怎樣
-Cut this shit. - Tell us now.
我想說我覺得我們是時候該離開了 怎麼樣
All I wanted to say was I think it's time to go, okay?
我很開心 簡直太讚了
I had a great time. This is wonderful.
我認識我們已經情感交流過了
I think we all bonded.
是時候該離開了 好嗎
It's time to leave now, all right?
好吧 我們稍後會去個派對
Well, we're going to a party later,
你可以和我們一起
if you want to come with us.
你不能再讓我難堪了
You just can't embarrass me.
好吧 無所謂了 讓我們他媽趕緊離開這
Sure, whatever. Let's just get the fuck out of here.
他情緒不錯啊
He's in a good mood.
試著你這輩子都哄著他
Try doing it your entire life.
今晚我們會玩得很開心的
We're gonna have a good night.
不 我們不會的 我很討厭大學派對
No, we're not. I hate college parties.
你可是從來都沒有來過大學派對的
You've never been to a college party.
好了 放飛自我
Come on, just enjoy it.
-放輕鬆 投入進去 -對的 放輕鬆
-Relax. Go with it, okay? - Yes, relax.
你修什麼專業
What's your major?
是 嗯 嗯 社會進化學
It's, uh, uh, evolutionary sociology
與生物學有點關係
with-with a splash of bio.
哦 我覺得這個不太可能
Oh. I-I didn't know you could do that.
你可以想特麼幹什麼就幹什麼 這可是大學
Yeah, you can do whatever the fuck you want. It's college.
我喜歡你的紋身
I like your tattoos.
我是個演員 所以我不覺得
I'm an actress, so, like, I don't think
我能紋許多處紋身 因為 比如
I can get that many tattoos, because, like,
如果我有個試鏡 白蓮花角色
what if I get cast as, like, an angelic role?
我感覺自己就是一個 年輕版的薇諾娜·瑞德
Like, I'm kind of, like, a young Winona Ryder.
我也可以演那些角色 而且啊就是
So, like, I could play those parts, and, like, also, like,
在莎士比亞寫戲劇的時候
back when Shakespeare was writing plays, like...
- 你覺得如何？ - 這是什麼呀？
- What do you think? - What is that?
菊花
It's a butthole.
-懂嗎？ -我的天啊
- Get it? - Oh, my God.
-嗯 -我們在談論為什麼百分之一的人口
- Uh-huh. - So, we're talking about how the one percent
越來越富有
keeps, like, getting bigger and bigger and bigger,
貧富懸殊越來越嚴重
and the wealth inequality is just out of control,
而我們不能再繼續以這種方式走資本主義道路
and we can't continue with capitalism this way.
是的 我已經厭煩了這種無意義的競爭
Yeah, I'm s... I'm sick of the rat race.
是這樣的
Yeah, no, exactly.
美國夢都變成什麼樣了
Like, what happened to the American dream?
據我所知 現在已經是美國噩夢了
I know. It's like an American nightmare now.
- 哦天 是 - 是吧
- Oh, my... Yeah, exa... - Right?
-拿過來 太爽了 -哇 爽
- Bring it... Oh, shit! - Oh! Oh, shit!
哇 爽
Oh, shit!
太特麼爽了
That was fucking fun.
我當然知道 很爽
I know. It was so fun.
是呀 我覺得
Yeah, like, I feel like,
我覺得我頭一次可以這般融入進去
I feel like I kind of fit in for once, you know?
第一次感受到不是所有人都討厭我
And not everybody hated me for the first time.
你可以常來呀
You should come here.
是嗎 你覺得我有機會可以進入到這樣的一個地方嗎
Yeah? You think I can get into a place like this?
我的意思是 你僅需要高分的成績
I mean, you'd need a good GPA.
好吧 我可沒有考過高分
Yeah, well, I don't have a good one of those.
我甚至高中都沒畢業
I-I didn't even graduate high school.
不是得高中畢業才可以讀大學嗎
Don't you have to graduate high school to go to college?
是的 不過現在著手去做為時不晚
Yeah, but it's not, like, too late to do that.
好吧 儘管這樣 我還是覺得自己年紀有些大
All right, even so, you know, I-I'm a little too old.
你懂嗎 我看起來就像個緝毒警察
I'd look like a narc, you know?
在角落裡一呆很異類
I would look creepy in the corner.
每個人都覺得 「這傢伙在這幹嘛」
Everybody'd be like, "What's that guy doing here?"
這裡的每個人年紀都不小
Everybody here is so old.
好吧 我就是個傻逼 好嗎 Claire
All right, well, I'm fucking stupid, Claire, okay?
你想讓我這樣說嗎
Is that what you want me to say?
我無法集中精力 我無法安靜的坐著 好吧
I can't pay attention. I can't sit still, okay?
我是個煞筆 我是個蠢貨
I'm stupid. I'm a dumb idiot.
我還得比其他人努力十倍
I would have to work ten times harder than those people.
然後還他媽被嘲笑
And everybody would fucking make fun of me,
我可不想再嘗試一次 所以 不想
and I'm not ready to deal with that again, all right? So, no.
所以 就這樣嘛
So, that's it?
啊
Huh?
這就是你在思考上大學這件事上
That's how long you're gonna think about
花的所有時間嗎
going to college for?
這已經是 40秒步行了
I mean, that was, like, a 40-second walk.
已經思考了很久了 你不覺得嗎
Uh, that's a lot of consideration, don't you think?
好吧
Okay.
- 是你的道路 - 那是
- It's your journey. - Indeed.
好了 現在 我們進入正題
Now, let's get down to brass tacks, all right?
關於Ray的出現我們該怎麼辦
W-What are we gonna do about Ray?
- 什麼意思  - 別裝傻
- What do you mean? - Don't act stupid.
我的意思是 我們該怎麼做
I mean, h-how are we gonna, you know,
使他跟老媽分手
get Mom to break up with him?
我覺得他不錯
I think he seems fine.
- 你覺得他不錯  - 你有什麼想法
- You think he's fine? - What do you want?
那是老媽的選擇 我們無權過問
It's Mom's choice to make. We don't need to get involved.
好 我知道 但我們仍需要保護她
Yeah, I know, but we should still protect her.
她不能就這樣繼老爸後
She can't just be with
下一個男人就隨便好上了
the first guy she's been with since Dad.
她該貨比三家
She got to, like, peruse some dick.
老媽不需要挑選老二
Mom doesn't need to peruse dick.
- 你知道她需要的 - 我覺得老媽很開心
- You know she needs to. - I think she seems happy.
你想讓她跟很多人上床嗎
You want her to have sex with a ton of people?
不 但 也許吧
No, but, yeah, kind of.
- 我的意思是... - 真噁心
- I mean... - That's gross.
可是 如果你知道在最開始的時候 情形會往壞處發展
Well, if you knew something was bad before it even started,
假設你有機會去阻止 難道你不會去阻止嗎
wouldn't you stop it if you had the chance?
就像把希特勒扼殺在搖籃中一樣 你懂的
It's like that whole baby Hitler thing, you know?
如果你有機會在希特勒長大前 殺掉搖籃中的希特勒
If you had the chance to kill baby Hitler before it grew up,
你會去做嗎
you do it?
你難道不會扼制它 讓它完全完全死掉
Wouldn't you strangle it until its eyes popped out?
所以 Ray是嬰兒希特勒嗎
So, Ray's baby Hitler?
是呀 在這個情況裡 他就是
Yeah. In this situation, he is, yeah.
他就是嬰兒希特勒
He's baby Hitler.
你想幫我殺了這個嬰兒希特勒嗎
So, do you want to help me kill baby Hitler?
好吧 你全對 Scott 你全對
Okay, you're right, Scott. You're right.
- 明天見 - Claire
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Claire!
Claire
Claire!
告訴你 Claire是真的
Tell you, Claire really seems like
很喜歡大學生活
she's enjoying school, you know?
是呀
Yeah.
她正當年呀
She's just blossoming.
是呀
Yeah.
她似乎覺得她可以擁有這個世界
Girl just seems like she could take on the world.
我和你講
I'll tell you,
無論你之前怎樣培養過她 你做的太讚了
whatever you did with her, you did it right.
也可以培養下Scott
Dump some of that on Scott, you know?
你覺得他的紋身餐廳的想法如何
What do you think about his tattoo restaurant idea?
我覺得不怎麼樣
I think it's terrible.
紋身就像一個醫療療程
Getting a tattoo is like, uh... it's a medical procedure.
你肯定不想看著病
You don't want to go to the hospital
吃著晚飯
and order supper, you know?
我就是欣賞他有遠大的理想 不過他也太迷茫了
I just love that he has big dreams, but he's just so lost.
無論我怎麼努力給他輸入正能量 他就是
I mean, no matter how much I try to fill him with good energy, he just...
他毫無自信
he's got no self-esteem.
他的前途可堪呀
He's really going nowhere.
別這樣責備自己
Don't be so hard on yourself.
科學家們從事這類研究很久
Scientists have been doing studies.
他們覺得很多東西都是來自遺傳
They say a lot of this stuff is genetic.
你從你的祖父母們繼承了這個
You know, you inherit it from your grandparents.
所以責任歸於他們
So blame them.
我們走
Let's go.
如果有人看見我們
Right. If anybody sees us
或者你聽見警笛再或者情況不妙 你給我傳信息「你醒著嗎」
or you hear sirens or anything bad, you text me, "You up?"
我可以發些其他的東西給你嗎？
Could I just text you something else?
這個感覺有點像我找你約炮...
That sounds like I'm trying to bang you, kind of.
- 按照我說的做 - 好吧
- Just do it. - Fine.
- 好吧  - 我們走
- Fine.  - Let's go.
- 我們出發 - 等一下
- Let's roll. - Hold on.
好 我們出發
All right, let's go.
一切順利 兄弟
Good luck, homey.
愛你 Scott
Love you, Scott.
我去
Oh, shit.
玩真的
This is real.
太讚了
Yes! All right.
你死定了
You're dead.
你在幹嘛
What's going on?!
臥槽
What the fuck?
- 你誰呀  - 你不該在這的
- Who are you?! - You're not supposed to be here.
你在說什麼 這是我的店
What are you talking about?! It's my store!
你在和誰講話
Who are you talking to?
- 他是誰呀  - 快進屋
- Who is that?! - Go back inside.
- 快進屋 - 什麼 不需要你告訴我進屋
- Go back inside! - What? Don't tell me to go back inside!
我來解決這事
I'm handling this!
不錯 不行 不錯
Yes. No. Yes.
不行 不錯 不錯 不行
No. Yes. Yes. No.
趕快從我的店裡滾出去
Get the fuck out of my store!
- 我不想傷害你  - 滾出去
- I just don't want to hurt you, okay?  - Get out!
- 我只是... - 不能再容忍你們這樣了
- I just...  - You're not doing this again, okay?!
- 這已經是第三次了 - 你們夠了
- This is the third time! - Enough of you guys!
- 一年裡三次  - 媽蛋的
- Third time this year! - Shit! Shit!
- 滾出去 - 搞什麼
- Get out! - What the hell?
- 放開我 - 今天絕對不行
- Get off me! - Not today!
今天絕對不行 今天是Alan Moskowitz的反抗日
Not today! Today is Alan Moskowitz's day!
所製作的電影多為人類反抗電影
這個漂亮的妹妹是誰
Well, who's the pretty lady?
嗨 安吉麗娜朱莉
Hello, Angelina Jolie.
- 這怎麼鎖了  - 鑰匙在哪
- Yo, it's locked! - Where are the keys?
我們都把鑰匙放在櫃檯
We left the keys on the counter.
為什麼你把門鎖了
Why'd you lock the door?
那是我不想讓其他人進來
Because I didn't want anybody to come in, man.
不能再容忍你們這樣對我了
You're not gonna do this to me again!
絕不可以在我的店裡再有這種事
Not in my store!
- 我們可從來沒來過這呀 - 媽蛋的
-We've never been here before! -Shit!
我絕不輕饒
I'm standing my ground!
臥槽
Fuck.
靠
Shit!
你醒著呢嗎 你醒著呢嗎 你醒著呢嗎
"You up? You up? You up?"
- 現在怎麼辦  - 別出聲 別出聲
-What's happening? -Be quiet. Be quiet.
別出聲 別出聲
Be quiet. Be quiet.
想約炮嗎 想約炮嗎 想約炮嗎 想約炮嗎
"Want to fuck? Want to fuck? Want to fuck? Want to fuck?"
想約炮嗎
"Do you want to fuck?
想約炮嗎 想約炮嗎
Do you want to fuck? Do you want to fuck?
好吧 Igor
Okay, right, Igor.
接電話 Igor
Answer the phone, Igor.
快接呀 快接呀 快接呀
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
不 不 不
No. No. No. No. No.
Scott
Scott.
快點關掉
Shut off your ringers!
該死的
Goddamn it.
嗨 Oscar 我是Scott
Hey, Oscar, it's, uh, Scott.
我很想知道
I was just, uh, wondering if, uh, you know,
你那事幹完了嘛
you're almost done with that thing.
我們需要鑰匙
We need those keys.
臥槽
Fuck that!
靠
Holy shit!
快點 Igor 快點
Come on, Igor! Come on! Come on!
賊在裡面
Um, the robbers are inside!
舉起手來
Hands in the air!
店裡那個女人有槍
The lady inside's got a gun.
趴在地上
Get down on the ground!
別動
Do not move!
為什麼你們要搶劫藥店
Why would you rob a pharmacy?
我沒有在搶劫藥店
I wasn't robbing a pharmacy, okay?
我只是個望風的
I was the lookout, for your information.
望風也是犯罪
The lookout is also committing a crime.
你腦子進水了嗎
Are you fucking crazy?
聽著 這都是Ray的錯
Look, it's all Ray's fault, okay?
他想踢我出局
He's trying to kick me out.
我慌了然後做了個錯誤的決定
So I panicked and made a bad decision, okay?
我也是個人
I'm only human!
錯誤的決定 這可是重罪
A bad decision? That's a felony.
那又怎樣
Yeah, so?
我根本就沒進去
I didn't even, I didn't even go inside, all right?
我與此事無關
Uh, it's not...I'm untouchable.
我什麼都沒做
I didn't do anything, all right?
都是Ray的錯
Uh, i-it's Ray, okay?
我知道他心存不軌
He... I-I know he's up to something.
- 他就是想抹去老爸的存在 - 你就不想讓老媽幸福生活嗎
- He's trying to erase Dad. - Can you just let Mom be happy?
老媽很幸福
She is happy.
只要她離開那個人 老媽會幸福的
Well, she will be, you know, once I get rid of that guy.
他心存不軌 他心存不軌
He's hiding shit, okay? He's hiding shit.
他就是個黃鼠狼 我已經發現他了
He's a weasel. I-I'm onto him.
這就是你為什麼不想離家的原因
This is why I didn't want to leave,
你把你的神經質都放在了老媽身上
cause now all your crazy's focused on Mom.
我沒做什麼神經質的事
I'm not doing anything crazy, okay?
什麼都不做才是神經質 我現在要做些什麼
Doing nothing would be crazy. I'm doing something, okay?
我要採取行動
I'm taking action!
別去騷擾老媽 別再想你這樣了
Leave Mom alone. Stop acting like you.
什麼意思
What's that mean?!
你毀掉了我的萬聖節派對
You ruined my Halloween party.
我明知故問
You know, you know what? You know what?
去好好享受你的派對 我瞭解了
Go enjoy your party. I-I got this.
你不瞭解 別做蠢事
You don't got this. Don't do anything.
我瞭解了
I got this.
什麼事也別做
Don't do anything!
嗨 Scott 有事嗎
Hey, Scott. What's up?
- 哦 嗨  - 嗨
- Oh, hi.  - Hi.
我就是過來看看孩子們
I, uh... I just came by to say hi to the kids.
他們在嗎
Are-are they around?
噢
Oh.
他們不在家
Well, they're not here.
他們去了他們的奶奶家
They went to their grandma's.
哦
Oh.
你在幹嘛呢
Well, what do you got going on over there?
我在開這瓶紅酒
I'm trying to open this bottle of wine,
不過我把這木塞搞壞了
but I think I mangled the cork.
我可以幫忙 想讓我幫把手嗎
Oh, well, I could help. You want me to help?
好呀
Yes. Yes.
來吧
Please.
- 耶  - 好棒
- Yeah!  - Yes.
你有好朋友來拜訪嗎？
So, uh, do you have a friend coming over or something?
不
Oh, no.
不 我自己小酌下
No, I just need some mommy time.
當孩子們不在的時候 媽媽們需要小酌下的
Sometimes, mommies need to drink when the kids are away.
我可以一起嗎
Oh, well, could I hang?
我也想小酌下
I-I could use some mommy time.
當然可以 不過你到了可以飲酒的年齡了嗎
Sure, but are you old enough to drink?
當然 我已經到了可飲酒的年齡 我還想吸點
Yeah, I'm old enough. I just... I'd rather smoke.
不介意我在這吸大麻吧
Do you mind if I smoke in here?
不介意
Oh, no. No.
門窗都打開
Let's crack some windows.
- 今天可是週二  - 確定嗎？
- It's Tuesday.  - Really?
Ray討厭我吸大麻
Cause Ray hates when I smoke weed.
我討厭Ray
Mm. Well, I hate Ray.
太讚了
Awesome.
- 嗯 - 你知道嘛...
- Mm. - You know...
你的孩子是我見過
You have the sweetest,
最討喜最可愛的
most adorable kids I've ever met in my life.
我簡直不敢相信是Ray的孩子
Like, I can't believe they came out of Ray.
我懂
I know.
你知道嗎
And you know what?
關於Ray
You know what the thing is about Ray?
我從來沒在孩子們的面前說過他的一句壞話
I never say a bad word about him in front of the kids,
做這事超級難的 因為他就是個混蛋
which is very difficult because he's a cunt.
是的 我可以想像
Yeah, I-I can imagine.
我不是他的孩子 所以來說他的壞話吧
Well, I'm not one of your kids, so have at it.
都說出來吧 都告訴我
Let it all out. Tell me everything.
你知道嘛 他在法庭上
Do you know he is fighting to
爭取放棄撫養權
actively not have custody of his kids?
- 還有這種操作嗎  - 是呀
- You can do that? - Yeah.
- 簡直不可想像 - 我懂
- That's insane. - I know.
居然有人不想和你的孩子在一起
Who wouldn't want to hang with your kids?
誰不想跟那些孩子們一起玩啊
Who wouldn't want to hang out with those kids?
什麼樣的怪物會不想跟那些孩子們一起玩啊
What monster wouldn't want to hang out with those kids?
每一秒都那麼美好
Every second!
你姑娘那天唱了首歌
Your daughter sang the other day.
她唱了啥
What did she sing?
俄克拉荷馬裡的什麼吧
Something from, like, Oklahoma! or something,
雖然我討厭那破玩意 但是我他媽的愛死她的歌聲了
and-and I hate that shit, and I fucking loved it.
她真是個小天使
She's such a little angel.
- 嗯  - 我還以為她是個機器人什麼的
- Mm.  - I-I thought she was a robot for, like,
最初跟她玩的那幾天的時候
the first couple days I was hanging out with her.
我說吧  她真的好完美啊
I know. She's so perfect.
什麼品種的傻逼啊
What a fucking putz.
嗯 所以他只想在
Yeah, so he only wants to see them
週三晚飯和週日的時候探望他們
on Wednesday night for dinner and Sunday.
- 你不能這樣隨便挑的  - 還有
-  You can't just pick and choose.  - And, uh...
對啊 你不能挑的
No, you can't.
把孩子當什麼了 橄欖球季票麼
What are your kids, the NFL package?
- 等等 對啊  - 對吧
- Wait, you're only... Yeah.  - Yeah.
不過你也不會想要孩子的監護權的
But why would you want your kids, really·,
尤其現在你連自己的住所都沒有還睡在消防隊裡
if you don't have an apartment and you sleep at the firehouse?
就是
I mean, you...
無法理喻
Unbelievable.
什麼樣的成年男人
What kind of a grown man
在史泰登島住不起自己的屋子
can't afford his own apartment in Staten Island?
真他媽廢物
Fucking loser.
他把我們所有的錢都賭輸了
He lost all our money gambling.
他無家可歸 身無分文 還是個不負責的孩子爹
He is homeless, he's penniless, and he's a deadbeat dad.
你媽為啥跟他在一起啊
What is your mom doing with him?
你懂得 我媽17年都沒對象
You know, my mom hasn't gotten laid in 17 years,
所以我覺得她的標準相當低了
so I think her bar is pretty low.
真的  好吧
Really? Yeah.
雖然不想承認 但是他床上倒是真不錯
He's good in bed, I hate to say it.
好吧
All right.
好吧 我倒不是真的需要知道這事
Well, I didn't really need to know that.
嗯啊
Yeah.
他有個漂亮的雞巴
He's got a beautiful cock.
這是 他唯一的優點了
I mean, it's the... it's his only attribute.
那個大粗雞巴讓我
That big thick cock kept me in it
多跟了他8年
for eight years longer than I should have stayed.
這是事實
It's a fact.
我就知道我能聞出來
I knew I smelled you.
- Scott你搞什麼鬼  - 啥
- The fuck, Scott?  - What?
啥  你現在開始監視我了嗎
Huh? What, are you spying on me now?
- 你是夏威夷神探嗎  - 啥
- You Magnum, P.I.?  - What?
跟你媽說我無家可歸
Telling your mom that I'm homeless?
說我是個廢物 你覺得很搞笑麼
You think it's funny to tell her that I'm a loser?
你在說啥 不搞笑啊 啥啊
What are you talking... No. What?
什麼叫我在說啥
What do you mean, what am I talking about?
你跟那誰  你去找我前妻嘮嗑去了
You've been speak... You talking to my ex-wife?
呃 是啊  她其實是個很好的人啊
Uh, yeah. She's actually a really nice person.
- 哦 是嗎  那你咋不娶她啊  - 啊
- Oh, is she? Why don't you marry her?  - Yeah.
你咋不娶了她再看看會發生啥
Why don't you marry her and see what the fuck happens?
嘿 我只是想保護我媽不被你傷害 好吧
Hey, I'm just trying to protect my mom from you, okay?
你他媽是個神經病
You're a fucking psychopath.
- 哦 我是神經病  - 是
- Oh, I'm a psychopath?  - Yeah.
我對你簡直是不能再好了
I've been nothing but nice to you!
我努力指引你
I tried giving you direction.
然而你卻一直他媽的忙著飛你的葉子
You're too busy smoking your fucking weed.
你除了一直在迫害我
And all you've been doing is trying to destroy
和Margie的感情以外沒有幹別的
everything that I have with Margie.
因為你他媽的是個廢物啊 弟弟
Because you're a fucking loser, dude!
你是 你是個無可救藥的賭徒
You're a, you're a degenerate gambler
你都 你都50多了 還壓在噴氣機隊上
in your-your mid-50s, who bets on the Jets.
呃 你難道這麼多年賭出來不長記性麼
Uh, who... Have you not learned anything about betting?
- 噴氣機隊會贏回來的  - 不 不可能的
- The Jets are gonna come back!  - No, they're not!
他們挑了三個種子選手
They got three number one fucking picks!
他們永遠贏不回來的  他們永遠贏不回來的
They're never gonna come back! They're never gonna come back!
我在努力給你媽一個好的生活
I'm trying to give your mother a good life!
我 沒 你沒有好吧  你就是坨屎 弟弟
I... No, you're not, okay? You're a piece of shit, dude.
你他媽吸毒上癮 然而我是屎
You're a fucking drug addict! I'm a piece of shit?
是啊 你就是坨屎  我是他媽廢物
Yeah, you're a piece of shit! I'm a fucking loser?
你是我這輩子他媽的碰到的最大的廢物
You're the biggest loser I ever met in my fucking life!
- 哦 這樣  果然你最懂啊  - 是的就這樣
- Oh, really? You should know.  - Yeah! Yeah!
因為你身邊都是這種人
You surround yourself with them.
- 哦 真的  你來啊  - 哦真的
- Oh, yeah? Why don't you try me?  - Oh, really?
你來啊 來啊 來啊 來啊
Why don't you try me? Yeah, yeah, yeah...
那接下來可不會按你想像的一樣的
This ain't gonna go how you think it's gonna go.
所以你最好從我眼前  靠玩真的
So why don't you get the fuck out of my... Really?
- 操你大爺  - 你他媽敢打我
- Fucking asshole.  - Throw a fucking punch at me?
- 就敢打  - 啥  你能不能冷靜一下
- Oh, yeah.  - Huh? You gonna cool off?
- 過來啊你個混蛋  - 你能不能冷靜一下
- Come here, cocksucker.  - You gonna cool off?
我他媽的幫你冷靜冷靜
I'll fucking cool you off.
Yeah, I'll fucking cool you off!
嘿 你現在冷靜下來了
Hey, you cool off now?
這可是你自找的
You're in there 'cause of your own actions!
你在逗我嗎
Are you kidding me?!
我要告訴我媽你要淹死我
I'm gonna tell my mom you tried to drown me.
在這種小破水池子裡
In an aboveground pool?
你他媽至少2米4好吧
You're, like, fucking eight feet tall.
我爸不在這你算是撿著了 他非打死你不可
You're lucky my dad isn't here. He would kick your ass.
噢 真的麼 你猜怎麼著 我認識你爹  好吧
Oh, yeah? Well, guess what, I knew your dad. Okay?
- 所以呢  - 所以我見過他幾次
- Yeah?  - Yeah, I crossed paths with him a number of times.
你猜怎麼著  他比你還混球
And you know what? He was even a bigger asshole than you are!
好了 就這樣吧 停下
All right, that's it, that's it.
你贏不了 別打了
It's over. It's over.
你想這樣嗎  你想這樣嗎
You like that? You like that?
- 天啊  - 你大爺的
- Jesus.  - Fucking asshole.
好啦 認輸吧 認輸吧
Come on, tap out! Tap out!
- 操你大爺的  就不  - 放開我  放開我
- Fuck you! No!  - Get me out! Let me out!
- 不 就不  - 放開我
- No! No!  - Let me out!
- 我的天啊  - 放開我
- Oh, my God!  - Get me out!
你倆什麼毛病啊
What's the matter with you?!
他是神經病
He's a psycho.
不是
No.
- 我們就是在聊天  - 聊啥啊
- We're just talking.  - About what?
- 他跟你說的那些關於我的假話  - 他就是個畜生
- About him telling you lies about me.  - He's an animal.
他抱起我然後扔到了泳池裡
He picked me up and he threw me in the pool.
- 他必須得走人  - 不 我要你走人  現在就走
- All right? He has to go.  - No, I need you to go. Now.
啥  為啥是我 他先起的頭
What? Why-why me? He-he's the one who started it.
那就對了 趕緊滾吧
Yeah, that's right. Get the hell out of here.
順便趕緊找個工作好好過日子得了
And get a job and a life while you're at it.
你吃白食的日子到頭了
Your freeloading days are over.
你 也是  滾蛋
You, too. Get going.
等會 我干了啥啊
Wait, what did I do?
你對我兒子動手了
You put your hands on my son!
你不尊重我的家庭
You're not respecting my family!
你是個畜生
You're an animal!
稍等  聽我說
Look, okay, just listen.
- 先冷靜一下  - 我不需要冷靜一下
- Just calm down.  - I don't have to calm down!
你打了我的兒子
What are... You're attacking my son!
你還滿嘴胡說八道
And you're, and you're making up lies!
你騙我讓我覺得你是個好人
You made... You tricked me into thinking you're a good guy.
你不是好人
You're not a good guy.
- 好吧  - 你他媽就是個小人
- Right. Mm-hmm.  - You're a fucking small guy.
Margie Margie 你聽我解釋
Margie, Margie, just let me explain this to you.
- 你聽我解釋好吧  - 你管不了我
- Just let me talk to you, okay?  - You are not in control of me.
好的 好的 聽我說好吧
Okay, okay, listen, all right?
你看到的只是事情的一部分
Okay, you don't have all the information you need.
Scott在作妖
All right? Scott is acting out
因為他不敢前進
'cause he's afraid to move on with his life.
跟波士頓紅襪隊
It's no different than when the Boston Red Sox
終於贏了世界大賽是一個原理的
finally won a World Series, okay?
- 哦 我的天  - 他們需要達到那種狀態
- Oh, my God.  - They had, they had to get to a point
- 那種相信自己 好吧  - 你可閉嘴吧
- where-where they believed, okay?  - Just shut up.
- 所有  - 你他媽閉嘴
- All-all...  - Shut the fuck up.
我就問了他一個問題 然後他就翻臉了
All I did was just ask him a question, and he flipped out.
所有我就把他放在溫和的水裡
So I put him in the water, which is soft.
我緩解這個危機
I diffused the situation.
我的培訓裡都有這些的
It was what-what m-my training's all about.
我 我真的是緩解了這個危機
I-I wa... I was totally diffusing the situation.
你有閉嘴的時候嗎
Do you ever shut up?
你他媽有閉嘴的時候嗎
Do you ever just shut the fuck up?
你就在那叭叭叭叭
You just talk and you talk and you talk,
自己都不知道自己在講啥
and you don't know what you're saying.
狗屁不通
It makes no sense.
感覺就像你收集了各種
It's like you picked up all these little pieces
各樣的信息
of information from all over.
全是斷片的  毫無意義的
They don't make any sense. They're fragments.
無意的 廢話
No sense. Nonsense.
我現在不講了
I-I'm not talking.
我忍了這麼多了 我不管了
I've had it up to here. I'm done.
你倆 滾犢子
Both of you, get your shit out of here.
Margie
Margie.
操
Oh, fuck.
所以
Well
所以 現在我們去哪兒
Well, where do we go now?
你問我幹啥
What are you asking me for?
你捅的婁子 你個蠢貨
You created this whole mess, you fucking schmuck.
嘿 哥們
Hey, man.
你生我氣嗎
Are you mad at me?
我  當然沒有啊
Me? No, of course not.
那你生我氣嗎
Are-are you mad at me?
我啊
I mean,
- 沒生但是  - 他們
- no, but...  - Are they...
他們有在問我嗎
Are they asking questions about me?
我不會告密的 哥們
I'm not gonna snitch on you, man.
但是吧 就是 我跟他們說什麼啊
But at the same time, like, what am I gonna say to them?
你是那個望風人 但是沒望風
You were the lookout that didn't look out.
呃 好吧 我其實想問你
Um, well, I've been meaning to ask you.
介於你現在住這兒了 呃 我在想
Um... you know, since you're in here, uh, well, I was wondering
你介不介意我在你家住一段時間
if you wouldn't mind me staying at your house for a little bit.
你來就是為了問我這個
You came up here to ask me that?
- 我也是來看你的啊  - 你來
- I also came to see you.  - You came...
不你不是來看我的  你是來問這個的
No, you didn't come to see me. You came to ask me that.
然後 不你不能住我家
And, no, you can't stay at my house.
抱歉 但是我沒地方去了哥們
I'm sor... I have nowhere to go, bro.
- 我家挺嚇人的  - 我媽把 我媽
- My house is frightening, dude.  - My mom kicked, my mom
- 把我趕出來了  - 你他媽生活怎麼搞的
- kicked me out.  - The fuck are you doing with your life?
大老遠開車過來就是為了問我
Drive all the way down here just to ask me
能不能住我家
if you can stay at my house.
- 不是  - 對 你根本不愛我
- No, I-I...  - No, you don't love me.
我愛你啊
I do love you.
抱歉 我 我 你說得對
I'm sorry. I-I... You're right.
我不應該提的 抱歉
I shouldn't have asked. I'm sorry.
你知道嘛 我正好想讓你幫個忙
And you know what? I need you to do me a favor.
說吧哥們 啥都行
Anything, bro. Just ask.
你得幫我喂貓 行吧
You got to feed my cat, all right?
喂大概三到五個月吧
For the next three to five months.
有其他別的我能做的嗎
Is there anything else I could do?
因為我有點對貓過敏
'Cause I'm-I'm kind of allergic to cats.
你可得照顧好我家小糖糖
You better look out for Sprinkles,
因為我可是一直在照顧你
because I'm looking out for you, all right?
聽你的
You got it.
聽好了 哥們
And, listen, man.
我要你花時間陪著小糖糖
I need you to spend time with Sprinkles.
我不要你只是
I don't want you just
到那兒喂完食就跑了
going in there, feeding him and running out.
你得到那兒 撓他的肚子
You got to go in there, scratch his belly.
你得告訴他我想他 過不久就回去見他
You tell him I miss him and I'll see him soon.
好的
Right.
呃 弟兄們都怎麼樣
Um, how, uh, how are the boys?
Igor和Richie在裡面過得好麼
How's Igor and Richie doing in there?
我跟你講 我還沒見到Richie
I'll tell you right now. I haven't seen Richie.
Igor呢
Igor?
哥們 朝右看
Bro, look to your right.
那是Carla
That's Carla.
Carla
Carla.
臥槽 別開玩笑
Holy shit! Get the...
哥們 她他媽是活的
Bro, she's fucking real.
是一個大活人
She's fucking real.
竟然他媽是活的 臥槽
She's fucking real. Holy shit.
喲 大美女啊
Yo. She's hot, man.
他說的都是真的
He was telling the truth the entire time.
- 真好啊  - 是啊
- Good for him, man.  - I know.
- 酷斃了  - 是啊
- That's awesome.  - Yeah.
嘿 說你呢
Hey, you.
你他媽的在這幹啥呢
What the hell are you doing there?
哦 抱歉 我以為這是我家
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought this was my house.
從我家後院滾出去
Get out of my backyard!
滾出去
Get the hell out of here!
剛剛做的還是蠻開心啊
I'm really glad we did that.
真的很舒服
It was really nice.
我也是
Me, too.
碉堡了
That was awesome.
嗯我好想你的
Yeah. I missed you.
是吧  我也好想你來著
Oh, yeah? I missed you, too.
就像從前一樣的
Just like, uh, old times.
我想我的朋友們了
I miss all my friends, you know.
鯊魚先生  怪骷髏先生
Mr. Shark, Mr. Weird Skeleton.
嗯 他們也想你了
Well, they missed you, too.
他們也想你了
They missed you, too.
嘿 我現在出了點狀況
Hey, I, uh... I'm in a bit of a situation.
我能在你這兒待幾天嗎
You think I could stay here for a few days?
你在說啥
What are you talking about?
說起來挺丟人的
Well, it's silly.
我跟Ray大吵了一架
Me and Ray got into this big fight,
然後碰巧我媽看見了 然後她就吼了我倆
and then my mom caught us, and she just started yelling at us.
然後就把我倆趕出來了  她有點不太對勁
And she threw us out, so... She kind of lost her mind.
所以你就來我這兒了
Is that why you're here right now?
不是
No.
你干我就是為了有地方住
Did you just fuck me for shelter?
不 我不是為了有地方住干的你
No, I didn't fuck you for shelter.
我啥都沒干
Uh, I-I-I didn't do anything.
啥  我啥都 我就 我就想要個待的地方
What? I didn't... I just... I just need a place to stay.
我的天
Oh, God.
老哥 我們還要吵多少次
Dude, dude, how many times we got to do this?
你在說啥 我就是想
What do you mean? I-I just want to...
我就是需要  需要幾周而已
I just need... It's just for a couple weeks.
沒啥大不了的
It's not that big of a deal.
幾周  你剛才還說幾天
A few weeks? You just said a few days.
- 額 也可能是幾個月  - 幾個月
- Uh, or a couple months. It's...  - Months?
我在思考人生
I'm figuring my stuff out.
未來不確定的
I don't know the future.
哦 我的天 你
Oh, my God, you...
走你
There you go.
- 嘿 幹嘛  - 我不會再讓我自己
- What the... Hey.  - I'm not going to let myself
生你的氣了 不過我告訴你
be upset by you, but I'm gonna tell you something.
你讓我覺得自己像個瘋子
You make me feel so crazy.
不過我不會讓我自己變成瘋子的
I'm not gonna let myself be crazy now,
但是你讓我覺得自己像個瘋子
but you make me feel crazy!
你自己就是瘋子然後
You are so crazy that you make
你還會把你周圍所有人都逼瘋
everyone around you feel fucking crazy.
遇見你的人 那些普通人
The people meet you, and they're normal people,
他們跟你呆久了 就他媽的變成了
and then they hang out with you, and then they're fucking
好吧 好吧 對對對
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我要保持禪境  我要去冥想
I got to stay Zen. I got to meditate.
我現在就在冥想 而你需要滾蛋
I'm meditating right now, and you got to go.
- 啥 啥  - 沒錯 帶走你的破爛
- What? What?  - Yeah, here's your shit.
好吧Okay.
保持冷靜
Staying calm.
你得走了  現在就走
You got to leave. It's time to go.
可是
Well...
滾蛋
Get out.
可是我沒地方去啊
Well, I don't have anywhere to go.
那我就不管了
It's not my problem anymore.
謝謝你來的這一炮
Thank you for the sex.
在你張嘴說話之前還是蠻美好的
It was wonderful until you started talking.
你走吧
You got to go.
我能睡你弟弟那屋嘛
Could I sleep in your brother's room?
不行
No.
可是他有上下鋪喂
But he has bunk beds.
他才14歲
He's 14 years old.
嘿 喲 Dougie 我能睡你屋嘛
Hey, yo, Dougie, can I crash in your room?
沒門老哥
That's not happening, bro.
老天爺
Jesus Christ.
操
Fuck.
嘿 你知道Ray Bishop在哪兒嗎
Hey, do you know where Ray Bishop is?
他在後面  跟我來
He's in the back. Come with me.
那你下次能不能先戴面具
How about next time you put your mask on
然後再下車
before we get off the rig?
我得在門口等你一分鐘
I mean, I'm standing at that front door for a minute
- 什麼鬼啊   - 我讓他這麼幹的
- waiting for you. What the hell?   - I told him to.
總是陰陽怪氣的誇人
Always with the backhanded compliment.
你為啥就不能
Why can't you just, you know,
光說兩句好聽的
at least say the nice thing and then...
- 跟你 給句好話就不錯了 - 好吧
- Listen, you should be happy with any compliment.  - Okay.
- 這叫建設性意見  - 這叫
- It's constructive criticism.  - It's...
- 就是 總是損人  - 繼續
- It just... It's always bad.  - Go ahead.
我更能接受鼓勵什麼的
I would respond better to encouragement.
我就
I'm just...
那我鼓勵你他媽閉嘴吧
I encourage you to shut the fuck up.
他太弱了  他禁不住的
He's soft. He can't take it.
- 你說的的  - 他一肚子情感
- You're right.  - He's an emotional eater.
可不 這一代的毛病就是這個
Well, that's the problem with this generation, man.
禁不起批評
They can't take criticism.
- 他們 可委屈了  - 我知道
- They get, they get all-all upset.  - I know.
嘿 我不能代表我們這一代所有人 好吧
Hey, I'm not a whole generation, all right?
我就 我就是個普通爺們  一個有感情的普通爺們
I'm just, I'm just a man. A man with feelings.
- 哦 我的天  - 嘔 嘔
- Oh, my God.  - Aw! - Aw!
現在你讓我變成壞人了
Now you're making me look bad.
- 你這算爺們嗎  - 停一下  現在你讓我變成壞人了
- You're a man?  - Now you're making me look bad. Stop.
Ray
Ray.
嘿 Ray
Hey, Ray.
哦 老天爺
Oh, Jesus Christ.
你在這幹啥
What are you doing here?
就 我沒地方可以去了 好吧
Look, uh, I-I don't have anywhere else to go, all right?
我沒有辦法了 所以
I'm out of options, so...
我為啥要管
Why would I care?
我很抱歉 呃
I'm sorry. Like, uh-uh...
找個樹底下躺著去  我不管
Go sleep under a tree. I don't care.
你知道你讓我失去了什麼嗎  你知道嗎
Do you have any idea what you took from me? Do you?
嗯  你採訪我前妻了60分鐘
Huh? You do a 60-minute interview with my ex-wife
去瞭解了我是個什麼樣的人
to find out what kind of guy I am?
你覺得她準備說啥
What do you think she was gonna say?
- 我不知道啊  - 順便
- I don't know. I...  - By the way,
我不是個賭徒 我是做短線投資的
I'm not a gambler, okay? I day-trade.
我不知道有啥區別啊
I don't know the difference.
那你張嘴之前應該先去弄明白有啥區別啊
You should've found out before you shot your mouth off.
我知道你吸了不少大麻 但是你不蠢
I know you smoke a lot of weed, but you're not dumb.
你知道你他媽的自己在幹啥
You knew what the fuck you were doing.
你去找了世界上最恨我的人
You went to the person that hates me the most
得到了我所能得到的最差的評價
to get the worst review you could possibly get.
你咋不來這而問問這些人呢
Why didn't you come down here and ask these guys
問問他們覺得我怎麼樣
what they thought of me?
你有想過這麼做麼
Did you ever think of doing that?
抱歉  你說的對 你說的對
I'm sorry. You're right. You're right.
- 額 我不應該  - 你才沒有歉意
- Uh, I shouldn't have done...  - You're not sorry
否則你就不會那麼干了  所以現在呢
or you wouldn't have done it. So now what?
現在你沒地方住了
Now you don't have a place to stay?
你現在跑到這裡來瞪著你那水靈靈的大眼睛
So now you come down here with your little puppy dog look
然後我就會於心不忍麼
on your face, and I'm supposed to feel bad?
但是 我知道
Look, all I know is,
如果你不對我好 我媽會恨你一輩子
if you're not nice to me, then my mom will hate you forever
而且永遠不會原諒你
and she'll never forgive you.
真的  這種情感牌你也敢打
Really? You're gonna play that card?
這 這牌超好用的
It's a, it's a pretty good card.
而且我就這一張牌了
It's all I got.
Ray
Ray.
嘿 Ray
Hey, Ray.
Raymond
Raymond.
Ray
Ray!
幹啥
What?
嘿 我睡不著
Hey, I can't sleep.
我 我從來沒睡過這麼早
I-I never go to sleep this early.
哦 那 你知道你該幹啥嗎
Oh. Well, you know what you should do?
你該閉他媽的嘴
You should shut the fuck up.
睡覺去
Go to sleep.
謝了
Thanks.
睡不著
Can't go to sleep.
你咋不把你的大麻蘸到奈奎爾裡面
Why don't you dip your weed in NyQuil,
類似於白加黑的黑片
你個癮君子
you fucking drug addict?
嘿  我要做什麼
Hey, w-what do I do?
做你平時做的事  原地不動呆著
Do what you always do. Sit there and do nothing.
嘿 上廁所怎麼走啊
Hey. Where do you go to the bathroom around here?
小號的話 直走
Well, number one, down there.
大號的話 街對過的唐恩都樂
Number two, Dunkin' Donuts across the street.
今天過得開心點哦
Have a wonderful day, man.
哦 謝了
Oh, thanks.
大個  睡得咋樣啊
How'd you sleep, big man?
我聽說你是Stan的孩子
I hear you're Stan's kid.
他是個勇敢的人  很榮幸認識你
He was a brave man. It's an honor to meet you.
謝了 大哥
Thanks, man.
很 也很榮幸認識你
It's a, it's an honor to meet you, too.
雖然我什麼也沒做
I-I didn't do anything, though.
你覺得你什麼都沒做
You don't think you did?
沒做啊
No.
謝謝你的犧牲
I appreciate your sacrifice.
我紋這個身是為了泡妹子
No, I got this one to impress a girl.
噢 結果怎麼樣
Oh? And how did that work out?
不怎麼樣
Not good.
- 我們已經結婚18年了  - 喔 你老婆好慘
- We've been married 18 years.  - PAPA: Ooh, poor woman.
- 18年了是嗎  - 恭喜
- 18 years, huh?  - Congratulations.
- 謝謝  - 哇哦
- Thank you.  - Wow.
剩下的這些是毛利人的部落圖案
The rest I got, you know, Maori, tribal.
很好看啊兄弟
It's beautiful work, man.
謝謝了 兄弟
Thank you, man. I appreciate that.
- 這個是什麼  - 是毛利人圖案
- What was that one?  - Maori.
代表著力量和勇氣
This stands for strength and courage.
- 真的嗎  - 對
- Really?  - Yeah.
你還待在這幹什麼
What the hell are you still doing here?
是這樣 信不信由你
Well, you know, believe it or not,
我找不到地方住一晚 所以
I-I couldn't find a place to live in just a night, so...
- 我信  - 我算是完蛋了 Ray
- I believe it.  - I'm kind of fucked, Ray.
沒錯
Yes, you are.
趕快吃完你的免費早餐
I'd say finish up your free breakfast,
然後滾吧
and, uh, hit the bricks.
沒關係 沒關係
All right. It's all right.
這小子可以留下
The kid can stay.
但是你得幹活 好嗎 你願意工作嗎
But you got to work, all right? You ready to do some work?
願意啊 你這是 讓我做消防員了嗎
Yeah. Did... did you just, did you just make me a fireman?
不是
No.
你要不就打掃廁所 要不就滾
Go clean the toilets or get the fuck out.
我讓你做 什麼鬼
Did I make you a... What...
嘿 幫我個忙
Hey, do me a favor.
樓下那間廁所 我用過了
The bathroom downstairs...I-I used it.
你就從那間開始吧
You can start there.
好極了呢
Great.
戴上手套哈 容易濺上
Get gloves. Pretty muddy.
你知道嗎 當我看到這種大塊污漬
You know, when I see a big stain like that,
我就先上下刷 然後左右刷
I go up and down, and then I go left and right.
- 真是美好時光呢   - 這就對了
- Good times.   - There you go.
你要把濺上去的也洗了
You got to get the splatter.
看到了嗎 真是條完美的直線
You see that? That's a nice straight line.
你們要做很多無聊的工作哈
Yeah, you guys, uh, got to do a lot of shit work, huh?
我們不會說這是無聊的工作
We don't refer to it as shit work.
這是我們的家 我們希望它漂漂亮亮的
This is our house. We want it to look nice.
懂嗎 集體榮譽
You know, company pride.
要用熱水洗
You got to wash it hot.
熱水 不是溫水 不是冷水 要很熱
Hot. Not warm, not cold. Extra hot.
- 好的  - 因為有臭蟲
- Okay.  - Because of the bedbugs.
啥 什麼是臭蟲
What-What's bedbugs?
就是 呃 一種小昆蟲
They're, uh, a-a tiny insect
它們進了你的家門就要把你逼走
that get into your home and they run you out.
- 你知道它們怎麼繁殖嗎  - 不知道
- You know how they procreate?  - No.
雄性臭蟲把他的丁丁
The male bedbug takes his penis
塞進雌性的肚子裡
and jams it into the female's stomach.
雌性臭蟲有陰道嗎 是有的
Does the female have a vagina? Yeah, she does.
這不重要
It doesn't matter.
他塞進她的肚子裡
He jams it into her stomach.
你是怎麼知道這些的 兄弟
Well, how do you know all this, man?
我怎麼知道 我研究過啊
How do I know? I researched it.
- 就翻過來  - 哦 翻過來
- Just flip it over. Flip.  - Oh, just a flip.
- 對了 沒錯  - 好的
- There you go, yeah.  - Okay.
你學會了 就順著翻下來
You got it. Just flip it right down.
- 疊得很好啊  - 嗯
- Very nice.  - Mm.
幹得好
Well done.
當你長了臭蟲 所有人都會離開你
When you have bedbugs, everybody leaves.
我父母不和我聯繫了
My parents stopped calling.
我兄弟姐妹不來看我了
My brothers and sisters stopped coming over.
我女朋友把我甩了 所有人都走了
My girl left. Everybody's gone.
你知道最後誰會留在你身邊嗎
And you know who's there for you at the end?
無比諷刺
Ironically?
只有臭蟲
The bedbugs.
我從沒想過我會這麼說
I never thought I'd say it,
如果我當上了主廚 我就讓你做我的助手
but if I make chief, I'm making you my aide.
- 是嗎  - 你好啊小子
- Yeah?  - What's up, kid?
你覺得你測試做得怎麼樣
Well, how do you think you did on the test?
測試太難了
Tough test.
當然了 我希望我做的還不錯
I mean, you know, I hope I did good.
我操
Fuck!
他幹得不錯
He's doing a good job.
他洗車洗得不錯
He knows how to wash a truck.
那就收拾收拾去洗車行干吧
Getting ready for his career working at a car wash.
你怎麼就不肯放過這孩子
You ever gonna give this kid a break or what?
我不知道該做什麼
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
那就什麼都別做
Then do nothing.
Stan死的時候你在嗎
Were you on the job when Stan was killed?
是啊 你知道我在
Yeah. You know I was.
你聽說的時候第一個念頭是什麼
What's the first thing you thought of when you heard?
我想知道他有沒有孩子
I-I wondered if he had kids.
我們到底為什麼要洗車
Why do we have to clean this thing anyway?
反正它都會著火
It's just gonna get fire on it.
那些被活活燒死的人
You think the people that are burning alive
會在乎車洗得亮不亮嗎
give a fuck if the truck is shiny?
我就隨口一說
Just saying.
我都不知道你為什麼要洗車
I don't even know why you got to clean the truck.
怎麼地 你還想在大火面前性感一點嗎
What, you're trying to show up all sexy to a fire?
我喜歡他
I like him.
不要 住手
No! No! Stop!
夠了
All right!
我給你扶一下書包 滑下來了
Let me fix that backpack. It's slipping.
你送我去學校感覺好奇怪
It's weird having you walk me to school.
為什麼呢
Why is that?
因為平時都是Scott送我
'Cause Scott always walks me.
有時候我也送你
I walk you sometimes.
好像是
I guess so.
他和你們在一起時奇怪嗎
Is he, uh, is he weird around you guys?
沒有啊
No.
他挺好的
He's nice.
他經常問我還好嗎
He asks me how I'm doing.
你怎麼回答他
What do you tell him?
我說我還好
I say I'm doing fine.
你不用說謊來照顧我的感受 好嗎
Look, you don't have to lie to make me feel better, all right?
我知道我和你媽媽做得不夠好
I know me and your mom could do a better job
我們應該一起克服這事
getting along through all of this, and, uh...
對不起 我處理得並不好
Hey, I'm sorry if I haven't handled it so well.
這是什麼
What's that?
這是閃冰俠
Oh, that's Ice Flash.
Scott給我畫的 但是畫得不太好
Scott drew it for me, but it didn't come out so good.
是啊 我覺得他畫的很亂
Yeah, I think his drawings are a little shaky.
這張是我畫的
That's the one that I drew.
這是他畫的
This is how he drew it.
挺不錯吧
It's good, right?
是啊 豈止是不錯
Yeah, it's better than good.
這很厲害
Did a great job.
是啊
Yeah.
他說他會教我
He said he was gonna teach me.
他說他要教你畫這個嗎
He said he'd teach you how to do that?
對
Yeah.
他說話算數
And he stays to his word.
現在來這裡好愜意啊
It's so nice in here now.
我好喜歡這種顏色
I love it. I love the colors.
我全都喜歡
I love everything.
- 來啦  - 嗨
- Mm!  -  Hey.
- 你好呀 Scott  - 怎麼
- Oh, hey, Scott.  - What's...
這是怎麼了
What's going on in here?
這是 為什麼全都不一樣了
Where... Why is everything so different?
好看嗎 你喜歡嗎
Isn't it nice? Do you like it?
那是張粉色的椅子嗎
Is that a pink chair?
- 是啊 我們在重新裝修  - 這窗簾怎麼也變了
- Yeah, we've been redecorating.  - W-What's up with the drapes?
是啊
- Yeah.
植物也換了
Plants, too.
可不嘛 為啥
Yeah. Why's...
你媽媽的品位很好
Your mother has great taste.
好吧
Yeah.
你最近都去哪裡了
Where have you been staying?
我一直在消防站 和Ray在一起
Oh, I've been, uh, at the firehouse with Ray.
好的 我很高興你沒有流落街頭
Oh, okay. Well, I'm just glad that you're not on the street.
我跟你說他不會無家可歸的
I told you he wasn't homeless.
你一點沒錯 我好喜歡這個綠色
When you're right, you're ri... I love this green.
- 是啊  - 其實我一直在
- Yeah, well... - We... I actually have been
學著 就是 和那些弟兄們相處
learning, uh, a lot and, like, bonding with the guys.
- 是嗎  - 所以 是啊
- Oh.  - So, uh, yeah.
對 他們讓我做清潔
Yeah, they got me cleaning.
他們讓我洗洗東西
Uh, they got me, like, washing stuff and, like,
- 在消防站裡幹活  - 是吧
- working around the firehouse and...  - Mm-hmm. Oh.
我確實明白你之前的想法了
I really understand where you were coming from before.
就是你把我趕出去的時候
You know, when you threw me out.
我覺得我現在已經改過自新了
Like, I think I really got my shit together now,
我已經準備好 搬回來
and I'm ready to, like, come back and...
好吧
Okay.
所以 你覺得你已經懂得什麼叫辛苦工作了
So, like, you think you know what hard work is?
倒也不是 但就是
Well, I wouldn't say that, but, you-you know,
我 我有個初步認識了
I-I-I definitely have an idea.
你拖了下地
You mopped a floor
做了做飯
and-and you cooked.
你打掃了一下廁所
You cleaned a bathroom once.
哎呀 Scott
Oh. Oh, Scott.
那你幹完這麼多重活肩膀酸嗎
And how's your shoulder feel after all that very hard work?
哦 你們取笑我
Oh, you're making fun of me.
你們為啥拿我開玩笑
Why are you making fun...
我工作很辛苦 真的
I-I worked really hard. I did.
不信去問Ray
Ask Ray.
他想搬回來
He's trying to get back.
吃雞巴去吧 Joy
Eat a dick, Joy.
早上已經吃過了
Had one for breakfast.
已經飽了
I'm full.
喂
Hey!
還有  爸爸的神龕在哪裡
And-and wh...and where's Dad's shrine?
- 在哪 去哪了  - 哦 你把氣氛都破壞了
- Where-where-where...  - Oh, you're ruining the vibe.
神龕呢 爸爸的神龕呢
Where's his shrine? Where's Dad's shrine?
他的東西也不見了 我的東西也沒了
All of his stuff is gone. All my shit's gone.
- 到底怎麼回事 - 寶貝
- What's going on?  - Honey.
好吧 讓我 我很抱歉
Uh, all right, let...I'm-I'm really sorry.
我不該大聲說你 對不起
I'm sorry I raised my voice. I'm sorry.
- 我不該笑你 - 我們能私下說話嗎
- I'm sorry I laughed.  - Could we talk in private?
- 好的 我們出去吧  - 行
- Let's go outside, yeah.  - Yeah.
我們出去說幾句話
So we're gonna speak for a minute.
- 對不起  - 真的抱歉  - 沒關係 Joy
- I'm sorry. - So sorry.  -  It's okay, Joy.
- 我們好好談一下  - 是啊
- Let's just have a real...  - Let's just... Yeah.
- 我們去外面吧  - 好好開始談談
- Let's just talk outside.  - Let's just get into it.
行啊 好勒
You know? Right. Okay.
- 那麼…
- So...
天 你不是吧
Oh, no, you did not!
警報
Code alarm.
- 引擎和卡車馬上就位
- Engine and truck are first due.
房號118
Box 118.
房頂上有很濃的煙
Heavy smoke coming from the roof.
嘿 Scott 你想跟這輛車一起過去嗎
Hey, yo, Scott, you want to ride this one in?
可 可以嗎
Is-is that okay?
好啊 上車吧
Yeah, jump in.
- 上車
- Jump in.
- 都聽好
-  Listen up.
這個房間的警情已經接到很多個電話了
We're getting multiple calls on this box.
我們肯定要進火場 穿好裝備
We're going to a fire. Suit up!
5-7號消防梯呼叫史泰登島
Ladder 5-7 to Staten Island.
收到請講 5-7號
Yes, go ahead, Ladder 5-7.
二次警報傳輸中
Transmitting second alarm.
房號 1-1-8
Box 1-1-8.
五層建築的
Fire in the first and second floor
一樓和二樓失火
of a five-story multiple dwelling.
1-4-9 呼叫1-4-9
1-4-9 to 1-4-9,
司機準備開始工作
Chauffer to start work.
1-4-9司機已就位
1-4-9 Chauffeur to Control.
打開消防栓
Turn on the hydrant.
好的 穿好裝備
All right. Suit up.
10-4號
10-4.
5-7號梯呼叫司機
Ladder 5-7 to Chauffeur.
George 帶上天線 打通三樓的窗戶
George, take the aerial and vent that third-floor window,
然後帶上天線上樓頂
and then get the aerial to the roof.
1-4-9呼叫1-4-9
1-4-9 to 1-4-9.
司機 供水
Chauffeur, start water.
準備好了嗎 我開門了
Are you guys ready? I'm opening the door.
49號 水來了
49, here comes your water.
滅火滅火 趕快 撲滅它
Hit it, hit it. Go. Hit it, hit it!
我沒事
I'm good.
- 你還好嗎  - 還好
- You all right?  - Yeah.
他們會沒事的 他們能搞定
They're gonna be fine. They got this.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, yeah, I-I know.
我知道看起來很嚇人 但他們心裡都有數的
I know it looks bad, but they know what they're doing.
好嗎
All right?
5-7號梯 5-7號司機
Ladder 5-7, Chauffeur 5-7.
我打開了三樓窗戶
I just vented the third-floor window.
我現在帶著天線上樓頂
I'm bringing the aerial to the roof.
5-7號
5-7 O.V. to 5-7.
我在二樓發現一名10-45
I got a 10-45 on the second floor.
我從裡面的樓梯把他帶到樓下
Gonna bring him down the inside stairs.
10-4號 Ray
10-4, Ray.
5-7號樓頂
5-7 roof to 5-7...
1-4-9號司機
1-4-9 Chauffeur to 1-4-9.
- 水壓怎麼樣  - 水壓沒問題
- How's the water pressure?  - Pressure's fine.
5-7-9呼叫5-7
5-7-9 to 5-7,
一樓所有房間已經撤離
all the apartments on the first floor are clear.
10-4 隊長
10-4, Cap.
每個人第一次進火場
You know, everyone gets nervous
都會緊張的
during their first fire.
你知道嗎 我還是個新手的時候 我害怕死了
You know, when I was a probie, I was so scared,
走到哪都跟著我的隊長
I would follow my captain everywhere,
拽著他的衣服
just hold on to his jacket.
就緊跟著他 希望自己活下來
You know, follow him around, hold on for dear life.
- 是啊  - 但是 呃
- Yeah.  - No, but, uh,
每個人都會有點害怕的
you know, everybody gets a little scared.
我覺得 這說明你是坦率的
I mean, you know, I mean, it's... keeps you honest.
知道嗎 如果你不害怕
You know? No, if you don't get scared,
- 那你肯定不正常  - 是啊
- there's something wrong with you.  - Mm-hmm.
但是 你爸爸從不會害怕
And, by the way, your dad never got scared.
是嗎 你怎麼知道
Yeah? How-how do you know?
以前吧 我和他在同一個消防站
I mean, back in the day, I-I was at the same house
一起待了六個月
with him for about six months, so...
等等 你和我爸爸共事了六個月
Wait, you worked with my dad for six months
- 你現在才告訴我  - 是啊 我覺得
- and you're just telling me?  - Yeah. I mean, I...
我不想讓你感到彆扭
Yeah, I didn't want to make you feel weird.
我們不想傷害你
We didn't want to insult you
因為你看上去很脆弱
'cause you seem a little delicate.
- 拜託  - 確實是
- No. Please.  - Well, yeah.
那 他是什麼樣的人
What, w-what was he like?
他和你有點像
He was kind of like you.
就是 如果你不瞭解他
You know, like, if you didn't know him,
你就會覺得他是個巨嬰 但是他
you'd think he was a crack baby, but he was...
但他是個好人 他是個很不錯的人
No, but he was a good guy. He was a, he was a great guy.
- 他是個好人  - 是啊 我聽說
- He was a great guy.  - Well, I-I, I mean, I heard
- 他超級搞笑的  - 是的
- he was fucking hilarious.  - Oh, yeah.
他干了好多破事都逃脫了
And-and he got away with so much shit,
因為他太討人喜歡了
like, because he was so freaking likable.
什麼事 他逃脫了什麼
What kind of stuff? Like, w-what'd he get away with?
有一次 我們正在西邊高速上開車
One time, we were driving down the West Side Highway
- 在外面玩了一整晚  - 對
- after being out all night...  -  Mm.
你知道這事
You know this.
這事超經典
This is a good one.
然後他就
And, uh, he's, like,
爬出天窗 爬上去
he's up on the... through the sunroof.
他就坐在車頂上
He's, like, sitting on top of the car.
我們沒辦法讓他下來
We're like... We couldn't get him in.
我們就加速開車 然後急剎
So we start speeding up, stopping short, you know.
後來我到了橋那裡停下 他直接跌到擋風玻璃上
By the time we hit the bridge, he fell onto the windshield.
- 他就  - 怎麼了
- So he's...  - What?
他就
he's, like...
什麼玩意兒
What?
就趴在那 咒罵我們 他的臉
Hanging on, cursing at us, putting his face
就擠在擋風玻璃上
up against the windshield.
他罵道 你們這些狗日的
He's like, "You motherfuckers!"
就像阿湯哥的電影
It was like some real Tom Cruise shit.
然後
So...
我們到了布魯克林
We get into Brooklyn.
當然啦 那就有警察
And sure-sure enough, there's cops.
就像專門在那等我們似的
Like, uh, like they were waiting for us.
糟了
Oh, shit.
我就想 我們肯定完蛋了
So now I'm like, "Oh, fuck. We're screwed."
Stan從車上下來 他對著警察走過去
Stan gets off the car. He goes over to the cop.
我就想 完了 他要去跟警察鬧事了
I'm thinking, "Oh, shit, he's gonna fucking clock this cop.
他肯定會那樣
He's gonna, you know..."
結果他直接走過去 捧著警察的臉
And he goes right up to him, grabs his face,
親了他的嘴
and he kisses him on the lips.
他們是高中同學
They went to high school together.
搞半天他們是高中同學
They went to fucking high school together.
我就想 只有Stan才能逃脫這種事
I'm like, "Only Stan could get away with that."
真的 我發誓
I swear to God.
你知道嗎 傳聞說
Well, you know, the rumor is
他的可卡因就是從警察這拿的
that he got the coke from the cops.
不是那一個警察 他還認識一個在曼哈頓的警察
Not that cop. There was another cop he knew in Manhattan.
什麼 不是吧不是吧不是吧
What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! No.
- 可卡因 啥 不是吧  - 夥計們
- Coke? What? No.  - Guys, guys, guys.
- 那是他父親啊  - 所以呢
- Guys, it's his dad.  - So?
- 我不知道這不能說  - 那是他父親
- I didn't know it was a secret.  -  It's his dad.
你們不能話說一半啊
You can't just tease me with that.
- 拜託了 夥計們  - 可這是
- Please, guys, but...  - It was...
你們不懂 我媽跟我說
You don't understand. My mom, my mom tells me
說了好多他的故事
all these stories about how much
說他就是個聖人啊什麼的
he's like a saint and all that shit.
我超想聽可卡因的故事
Like, I-I would love to hear a coke story.
- 拜託了  - 說13禁的版本
- Please.  - The PG-13 version.
不要啊 說完整的版本
No, you don't...No, the real version.
你們不懂我承受的壓力
You don't understand the amount  of pressure I'm under,
- 以為他是個完美的人  - 好吧 隨你了
- thinking this guy's perfect.  - All right, fuck it, fuck it.
好吧 我們那時候都磕得上頭了
All right, we were coked out of our minds.
- 妙啊  - 是嗎 我們全都磕了
- Nice.  - All right? We all were.
- 我們 是啊 我們都有份
- We all... Well, I mean, uh, we were.
- 但是時代不一樣 那時候我們都有份  - 是啊
- But that was a different time. I mean, we all did it.  - Right.
這傢伙是個癮君子
This guy was the cokehead.
- 你就是個癮君子  - 好吧
- You were the cokehead.  - All right.
我四年前就戒了 你知道的
I stopped four years ago. You know that.
你在說啥 你以為
What are you talk...How do you think
他這些年怎麼保持這麼瘦的
he stayed this skinny all these years?
那是因為我新陳代謝快
No, I have a high metabolism.
你的臉皮應該刻在玻利維亞的硬幣上
They should have his face on a nickel in Bolivia.
但那是玩鬧的時候 好嗎
But playtime was playtime, all right?
你知道 當他工作的時候
Like, you know, when he was at work,
他就非常的專業
he was, he was all, you know, business.
他就是那種 當你衝進火場的時候
All right? And he was the guy you wanted by your side
你希望站在你身邊的人
if-if you were going into a fire.
我是說 如果你要
Yeah, I mean, if they were gonna,
從零開始塑造一個消防員的話
like, build a fireman from scratch,
他就是那個
he would've been, you know...
- 模板  - 是啊
- Prototype.  - Yeah. Yeah.
沒錯 他從頭到腳
Exactly. You know, top to bottom...
都是一個真正的消防員
He's a fireman.
知道嗎
You know?
- 他是最勇敢的那個  - 是啊
- You know, as brave as they come.  - Yeah.
我想到是玩遊戲說
You know, I was thinking about what you said at the game
消防員不應該生孩子
about, you know, like, firemen shouldn't have kids.
我告訴你
Let me tell you something.
你爸爸並不僅僅是那天晚上
You know, your dad, he didn't just die
救了兩個人然後犧牲了
saving those two people that night.
他經常幹那種事
I mean, he did that a lot.
你知道嗎 有時候
You know, like, sometimes,
他都等不到指令
he wouldn't even wait for the line.
就會直接衝進失火的房間裡
He'd just, he'd just go in, like, a fully involved room,
我們都在喊他 你這是做什麼
and you're, like...I'm like, "What are you doing?"
如果他聽到裡面有人的話
And because if-if he heard there was somebody in there,
他就會馬上衝進去
he'd just go in.
這就是他的方式
That's the way, you know...
他就是這樣的人
He... That's who he was.
他本性就是這樣 你知道嗎
That's how he was built, you know?
他不可能 不做這樣的事
He couldn't, he couldn't not be that way.
你明白嗎
You understand?
謝謝你 真的 謝謝你告訴我
Thank you. No, thank you, thank you for sharing.
太棒了
That's awesome.
他要是聽到我這麼說
He would slap the shit out of me
肯定會扇死我 但他確實是個英雄
if he heard me say this about him, but he was a hero.
人們需要英雄
And heroes are necessary.
而英雄應該擁有家庭 對嗎
And they should be allowed to have families, all right?
雖然我知道 那意味著
But I know it means, you know,
家人會因此受苦
that people suffer.
我很遺憾 真的
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
對不起 我說的話太混賬了
Well, but I'm sorry for being a dick.
- 所有事都有兩面性  - 不用道歉
- There's-there's two sides to every story.  - No.
謝謝你告訴我 謝謝你讓我明白這些
Thank you for sharing with me. Thanks for taking me here.
- 好了 我們別搞得跟奧普拉秀一樣  - 是啊
- All right, we don't have to get all Oprah.  - Yeah.
- 沒事的    - 嘿敬Stan
- It's all right. - Hey, to Stan.
- 來 敬Stan  - 來 敬Stan
- Yeah, Stan.- Yeah, Stan.
Stan Stan Stan
- Stan. - Stan.- Stan.
♪ 嘿
♪ 來吧嘗試一下
♪ 沒有什麼是永恆的
♪ 總有比中立
♪ 更好的事
♪ 但是我和灰姑娘
♪ 組裝了一輛車
♪ 只有一個車頭燈
♪ 我們也能開家的方向
唉 我點兒頭疼 我
My head hurts. I...
我就只能吸吸大麻 喝酒挨不住啊
This-this is why I don't drink.I just, I just smoke weed.
所以你未來打算怎麼走啊
Hey, so what are you gonna do?
什麼怎麼走
With-with what?
你的小日子啊
With your life.
你總有啥是感興趣的吧
You must be passionate about something.
呃 有啊 我對紋紋身有興趣啊
Um, yeah, the...the tattoo thing.
我超愛紋身的
I... I love that.
你只是嘴上說說的那種喜歡而已嘛
Were you, like, into that?
沒有 我其實私下經常練習的
No, you know, it-it takes a lot of practice, you know, and...
但現在我身邊的朋友已經沒法讓我繼續再給他們紋身了
None of my friends will let me tattoo them anymore and...
嘿 要不你給我紋個好了
Hey, why don't you give me a tattoo?
啥
What?
啥個頭啊
What-what?
來嘛 我反正沒有任何紋身
Come on, I don't have any tattoos.
我就像白紙一張 嘿嘿
I'm a, I'm a blank slate, man.
我後背隨你怎麼練手
Put it on my back. Yeah, use it for practice.
額 你不是喝多了
Well... well, you're just saying this
才這麼說的吧 你不是
'cause you're drunk, right? You're not...
- 你不是認真的吧  - 每個人第一次紋身
- You're not actually... - Isn't everybody drunk
不都是在喝醉的時候嗎
when they get their first tattoo?
好的吧 Ray
Touche, Ray.
成
Yeah.
反正在背上 我又不在意
It's my back. I don't give a fuck.
反正我又看不見
I'm never gonna see it.
還有 我跟你說
Plus, I got to tell you something, you know.
我看見你給Harold畫的英雄了
I saw that drawing you did for Harold.
我都震驚了
I was kind of blown away by it, man. You...
畫得有點忒好了
You're getting really good at it.
我練過很多次的
I'm practicing a lot.
是嘛
Yeah.
就像所有事一樣 只要堅持鐵杵能磨成針
Like anything, you keep doing it, you get better at it.
然後呢 我
And I, you know...
我也希望你能成功
You know, I do want to see you do well, all right?
我相信你
I-I believe in you.
哥兒們 謝了
Thanks, man.
你一定很愛我吧
You... you must really love me.
我也很愛你呢
I love you, too.
謝謝你這麼說但是我沒
Uh, I-I appreciate that, but I'm not ready...
你也會這麼對我說的吧
Y-You-you gonna say it back?
我沒準備好說這種話
I'm not ready to say something like that.
你得回應我呀
You got to say it back.
要不然我明天掛了 你怎麼辦
What-what if I die tomorrow?
那我就會說
Then I'll be that guy saying,
你知道嗎 雖然我沒說出口 但是
"You know, even though I never said it..."
嗯 好
Uh, look...
我會給你紋身
I would love to tattoo your back.
好勒
Okay, cool.
但是先說好啊 不要給我紋什麼獨角獸
All right, but here's the deal. No unicorns.
- 什麼彩虹啊  - 嗯
- No rainbows, all right? - Uh.
別整那些小姑娘喜歡上彩色的玩意兒
None of that shit little girls like to color in.
好
Okay.
還有別整人體器官 或者裸女哈
No body parts. No nudity.
- 好  - 別整中文字
- Okay.- No Chinese letters.
- 好吧 好吧 - 我想
- All right. All right, fine. - I want, I...
整些我看得懂的玩意兒
I want to be able to fucking read
紋在我背上
whatever you put back there.
別給我點個橘子雞什麼亂七八糟啥玩意兒的
I don't need some o-order for orange chicken or some shit.
好勒
All right.
要開始了哦 你準備好了麼
Here we go. You ready?
準備好了 開始吧
Yep, let's do it. Let's get it over with.
好 我真的很感謝
Yeah, I-I really appreciate this.
這個 這個很幫
This is... It's actually very nice.
好
Good.
我們開始了哦
All right.
我擦
Fuck.
哥兒們 為啥你們愛搞這玩意兒
Dude, why do you get these?
我不知道啊 我
Um, I don't know. I, uh...
每次不痛快的時候 我都會
Whenever I'm going through something, I just,
我都會搞一個紋身
you know, I get one.
讓我自己放鬆下冷靜下
It relaxes me and calms me down.
這有助於我思考人生
Helps me, like, think things through, you know.
- 這可以讓你放鬆  - 是啊
- This relaxes you? - Yeah.
你沒想過比如做瑜伽啥的去放鬆自己麼
You ever think of taking, like, a yoga class?
或者冥想啥的
Meditating?
或者獻個血
Why don't you just give blood?
那個也是用針扎的
There's still needles involved.
嗯這個紋身好看哦
Yeah, that's a nice tattoo.
很復古
It's aces.
- 你丫混蛋在偷看我牌嗎  - 啥
- You looking at my cards, you piece of shit? - What?
沒呢 我說的是紋身
No, no, no, no. I'm talking about the tattoo.
你幹嘛呢
What are you doing?
- 啥 - 你居然一晚上在搞我
- What? - First good hand you dealt me
你作弊
all night, you're cheating?
- 他說的是紋身好不啦   - 是啊
- He was talking about the tattoo. - Exactly.
-這麼爛的借口
- You are the worst liar ever.
6乘以4等於多少
What's six times four?
- 24.
24 對了 是 24
24. Yeah, 24.
那 7x5 呢
What's seven times five?
-35 答對了
- 35. - Good job.
你看看你多聰明啊
Look how smart you are.
我在猜你畫的都是些啥
I'm trying to guess what you're drawing
你手在我後背上上下下的動著
by the, by the way your hand's going.
記住啊 別整那些個奇怪的玩意兒啊 小心我的40米大刀
Remember, nothing weird or I'll kill you.
都是正常玩意兒  好吧
- Nothing weird. - Okay.
這看起來不奇怪吧
It doesn't look weird, does it?
挺正常的
No, not at all.
嗯 很好不然我會殺了他的
Oh, good, 'cause you know I'll murder him.
看著很不錯呢
It looks wonderful.
哎呀 這麼疼的咩
Oh! Is it supposed to hurt?
咋這麼疼呢
Is it supposed to hurt that much?
墨通過針扎進你皮膚 當然疼了
It's-it's a needle going into your back. Yeah.
道理我懂啊 我以為背上脂肪多點 會好點兒
I know, but I thought I had more back fat than that.
我可以也整個紋身不
Can I get a tattoo?
- 不 不行   - 可以啊
- No. No. -  Sure.
- 好吧  - 不行
- All right. - No.
絕對不行
Never.
別打擾專業人士幹活
Don't mess with perfection.
全員出發
Everybody goes.
全員出動 一級警報
Both companies, first due.
電話警報 警報號 3-4-3
Phone alarm. Box 3-4-3.
羅克蘭和富蘭克林路中間的卡朋特大道18號
18 Carpenter Avenue between Rockland and Franklin.
2樓的一個私宅窗戶有煙霧冒出
Smoke coming from the second- floor window of a private home.
出車
Turnout.
喲呵
Yoo-hoo.
- 你好  - 咋了
- Excuse me. - Yeah?
嘿 兄弟 你好麼
Hey, man. How you doing?
你好 兄弟
What's up, man?
幫忙一下
I need some assistance over here, please.
- 好勒 - 給我一個
- Sure, I... - Hey, give me a sh...
- 我的天  - 啊 沒什麼事的
- Oh, my God! - Ah, don't worry about it.
一切都還好的
Listen, everything's all good.
沒什麼大不了的
It's, uh, really nothing.
我只要你幫我一下下
I just need a little assistance.
這個馬上處理一下就好了
This is something that needs to be taken care of now.
你這是咋整的呀 你還好麼 你被槍擊了嗎
What happened? Are you okay? Did you get shot?
- 還是你被捅刀子了 - 這也不是什麼大事
- Were you stabbed? - It's not really a big deal.
可能我的電子煙在我褲兜裡爆炸了
My vape exploded in my pocket. Just...
也可能是我做瑜伽動作沒做對
I didn't stretch right before yoga.
可能我剛在玩兒乒乓球兒不小心滑倒了
I was playing tennis.I slipped.
- 到底咋回事兒啊 你 - 你要我說點兒啥
- Well, which one is it? - What do you want me to say?
沒啥事兒了
It was nothing.
我只是需要你幫我處理下傷口
I just need some medical attention, but just by you.
大哥 我大哥110 問下啊 我也不知道該咋整啊
Dude, I got to call 911. I don't know what to do.
別別別 別回頭把警察給我招來了
No, no, no, listen, listen. No police, please.
今兒就算了吧
Not today.
- 你說啥呢你  - 沒事
- What does that even mean? - No.
這個情況不需要政府介入
We don't need to get the government involved  into this situation.
我們一起弄弄就好了
We can handle this together.
大佬 我現在嗨著呢 沒法幫你啊
Dude, I'm so high. I can't help you right now.
我也很嗨著呢
I'm high, too.
那你應該很瞭解我的感受啊
Well, then you know how I feel.
你要我怎麼做
What do you want me to do?
幫我看下傷口
Take a look at this.
我需要清洗下傷口
I need some sort of foam.
- 我勒個去  - 你有針可以縫下麼
- Holy shit! - You got some stitching?
- 老兄  - 你 你有沒有針
- Dude! - Do-do you have, like, a little needle?
- 你有沒有類似針一樣的東西 - 沒有
- Do you have something with a needlepoint? - No.
這是咋回事啊
What happened?
就是一場誤會 發生點兒爭執
It was a misunderstanding. It was an argument.
不過我們和好了 我們解決了
But we're all friends again. We worked it out.
你懂的 都是朋友嘛
You know how buddies get.
老大我得把你送醫院去
Dude, I... We-we, we got to take you to the hospital
- 不然你會死的 - 我不會死
- or you're gonna die. - I'm not gonna die.
- 是的你會死  - 我會死
- Yes, you are.- I'm gonna die?
是的我確定
Yeah, I'm positive.
一定以及肯定 如果咱們不去醫院
I'm positive that you're gonna die
你會死的
if we don't go to the hospital.
這裡有金屬檢測器嗎
Are there metal detectors in here?
我不確定啊 咋了
I-I'm not sure. Why?
沒事
Don't even worry about it.
我後面再告訴你
I'll tell you later.
我去
Oh, shit.
- 啊 我去 疼啊 - 你會沒事的
- Oh, fuck.  - You'll be all right.
- 啊老天好疼  - 你會沒事的
- Oh, my God.  - You'll be all right.
有人嗎 幫個忙
Guys, I need help!
這個人在流血 他失了很多血
This guy's bleeding! He's losing a lot of blood!
- 麻煩給我一架輪床 - 謝謝
- I need a gurney, please! - Oh, thank you.
- 來 用手壓住  -謝謝
- All right, just hold... Put... - Thank you.
- 用手壓住傷口 會
- Put pressure on it, all right?
你好這個人不是被搶擊中了就是被人捅刀子了
Hi. This guy's been, uh, either shot or stabbed.
具體我也不知道 他沒說得很清楚
I don't know. He's been kind of vague about it.
先生 你被中槍了 還是被捅刀子了
Sir, have you been shot? Stabbed?
沒
No.
- 我失足掉進小樹叢了  - 好吧
- I fell in a thorn bush.  - Okay.
讓他填下這個表
Have him fill out this paperwork,
他填好了醫生一會會叫你名字的
and the doctor will call you when he's ready.
幫我個忙 跟我換個身份證行麼
Do me a favor, man. Can we just switch identities?
啥 不要
What? No.
那讓我借用下你駕照勒
Just let me use your driver's license.
- 大哥我們長得一點都不像啊  - 沒人會知道的
- We look nothing alike, dude.  - No one's gonna know.
相信我
Just trust me.
我流血流得我感覺要拉屎了
I'm bleeding. It feels like I have to shit.
我的天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
我是Margie的兒子 你認識
I'm Margie's son. Do you know...
我是Maggie的兒子
I'm Margie's son.
我不認識她
I don't know who that is.
我只是個負責登記的人而已
I'm just filling in.
好吧
Okay.
- 我懂  - 我越來越疼
- I know. - My pain keeps coming.
告訴我那個混蛋父親 我恨他
Tell that fucking cocksucker, my father, that I hate him
也愛他 我原諒他了
and I love him at the same time and I forgive him.
我不用替你轉達啊 你一定會沒事的
I-I-I do not need to do that, because you're gonna live.
告訴我姐姐 我知道她就是我媽媽
Tell my sister I know she's my mother.
哈
Huh.
我一聽到消息馬上就趕過來了
Got here as soon as I could.
老哥 我們得幫幫他
Hey, man, we got to help this guy.
他血都要流光了
He's bleeding out.
他是警察嗎
This a cop?
他看起來好像一個警察哦
He looks like a cop.
護士您好
Excuse me, ma'am.
我是Ray Bishop 消防57隊
Ray Bishop, Ladder 57.
幫我們找個醫生救治這個人
We got to get this guy some help.
我們要走過去
We got to move it along here.
- 跟我來 - 好 兄弟 起來
- Follow me. - Okay, come on, buddy.
來來來
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
就這樣 就這樣
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
好的
You're all right.
有個腹部受傷的患者
Abdominal wound!
到了
There we go.
哪兒呢
Where? Where?
放2號床
Put him in Two.
上2號床
In Two.
測量下他的生命體征
Let's get vitals.
- 好了 到了 兄弟   - 好 就把他放這裡
- All right, buddy. - All right, get him right here.
我們需要脫下你的衣服
We got to get your shirt off.
如果需要緊急創傷救治就告訴我
Let me know if you need trauma.
- 哦我去  - 好  我們開始了哦
-  Oh, shit. - Okay. Here we go.
-慢慢來 慢慢來  - 你倆去6號 6號
- Nice and easy, nice and easy. - I'll meet you at Six. Six.
你可以嗎 你會好起來的
You okay? It's gonna be okay.
他是你朋友
He's one of your friends?
不是啦 只是純幫忙而已
No, no, no. I-I was just helping him.
是啊 Scott 把他帶過來而已
Yeah, Scott brought him in.
那人是在我們出任務的時候
You know, guy just kind of wandered into the firehouse
不知怎麼的自己走到消防站去的
while we were out on a call.
把衣服脫了 衣服上都是血跡
You guys are covered in blood. Take these off.
把它們放這裡
Throw 'em here.
放那邊去
Put 'em over here.
放那邊就好 那下面
Just leave 'em there Down there.
那是啥
What's that?
- 你背上的是啥呢 - 哦 那個啊
- What's that? - Oh.
我是你兒子的紋身練習對像
I let your son practice on me.
看起來怎麼樣 他還沒創作完 不讓我看還
How's it look? He won't let me see it till it's done.
我看下
Let me see it.
他說想紋啥都可以的
He, um, he-he let me do whatever I wanted, so...
天啊
Jesus Christ.
他沒在我背上搞什麼亂七八糟的吧
He didn't put anything stupid on there, did he?
他搞好久了都還沒完成
Took forever.
沒
Nah.
呃 我眼睛老紋不好
Yeah, I, um... I can never get the eyes right
我好像把它們畫得過深了點 但是 我
'cause I-I just make them too dark, but I-I...
很美啊
It's beautiful.
我為你驕傲
I'm proud of you.
- 你真的紋得很好  - 謝謝
- You could really do this. - Thanks.
沒有中文字吧
There's not any, like, Chinese characters
有中文字
or anything back there, is there?
沒有沒有
No, no.
沒有
No, no, no.
你跟我說不要搞那些 我就沒搞了
You told me not to.
我很聽話的
I would never disobey you.
Ray 謝謝你 讓他在你背上練習紋身
Thank you for letting him do this, Ray.
我啥也沒做啊 只是做在那裡
Oh, I didn't do anything. I just sat there.
都是他在幫我紋
He did all the work.
你很享受給我後背紋身吧
You liked going over the spine, didn't ya?
他堅強的很
Took it like a champ.
我一直齜牙咧嘴
I sat there wincing.
哦我的天
Oh, my God.
你倆好歹拉下簾子
Can we at least close the curtain?
- 哦 我的男人們 - 你們 有人在這兒死掉 好吧
- Oh. My guys. - Guys, people die in here, all right?
- 我的男人們  - 哦 過來
- My guys. My guys. - Uh... - Aw, come on.
老媽我才不想跟他擁抱呢 他都沒穿衣服
Mom, I don't want to hug him. He's not wearing a shirt.
-來吧 你受得了的啦 - 老兄 你皮膚太滑了
- Come on, you can handle it. - Ah, dude, you're so smooth.
跟個海獺似的
You're-you're like a sea otter.
好了啦 差不多了
Please, we have to stop.
差不多了
We have to stop. Please. Please.
別抱了 別抱了
Please stop? Please stop.
但是首先 你要先去見Stark老爺和夫人 你還得
But first, you will get to Lord and Lady Stark and you will...
自打那天跟Ray和他同事從消防站
I hung out with, like, Ray and the guys
去酒吧玩兒的時候
from the firehouse the other night at the bar,
他們聊到了老爸的一些趣事
and, um, they were just telling all these stories about Dad.
那些故事我之前都沒聽你說過
And there were stories I never heard of before,
比如說他也嗑藥
like, you know, about him, like, doing coke
他也很搞笑
and being hilarious.
- 是啊  - 你知道吧
- Yeah. - You know?
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
他是很搞笑
Well, he was hilarious.
是嘛
Yeah.
呃
Uh...
他也經常幹些出格兒的事 他很瘋狂
He was also out of control and crazy.
- 聽懂了嗎 - 你不能這麼吼我
- Do you understand? - You can't.
你怎麼都不跟我說
Why-why didn't you just tell me?
不知道啊
I don't know.
可能我是想讓你對他只留下好印象
I just... I wanted you to have some good memories
從而去彌補見不到他的遺憾吧
to offset what happened.
我不知道應該怎麼跟你說這些事
I didn't know what to-to say.
我總不能跟你說 你爹很喜歡跟你一起看卡通
Was I gonna say, "Your dad really loved watching cartoons
因為他總是嗑藥磕到嗨
with you 'cause he was tripping all the time"?
可以啊
Yeah.
聽起來是個好父親呢
Sounds like a good dad to me.
不 你知道嗎
No, you know what?
嗯 我懂
Uh, I get it.
得知他跟其他人一樣也有自己的毛病
Knowing that he had his issues and... problems
我鬆了一口氣
just like everybody else, it makes me feel better.
他是個真正活生生的人了
It really... it really humanizes him.
他是個很好的人
Well, he was a great guy.
他也是個很複雜的人
He was a very complicated guy.
他的心很大
He had a really big heart.
嗯
Mm.
像Ray一樣嘛
Like, like Ray?
呃
Uh...
是吧 是像Ray一樣
Yeah, I guess, like Ray, yeah.
是哦
Yeah.
是的
嗯 你就是對這款的人毫無免疫
Um, I guess you could say that you have a type.
哼
Uh-huh.
是啊
Yeah.
我就喜歡這款的
I have a type.
你知道我雖不常提起他 但
I know we don't really talk about it much, but...
我
...I, uh...
我很想念老爸
I-I miss Dad.
很想很想
A lot.
是啊
Yeah.
然後
And, uh...
我為我之前叛逆的
I'm sorry that I've been
行為道歉
so difficult to deal with.
我會
I'll...
我會努力找到
I'll try and...
自己的生活
get it together.
就是這很困難
It's just hard.
我想總會很困難
I think it'll always be hard.
我
I, uh...
我真的很喜歡Ray但
I really like Ray, but I...
他真應該去刮下鬍子
He's-he's got to lose that mustache.
我的意思是
I mean, come on.
當我和他一起出門的時候
- When we go out in public,
人可能會以為我被他綁架了呢
people think that I'm kidnapped, you know?
就我倆出現在超市的那身打扮
The looks that we get at the supermarket.
人們看著我就像在問
They're like... People-people look at me like,
你還好嗎 我回答 我很好
"Are you okay?" And I'm like, "Yeah, no, yeah.
他是我媽的男票
It's my mom's boyfriend."
- 好了 兄弟 祝你好運 - 謝謝你送我一程
- All right, buddy, good luck. - Thanks for the lift.
老弟 不客氣
All right, man.
自信點哈
Confidence, right?
- 好的 - 加油 你可以的
- Yeah. - All right, go get 'em.
嗨
Hey.
Hi.
你還好嗎
Hey. How are you?
- 你在這裡幹嘛呢  - 呃 我就
- What are you doing here? - Oh, I just, uh...
我就想找你聊聊
I-I just wanted to talk to you.
我今天有公務員考試
Well, I have my civil service test today.
嗯 我知道啊
Oh, yeah, I-I remembered.
所以我才想
That's why I wanted to, you know...
- 我得走了 - 我可以一起去嗎
- I have to go. - Can I come?
啥 為毛
What? Why?
做你的精神支柱啊
You know, for, like, moral support.
我想在你身邊隨時支持著你
I just want to be there for you.
- 好吧 我阻止不了你  - 嗯 那挺好的
- Well, I can't stop you. - Oh, all right, great.
你頭髮真好看
Y-Your hair looks nice.
謝謝
Thanks.
我知道你現在可能想聊
Listen, I know you probably want to talk about
關於我倆的關係這些嚴肅的話題 但是我沒法跟你聊哈
relationship stuff and serious bullshit, but I can't.
我現在必須集中精力學習 才不會搞砸我的考試
I have to study and focus right now so I don't screw this up.
好
Okay.
我
I, um...
如果你願意我可以幫你啊
I can help you, if you like.
你才不會想幫我呢
You don't want to help me.
不 我很想幫你的
Mm, yeah, I do. I would love to.
好 那你幫我測試這部分
Okay, w-will you just test me on this part?
好 那個嗎
Yeah. That one?
- 準備好了  - 好
- All right. - Okay.
開始了哦
Here we go.
Amy必須要在一天內完成3個任務
"Amy must complete three tasks at work.
她預計前兩個任務
"She estimates that the first two tasks
她需要45分鐘完成
"will take her 45 minutes to complete
第三個任務需要花她
"and that the third task will take her
2小時45分鐘完成
"two hours and ten minutes to complete.
如果Amy的估計是準確的話
"If Amy's estimate is correct,
她完成所有任務的總耗時是多少
how long will it take her to complete all three tasks?"
3小時又40分鐘
Three hours and 40 minutes.
你猜的還是你已經知道答案了
Did-did you just guess that or did know the answer?
這就是答案
No, that's correct.
太厲害了
That's incredible.
- 哇 - 還好啦
- Wow.- It's not that amazing.
- 沒有 就是很厲害呢 - 別緊張
- It is, no. - Relax.
都是數學題啊
I-I... Is it all math questions?
應該是了 公務員考試不都這樣
I thought it was, like, city shit.
沒有沒有
No, no.
你得證明你不是個智障
You have to prove that you're not stupid,
這樣他們才會讓你在城市裡工作
and then you can work for the city.
哦哦
Oh. Oh.
看來我是沒法在城市裡工作了
So I can never work for the city.
嘿 我
Hey, uh, I...
我
I, uh...
I, um...
我愛你
I love you.
很愛很愛
A lot.
我一直都很愛你 我
I-I always have, and I, um...
所以我才表現得很奇怪
That's why I always act so weird.
我不知道我要如何表達自己
'Cause I don't know how to express myself.
不遵守秩序
Failure to do so
可能會導致嚴重受傷
could result in serious injury.
- 我要問下一題嗎  - 好
- Should I ask the next? - Yeah.
好 下一題  有250個人
All right, so, "Of the 250 people
在一家醫療機構工作 16% 是文員
"working at a medical facility, 16% are clerks.
多少個是
How many are..."
感謝您乘坐史泰登島渡輪
Thank you for riding the Staten Island Ferry.
我都忘了我讀到哪裡了
I've lost my place.
一家醫療機構有250名員工
"Of the 250 people working at a medical facility,
- 16% 是文員  - 嗯
- 16% are clerks."  - Mm-hmm.
非文員類的職員有幾個
"How many are not clerks?"
答案頁都被你洩露了
You're showing me the page.
你會等到我考完試嗎
Hey, will you wait for me while I do it
然後我們一起回史泰登島
and then we can go back to Staten Island together?
當然啦 你要考多久
Yeah. Of course. How long are you gonna be?
3個半小時
Three and a half hours.
好
All right.
- 真的啊  - 是啊 我去找點事做
- Really? - Yeah, I'll go figure something out.
好
Okay.
嗯 就這麼定了
All right. Cool.
考試加油哦
Good luck.
搞點有文化的
Maybe do something cultural.
拓展下你的視野啥的
Like, broaden your horizons.
好勒
All right.
加油哦 好好考
Good luck. Have fun.
我的天啊  我緊張死了
Oh, my God, I'm freaking out!
好害怕
I'm scared.
♪ 嘿
♪ 跟我說說你對夢想如何看待
♪ 你其實什麼都不清楚明白
♪ 你並不關心明日的挑戰阻礙
♪ 更願意躺在床上滿心悲哀
♪ 我走在追逐幸福的路上 我知道
♪ 並非一切發光的都是金子
♪ 只要得到它一切都會變好
♪ 我也會變好
♪ 我在追逐幸福的路上 我知道
♪ 並非一切發光的都是金子
♪ 只要得到它一切都會變好
♪ 我也會變好
♪ 跟我說說你對夢想如何看待
♪ 你其實什麼都不清楚明白
♪ 告訴我你瞭解多少
♪ 驚夢的昨宵
♪ 凌晨5點 一身冷汗 再也睡不著
♪ 我在追逐幸福的路上 我知道
♪ 並非一切發光的都是金子
♪ 只要得到它一切都會變好
♪ 我也會變好
♪ 追逐幸福
♪ 我會找到它
♪ 會變得更好
♪ 哦 我從未從不
♪ 停下腳步去想
♪ 有一天我會跟你在一起
♪ 暢遊在夢境世界
♪ 但是我來了
♪ 和你在一起
♪ 你是我快樂的源泉
♪ 我的快樂來自於你
♪ 絕不也從未
♪ 我從未停止愛你
♪ 有時候我停下腳步想問
♪ 你在哪裡
♪ 然後讓自己不再想你
♪ 因為我覺得你並不在意
♪ 但是我來了
♪ 又和你在一起
♪ 這回我懂了
♪ 我的心能允許我做的事
♪ 從未 絕不
♪ 未曾停止愛你
♪ 不知道為什麼
♪  一定要玩失去你的遊戲
♪ 才認識到
♪ 我還愛著你
♪ 是的
♪ 但是我在這
♪ 再一次和你在一起
♪ 你是我快樂的源泉
♪ 我的快樂來自於你
♪ 從未 絕不
♪ 未曾停止愛你
♪ 從未 絕不 未曾 寶貝
♪ 從未停止愛你
♪ 我就是無法停止
♪ 從未 絕不 未曾
♪ 不會停止愛你
♪ 寶貝 從來沒有
♪ 從未 絕不 未曾
♪ 不會停止愛你 寶貝
♪ 是的
♪ 絕不 絕不